(Doom at Your Service)
(All characters, locations, organizations, religions,)
(and incidents in this drama are fictional.)
It's a glioblastoma.
You have multifocal glioblastomas.
They are the cause of your dizziness...
and vomiting.
I will find out more with a biopsy.
But the location of your tumors isn't ideal.
I see.
Okay.
Do you perform the biopsy...
on the weekend?
No, I don't.
How many days will it take to do the biopsy?
It will take at least a week.
That won't work.
Pardon?
Then, I can't.
You can't do a biopsy?
No.
I already used some of my vacation days.
So I can't take a week off from work.
Shouldn't you put your health before your work?
I'm not sure.
Anyway, I can't take a week off.
Then, let's not do the test.
If you get the surgery, you'll have a year.
Without it, you'll have 3 to 4 months.
And you won't be able to live normally for that year either.
You may suffer from hemiplegia, a speech disorder,
and a cognitive disorder as well.
Getting a biopsy can be risky enough.
- It's risky?
- Yes.
Will I die?
Yes.
I see.
Okay.
(Neurosurgeon, Jung Seung Jun)
(Event Planning Report for Jung Dang Myun of "Dr. Yeomna")
You can take a look at the report...
for the event schedule.
And I'll also email you the report.
Like I told you earlier,
we made an agreement on the date with the platform.
I know you are busy, but you must send us...
your writing up to the 70th episode by early next month.
Okay.
I know your day job keeps you busy.
But the event is around the corner.
Please keep working hard.
- Okay. I'll call you.
- Okay.
You should give me a call too.
Okay. Mr. Jung.
You can do it.
And you were really cool today. You looked like a real doctor.
Thank you for letting me skip the line for the MRI today.
That was nothing.
I'm a real doctor.
Bye.
Ms. Tak.
Hang in there.
Okay. You too.
May I have your attention, please?
Medical staff is needed at the ER right away.
"Glioblastoma".
Why is he...
I know I'm handsome. But I'm busy.
We have trauma coming in!
Everyone, be ready.
- Move out of my way.
- Please step aside.
(Emergency Medical Center)
5, 4, 3, 2,
One.
- Trauma patients are coming in.
- Out of my way!
- Move!
- This way.
Take the patients.
What's happening?
He needs treatment now!
Step out of the way!
("Deadly Knife Rampage on Five-way Intersection in Gusan-dong")
What happened? So many people got injured.
Was there an accident?
A man at 2:30pm today...
went on a deadly knife rampage in the heart of Seoul.
Seven people, including the bypasser...
who was trying to stop him were injured.
The injured victims were transported to the hospital right away.
- Their injuries are being treated.
- My gosh.
- That's awful.
- And some victims...
- died in transport.
- That's crazy.
The suspect, Kim, - Are you going to pay?
- tried to commit suicide.
- Oh, yes.
(Outpatient, Neurosurgery)
(Total amount: 686.20 dollars)
- This is crazy.
- Pardon?
What? Nothing.
Can I pay this in installments?
For how many months?
If you get the surgery, you'll have a year.
Without it, you'll have 3 to 4 months.
Three months, please.
Okay.
- Hey, get ready for a patient!
- Please take good care of him.
- This way.
- Keep pushing.
Excuse us.
- He needs a doctor now.
- This way.
Oh, no.
- Over here.
- Take that off.
The stab wound in the abdomen is severe.
- And the bleeding is serious too.
- Sir, stay with me.
- Sir.
- His BP is dropping.
Not yet.
- We have a patient!
- This way.
He's here.
- All right. 1, 2, 3.
- 1, 2, 3.
He's the suspect.
He tried to kill himself at the scene.
And the police are on their way here.
A patient is coming in.
I'm sorry. Which department...
Put curtains around the patient.
And don't let anyone pass through other than the police officers.
Yes, doctor.
I'll take it from here. You can leave now.
- Pardon? But he...
- He won't die.
Okay.
Where do you think you're going?
Open your eyes.
I've been waiting. Why took you so long?
You think you're the man of the hour?
You must feel like you're in control.
But I'm in control. You are nothing.
Let me give you an analogy. What you did was...
parking your car in my spot in the most awful way.
That's why I'm feeling awful.
Get your car out.
I bet you didn't know this,
but I'm in control of your doom.
Since you tried to override me, let me do the same for you.
You will not face your doom which you deserve.
Don't worry. When the time is right, you'll get it back.
You'll probably wait for the day of your doom...
because you'll find out that there are worse things than death.
That's called life.
We're from the police.
How beautiful.
You're here.
Don't sound so laid-back.
You should have at least changed your gown.
I didn't, so you could see this.
How can a deity do whatever she wants with the world?
Are you bored at the hospital now?
Try to be a patient here. It's never boring.
Stop throwing yourself a pity party.
I'm like a gardener.
I plant them, water them, and wait with all my heart.
That's all I do.
So you're not responsible for this?
Some don't even get to sprout.
And some bloom late.
Some wilt away quickly.
Some turn out to be medicinal, and some, poisonous.
And some plants will kill everything around them.
Is that my fault?
Pull them out. Plant only the good ones.
And cherish some plants more than the others.
A garden doesn't belong to a gardener.
Then what about me?
What is my position in your garden?
You are a butterfly.
For the flowers in my garden.
Until when?
Forever.
You are way too cruel. Especially to a birthday boy.
Birthday? You think you're human?
Have you ever been born? Or human for that matter?
Go.
Go and become someone's wish.
Today is the only day that's possible.
Even my birthday isn't for me.
For humans.
Darn those flowers.
It's about time they wilt away.
A bus will arrive shortly.
(Glioblastoma)
(Boyfriend)
- Hey, sweetie.
- Are you busy?
No. I'm...
I'm outside. I was meeting up with a writer.
Really? Then can we meet now?
Now?
I need to see you right now.
What's wrong?
Let's talk in person.
Come to that cafe. Okay?
Hey...
Gosh.
- She splashed water on that girl.
- No way.
As you can see, this is all I can do because I'm pregnant.
Can you explain...
this?
You're the one who needs to explain things to me.
You're the mistress.
You expect me, his wife, to explain what happened?
Where did you learn your manners?
I see. That's what happened.
Fine.
That explains everything.
I heard that you met here for the first time.
Did you look through his phone?
You don't think I didn't?
Then you must have seen how he never called me on weekends...
and answered my calls at night.
Whenever I couldn't reach him, he told me his phone died,
it was on silent mode, and he was working.
You must've read those texts then.
That always bothered me.
I knew something was off, but...
Now, this explains everything.
Are you telling me you didn't know he was married?
Yes. I didn't.
You didn't know after dating him for three months?
Stop lying to me!
You didn't know your husband was cheating on you for three months.
Hey!
So you're saying you didn't do anything wrong?
Is that it?
I guess so.
"I guess so"? You're unbelievable.
Then whom should I splash water on?
You can at least take it out on me.
But I can't even take it out on you.
It's all that jerk's fault. What should I do?
Why are you telling me your sob story?
Right.
I shouldn't say that to you.
So...
you can keep blaming me.
What?
Pretend that your gentle, innocent husband...
was deceived by an awful woman and almost ruined his life.
Be it 10 or 50 years.
Live happily with that cheater for a long time.
That will be better for your child too.
- Are you okay?
- Gosh.
- Oh, no.
- I'm not okay.
- Should you go to a hospital?
- Are you okay?
Taxi! Right here!
Right here. Yes.
Wait. Be careful.
Be careful.
Sir, drive us to a nearby hospital with OBGYNs.
The mother is okay.
This happens frequently when mothers are stressed.
- You don't have to worry.
- Okay.
Are you her guardian?
No.
She's just a mutual friend. Something like that.
Do you know her guardian's number?
Yes.
(Boyfriend)
Then can you fill this out for me?
(Jo Dae Han)
(Phone number)
(Relationship to the patient)
(Husband)
We still need to talk.
Let's talk once you feel better.
I knew something was off too.
His excuses didn't make sense.
But I wanted to blame it on you...
because I thought if I did that, it might be your fault.
What I told you earlier...
I meant it when I told you to blame it on me.
Blame me for it because...
I'll die in three months.
I was wondering who's going to hear this news first.
I didn't know that I would be telling you that in this context.
Well, I didn't know that I was terminally ill.
Are you serious?
I meant everything I said at the cafe and here.
So...
you don't have to worry.
And...
I sincerely hope you two will have a long and happy life.
I'm really dying.
Hey, do you think work is a joke?
You left to meet with the writer hours ago.
Why did you come back so late?
You should have just gone home then. Why come back here?
- I'm sorry.
- That's it?
I'm sorry.
(CEO Park Chang Shin)
Are you acting out?
You should just quit. Why don't you quit your job?
You must think earning money is easy.
Kids these days don't have any work ethics.
I wasn't feeling well.
The writer told me to get a scan since I was already at the hospital.
I'm sorry.
This is why I can't hire women.
They always complain that they aren't feeling well.
They are like broken machines.
At least, I can get those machines fixed.
Gosh. I can't even get her fixed.
I don't feel well, either.
You know,
I have rhinitis and a herniated disk.
I feel like I'm dying too.
Gosh.
(Adulterer at Gangnam Cafe Today)
As you can see, this is all I can do...
- because I'm pregnant.
- What?
- Hey, isn't that you?
- Can you explain...
- What?
- this?
You're the one who needs to explain things to me.
You're the mistress.
You expect me, his wife, to explain what happened?
Where did you learn your manners?
That's not me.
You didn't know after dating him for three months?
That is you in the video.
Look at her outfit. You have the same outfit on.
You didn't know your husband was cheating on you for three months.
Hey!
That's not me.
Did you hear that?
She sounds just like you.
Then whom should I splash water on?
Hey!
- What are you doing?
- So what if that's me?
What are you going to do then?
Did you...
just yell at me?
You think I'm a joke, right?
What?
Of course. Even I think I'm a joke.
Why is everyone torturing me today?
I'll take a day off today.
I will.
I already don't have a lot of vacation days left,
so I'll use one today.
You...
What...
That's her in the video.
She said no, so it must not be her.
You think so? That's not her?
Are my eyes going bad?
Once it rains, all the ginkgo leaves will fall.
- Autumn is so short.
- Right.
We can't eat ice cream outside now.
(Adulterer at Gangnam Cafe Today)
Her brazenness is making me shake in anger.
Girls like her must be punished.
I hope she gets sick and dies.
Ms. Wife, hang in there.
People like her rot our society.
They must be incarcerated.
What a huge interest to pay for a three-month fling.
(File-sharing from Yoo Jin)
(File-sharing from Yoo Jin, Accept)
The man in a blue jacket is secretly taking photos.
Be careful.
Hey.
Are you getting a good shot?
What? So you can post it online too?
You dream big, girl. You got nothing to see.
What?
Hey! Stop right there!
What's wrong with you? Why are you chasing me?
Move out of my way! Move!
- Stop right there. Hey!
- What's wrong with you?
My gosh. Goodness.
Hey!
You!
Come on. Stop him!
Hey!
Hey.
Stop right there!
Are you crazy? Are you drunk?
Hey! Stop him, please!
Hey!
- What the...
- He fell into it.
Is that a sinkhole?
My leg...
What a way to ruin a smoke.
Are you okay?
- Sir!
- Oh, gosh.
Gosh, do you see that?
Are you okay?
You are a butterfly.
For the flowers in my garden.
Why does it have to be this way?
Have you ever been born? Or human for that matter?
What's so great about humans?
For humans.
What's so great about those insignificant and mortal beings?
It's raining.
- It's raining.
- I heard it was going to rain.
I'm the only one without an umbrella?
My goodness.
(Tak Brother)
What do you want?
Dong Kyung, can you wire me 500 dollars?
What?
I'm at Jeju Island with my friends.
And we just scratched the car we rented.
- Hey.
- I told them earlier...
that we should get expensive insurance.
But Sang Geun kept saying it'll be fine.
I shouldn't have become friends with him.
But fortunately, I'm not hurt.
I was really nimble.
Sun Kyung.
I'll pay you back next month. Can you lend me 500 dollars?
Do you have a death wish?
Why are you so angry?
I called you because it's urgent.
Hey, do you really have to do this today?
Don't you know what day it is?
Today? Wednesday?
Or is it Thursday?
It's the anniversary of our parents' death.
My gosh, it's that time of year already?
I was in the army last year.
Time really flies.
Just hang up, you punk.
Dong Kyung.
Dong Kyung doesn't have money.
Not knowing how to cry...
has been a habit of mine for a long time.
When I was 10,
I learned how to swallow my tears.
I wonder where all those tears...
ended up going.
Now I finally get it.
They're our family, so someone in the family should raise them.
It's not like you're going to volunteer.
It's not easy to raise someone else's children.
She has a point.
They shouldn't grow up walking on eggshells.
Why don't we just send them to an orphanage...
They'll hear you.
I wasn't able to cry ever since that day.
And all those tears must've...
turned into a lump and took place somewhere in my brain.
Hey, Aunt.
Today's the anniversary of your parents' death, right?
- Did you buy it?
- Cake?
Yes. People will think I'm crazy.
When a family gathers together, you call that a party.
It's way better than spending the day all depressed.
There's someone missing though. Sun Kyung is in Jeju Island.
What a weirdo.
Why did he go there all by himself when neither of us are there?
I guess he doesn't need us.
Aunt, don't give him money, okay?
Why? Did he get himself in trouble again?
Gosh, I should teach that punk a lesson.
How are you going to do that when you're in Canada?
Gosh, it's freezing here in Canada.
I can't believe I moved here at this age for love.
I guess you're doing well...
seeing that you're still talking about love.
How's work?
Are you healthy?
Work? Work is great.
I'm healthy too.
I only catch colds from time to time.
That's good to hear.
I just wish life would continue to be like this.
Really?
You, Sun Kyung, and I have been through enough.
I guess your parents are finally starting to help us from the skies.
Now we just need Sun Kyung to get a decent job.
Hey, it's time for Kevin to go to work.
I'll call you again, Dong Kyung. Don't skip your meals.
Call me if you need anything.
Okay. Don't worry.
Say hello to Uncle for me.
Bye.
I heard I'm going to die.
Do you think it'll hurt...
when I die?
I'll explain everything next time.
(Scum.)
Tak Dong Kyung, your school loan is overdue.
Please check and wire the money.
Korea Student Aid Association.
I just want the world to come to an end!
I want everything destroyed!
Just bring doom to this world!
Please let me win the lottery.
Please help me lose 10kg.
I just want the world to come to an end!
I want to be happy with my family.
I want everything destroyed!
Just bring doom to this world!
I smell alcohol in this wish.
(Small Village Makgeolli)
Gosh, who's here at this hour?
(3:33am, November 24, Tuesday)
My gosh.
Gosh, how annoying.
Seriously.
Hello.
I pranked you so you'd quickly open the door.
- What?
- I'm talking about how you saw...
Switzerland and Italy through the peephole.
Why is he...
Yes, I know I'm handsome.
My gosh. What are you doing here?
You called me here.
What?
I did?
Yes, you called me.
Who are you?
Myul Mang.
You took ages to come to the door, so I thought your house was big.
But it's tiny.
Hey! What...
Don't just stand there. Sit down.
This is my house.
I know. Don't worry about it.
The anniversary of someone's death?
Today's my birthday.
Oh, really? I see.
Happy birthday.
No one's congratulated me on my birthday before.
Don't bother wasting your energy. It won't take long.
You just need to tell me your wish out loud.
What?
- What wish?
- You wanted this world to end.
Just bring doom to this world!
You were listening to me?
You knew where I lived? Were you roaming around my house?
No, I didn't. I'm busy.
Who are you?
What do you want?
Is it cake?
We don't have time. You're going to die soon.
Exactly 100 days later.
What... By any chance,
are you from the hospital?
Do you think a doctor can do that?
No, I'm sure they can't.
My birthday doesn't come easily.
It travels worldwide and through the fates of many people.
So hurry up and make a wish before it's too late.
I didn't know glioblastoma would bring this kind of symptom.
- What?
- I'm hallucinating.
This is so cool.
I guess you need more time.
This situation is very unrealistic, so I understand.
What?
It's okay. My birthday isn't over yet.
See you later.
Is this a dream?
Of course not.
No, wait. My gosh.
I don't get it. I really don't.
It's taking longer than expected.
What's going on? Where am I?
My house.
Sit down. Make yourself at home.
It's his house?
Did I get kidnapped?
I guess you could say that. But to be more exact,
I came into your dream without permission.
My dream?
So you're saying this is a dream?
Seriously?
- Is this real?
- I know you're dreaming,
but have some manners. This is my house.
Look who's talking. You also...
By the way, why do you keep talking to me without honorifics?
You talked to me like that first.
- I did?
- "Just bring doom to this world."
You said it without honorifics, so I thought that's what you wanted.
I wasn't talking to you when I said that.
Then whom were you talking to?
I'm doom itself.
So you're telling me this is a dream?
What?
Where's the front door?
I'm going to go home.
I guess you don't like the location.
It's where you wanted to go.
It's for the cake.
So are you saying...
you're doom?
I'm responsible for everything that dies or gets destroyed.
Then why not end the world yourself? Why do you keep asking me for help?
Do you think I haven't tried?
It didn't work.
It's probably because I'm just a small part of a system.
What? I don't get what you mean.
In other words, you guys have more authority than I do.
It's how mother nature works.
But this time, I'm hoping it might be different...
because it's what a human being wants.
But why does that have to be me?
No one's ever looked up to a shooting star...
and made a wish like you.
Then do you disappear if you don't grant a wish?
That's what happens in fantasy novels.
Of course not.
It's just a small event.
I was told to become someone's wish on the day I was born.
Is this a nightmare?
Your life is a nightmare.
What?
Unfortunately, it's time for you to wake up.
It was a dream.
It was a dream. I swear it was.
Look at all this dirt.
My gosh, that crazy punk!
Is he American or what?
My gosh.
I'll help you feel no pain.
You won't feel any kind of pain as you die.
What do you say?
I'd like a roll of gimbap.
Fine.
I'll grant you another wish.
Not something you wished for when you were drunk...
but something you truly want.
But this is as far as I can go.
(Original Gimbap)
Let's not listen to the lunatic.
Don't listen to him.
My gosh, does everyone in the city go to work using the subway?
Why can't they all just disappear?
See? You also want it.
You...
I'm sick. I'm definitely sick.
Ms. Tak.
Thanks to the cafe owner downstairs,
I postponed my resignation to tomorrow again.
Ms. Jo, about yesterday...
Mr. Park isn't coming to work today.
He probably went to kneel before his girlfriend again.
- What?
- He was too hysterical yesterday.
So we assumed he fought with his girlfriend again.
Da In heard them fight on the rooftop.
Apparently, it was a huge mess.
He really needs to stop bringing in his private life to work.
Thank you for this.
Sure. Enjoy your coffee.
Just don't get furious and end up quitting your job.
If you quit, we'll have to suffer. You know that, right?
Why aren't you answering me?
Hey.
Ms. Tak.
The writer for "Siberia" is in the meeting room.
Already?
It's not time for the meeting yet.
Writers can be really self-centered.
Where's the writer?
He's inside.
There he is.
Are you a stalker or an American? Just choose one already.
I also sold gimbap and was also a doctor.
What did you do to them? It's like they're bewitched.
I really did bewitch them.
This is driving me crazy. Have I really lost it?
No, you haven't lost it.
The writer is wandering around somewhere. I needed time with you.
How do you know?
I know because I sent him somewhere.
No, not that. How can you read my mind?
I guess you're a little dull.
By any chance, are you...
I have a question for you.
Why do you work here if you hate the CEO and the firm?
Should I get rid of your CEO for you?
I can make it happen if that's your wish.
Stop reading my mind.
To be more exact, I hear things. I don't read them.
Stop listening.
Then accept my offer.
I'm unable to read or hear the minds of those who make a promise with me.
Get out.
I'll just leave instead.
I'm going to go and meet Ms. Lee Hyun.
Thank you for the coffee.
Ji Na.
Hey, I just woke up.
Why are you calling? Aren't you going to come anyway?
Something's driving me nuts.
What happened? Did your CEO bother you again?
A doctor... No, this American...
No, this crazy guy... I mean, this guy who sells gimbap...
- Gosh, where do I begin?
- What?
("Welcoming the Destruction of Lowell")
Never mind. I'll tell you when we meet.
Nothing changed even after I was told that I'll be dying.
You're not scared of things you can't see...
such as death or destruction.
But once they become visible,
your fear suddenly becomes real.
Pain...
is real.
Oh, dear.
Tell me. Who's having fun playing around with my life?
Hey!
The deity is on my side.
Choose. Will you die here and now?
Or will you take my hand?
And the answer is...
Me.
And just like that, I held Myul Mang's hand.
(Doom at Your Service)
You said to become a human's wish.
But that human's wish happens to be doom.
Why me? Why? Why must it be me?
Fate.
Smile.
Why are you so nice to me all of a sudden?
Get off me!
I'll take care of it. You should go inside and eat.
Shall we meet again tomorrow? Should I go pick you up?
What's with you?
You should be a bit more clingy.
What? To you?
No, to your fate that came to you.
Dramaday.net