RECORD OF YOUTH
THIS PROGRAM HAS BEEN SELECTED AS AN
"EXCELLENT BROADCAST CONTENT" AND IS SUPPORTED
BY THE MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS, TOURISM
AND THE KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
The answer is clear,
but I still don't know what to do.
What's your answer?
To be like you, of course.
What's up, guys?
-Did you invite him here?
-Yes.
Didn't you want me here?
-Switch places.
-Why?
Just get up already!
Now I'm the one who's pissed off.
What do you have against me?
Your mom's really scary.
You remind me of her.
Thinking about that day
still makes me shudder.
First my sister and now my mom?
You prick--
There's no need to get worked up over it.
Hae-na punched me more than enough.
-Like a brother, like a sister--
-She's nothing like me.
Damn it. Screw this.
I'm going home.
But I just got here.
That's exactly why I'm going.
He must have gotten an earful from my mom.
How does he expect
to date my sister like this?
He seems to have lost some weight.
I doubt it's easy for him.
What about you?
Can you really let Jeong-ha go?
I still can't believe it.
We haven't been in contact much.
I still feel like I can meet her
if I just call her.
But when I'm reminded
of her last expression
it feels harder.
The guilt is too much.
I'm sure that Jeong-ha
broke up with you for your sake.
Do you think so?
Because you would have to sacrifice a lot
if you chose her over your career.
You have a lot to lose.
But I can't stop thinking about
how I can be of any comfort
or be significant to anyone
when I can't even protect someone I love.
Those who love and support me must believe
that I'll protect them
like I protected Jeong-ha.
Truth prevails, right?
Neither of us said anything.
Words weren't exchanged,
but we remember everything
down to all the small movements.
RECORD OF YOUTH
Have you been well?
I've been trying to.
Congrats on the success
of your recent show.
I was worried a little
because the scandals dropped the ratings.
But I guess you were meant
to find success.
It's not raining anymore.
It stopped around the time we got here.
I need some air.
FINALE
In movies and dramas,
there's always foreshadowing
before something important happens.
But you skipped all that
and ended our relationship.
At least tell me what I did wrong
so that I can change.
You did nothing wrong.
Then why did you dump me all of a sudden?
-Are you upset?
-Yes.
Wanting to protect someone
isn't an old-fashioned notion.
It's a general emotion that we feel
toward a loved one.
I was grateful for how you wanted to
care for and protect me.
I only called it old-fashioned
because it made me want to lean on you.
Then you can.
I'm against being dependent on others.
It reminds me of my mom.
I need a little more time.
I hate unpredictable people,
and I've learned that this could
make me become one too.
I don't like those who generate anxiety,
but now I learned
that I could be that way too.
I love keeping promises,
but I learned how I could become a person
who sometimes can't.
I used to love stability,
but now I'm fond of instability too.
Being in love with you
changed me to be more complicated.
And I actually like it.
Being with you
helped me grow as a person too.
You were able to fulfill your dream,
but I'm just getting started.
Our timing is just off.
Forcing it to be synchronized
will drive us apart.
I'll try harder.
This is exactly why
I wanted to protect you.
I love you.
I know.
All that's left
is for us to respectfully part ways.
You were with me when my dreams came true,
so why can't I do the same?
The emotions I learned from being in love,
and my outlook on life.
That's your gift to me,
and that's more than enough.
I want to be remembered
as a beautiful memory.
Promise me that you'll remember
the time we spent together.
Okay.
Good.
Could you move more dynamically this time?
All right.
That doesn't seem natural at all.
Let's check the photos.
Hey. You should put those down.
-Aren't they heavy?
-Yes.
Sir, he looks good head-on,
but he looks better from the side.
I know.
Just leave it to me, okay?
Are you his manager?
-Yes.
-You must be very fond of your model.
We're good here,
so change into the next outfit.
-Want some water?
-No, I'm good.
You look down today.
Are you sick?
No, I'm good.
Are you acquaintances?
He's Hye-jun's father
and that's his grandfather.
Hye-jun's father…
Hye-jun?
Sa Hye-jun?
Yes, hello.
Jin-u already knows,
but I'm good at headshots and--
If the job brings in cash, he's your man.
-He wants to work with Hye-jun.
-I see.
Are you cutting me off
because you're quitting soon?
-Are you quitting?
-I want to pave my own way.
I can't work for others forever.
Others? Is that what you think of me?
He's only quitting because
he's friends with Hye-jun and Hae-hyo.
He thinks they'll work with him.
But Mr. Sa, the photos
I took of your father
will prove how talented I am.
That being said, could you perhaps
put in a good word for me
with Hye-jun?
I'm afraid I'm not that good with words.
I understand what you mean,
but I can still find the right words
when needed.
Honestly, sir. That rejection was like
a stab to the chest.
Rather than Hye-jun,
let me introduce you to the model
I have high hopes for.
-In five years, he'll make it big.
-Mr. Sa, that's ridiculous.
It'll only take three.
Jin-u, once you open your studio,
I'll only do shoots there.
But that's unfair. Shouldn't you--
He's just using his connections.
Jin-u, I'll put in a good word for you
with Hye-jun.
-Thank you.
-But how is that fair?
Mr. Yang, I've known Jin-u
for nearly 30 years.
We shared time, emotions, and even money
over those 30 years.
He shouldn't be on the same level
as someone I met three hours ago.
You work on your own connections.
It's all we have in the end, right?
Then let me join you.
-What's Hye-jun up to today?
-Hey, go back to work.
Mr. Sa, could you stand in the center?
Come in.
-Hello.
-Yes, hello.
We could have just talked over the phone.
A lawsuit is a pretty big deal.
I should deliver the news in person.
This is for when you need a sugar rush.
Right, thanks.
This is so that Hye-jun
will renew his contract with you.
Not at all.
Can't you change the name of your agency?
No! Why must you…
I mean,
Gyeong-jun, the complainant
has dropped the charges.
The case will be closed soon.
Why do people get upset
when they get called out?
I've met a fair share of people
in the generous years I've lived,
and you definitely have
somewhat of an odd personality.
Is that a compliment?
It is.
Let me tell you something.
Try to keep a straight face
if you're going to lie.
"It is." Is this good enough?
Yes, I guess that will do.
Anyway, do you want to have lunch?
Why is he being nice? Fine, let's go.
It's from a department store.
It was pricey.
I've never received chocolates before.
THE PRESENT
CONTRACT
CEO: LEE MIN-JAE
SA HYE-JUN
I may seem nonchalant, but I'm not.
If you say you'll leave,
I'll beg you not to.
Hye-jun.
I made gimbap, your favorite.
You can never go wrong with gimbap.
What were you reading?
-My contract.
-I see.
If Jeong-ha's less busy now,
let's reschedule.
What's wrong? Did you two argue?
No.
Even if I want to,
she won't engage in an argument.
Did you two break up?
THE FIRST HUMAN ENDS
WITH 21.5 PERCENT IN RATINGS
And Sa Hye-jun lives to tell the tale.
How do I get him to sign with me?
Tae-su.
I'm in trouble.
You moron. You're such a pain in my ass.
-In what way?
-Remember Min-jeong?
She's blackmailing me.
Who's Min-jeong?
That must be her. I told her to come here.
Come in.
Hello, sweeties.
I basically feed you girls.
-Wait, is someone going to give us a meal?
-We can pay money for a meal ourselves.
I don't mooch off anyone.
You're so dense.
What are you doing here?
Do-ha said we should talk to you instead.
Talk about what?
I may work at a hostess bar,
but that doesn't mean you can insult me.
When did I insult you?
You said I was dense, did you not?
But you are.
Facts aren't insults.
I'm not the only one.
You're just as dense as I am.
Do-ha.
We should talk.
She wants 500 million won to settle.
-Take care of it.
-What did you do with her?
This is all your fault.
You said it was a safe place.
Little did I know
that you'd become a regular there.
I never do anything halfheartedly.
Technically, it's your fault
for taking me there.
Show me all the texts and calls
you exchanged with her.
Where's your recording device?
Is it your phone?
I know you're recording this.
Who put you up to this?
Was this your idea?
As if.
I've shared all the communication
that Do-ha engaged in with me.
I could report you to the cops.
Sweetie, have you learned nothing
from celebrities
who went downhill
after a scandal like this?
This is something you need to silence.
If not, then call the cops.
-I have nothing to lose.
-As if.
You'll have to spend time in prison. You…
You're being recorded.
It won't be boring since your friends
will be joining you though.
I checked the texts and photos
that you two exchanged.
You're right.
It would hurt Do-ha's career.
But
he's not married
and he doesn't have a girlfriend,
so what's the issue?
Tell me.
Is it a crime to fall in love
with a girl who works at a bar?
Get lost.
Where are you off to?
I'm going to the library.
Be back before dinner then.
I'm going to Hae-hyo's early tomorrow,
so I might miss you.
I want you to stop working at Hae-hyo's.
-Why?
-Your son is rich now.
You being rich has nothing to do
with me having a job.
It does.
One of the reasons I wanted to earn money
was to provide an easy life for you.
-I don't want to be indebted to you.
-What if your health worsens?
You complain about
your bad knees and back.
I never did such a thing.
You groan when getting up from a chair
and massage your back often.
Mom,
if you love me,
please do what I want this time.
I want to thank everyone
for subscribing to my channel.
This will be the last video I upload.
I haven't been invested
in the channel much,
but most of all,
my view on life has changed.
Instead of wanting a stable life,
I've decided to enjoy
the current instability.
I thank everyone
who has helped me grow as a person.
FULL MAKEUP COUPON
I had no idea you had won this coupon.
What are you filming today?
Nothing.
Then why use the coupon?
As an excuse.
You probably find me uncomfortable now.
I do.
But I still need to work,
so I won't reject clients.
That's the An Jeong-ha I know.
Use the coupon another day.
Do you have any upcoming projects?
No. I'm enlisting instead.
The military?
I guess you have to.
I have the day off,
so let's shoot some hoops tonight.
Basketball only gets better after dark.
You work till late,
so tell us when to meet.
Aren't you guys busy?
You keep calling me.
And you come out whenever we call you.
You guys are famous. I'm not like you.
I'm not famous. Hye-jun is famous.
He didn't deny it.
He knows he's famous, too.
What's next for you?
Next?
-I'm not sure.
-That's not a workaholic's answer.
I might enlist now.
-Are you crazy? Don't be ridiculous.
-Why is that ridiculous?
You didn't go when people pushed you.
If you go now, you have a lot to lose.
Why would you?
I've always thought about it.
It's not a sudden decision.
Same here.
You can afford to take a break now,
but not Hye-jun.
I told you to postpone it
as much as you can.
Money is one thing,
but you'll be 30 when you're done.
You won't be able to play
a young character.
Hey, I'm asking
because I'm really curious.
How much does a top star
like Hye-jun make a year?
-I wouldn't know. I'm not a top star.
-I don't want to discuss it.
I won't ask you for money.
Come on, tell me.
Gosh, I should go home.
I have an early morning
for an honorary ambassador gig.
Go ahead. I'm going to talk to him.
Bye.
What is it?
Come with me.
I fulfilled my dream,
but I still have one homework left.
The faster you finish your homework,
the more relieved you become.
Hye-jun told me to quit my job.
What should I do?
Must you think about it?
Just quit.
What?
He paid back our debt.
And he bought the house,
so we don't pay rent.
We should listen to him.
You are very realistic.
It must be embarrassing to accept his help
given how you treated him back then.
I should admit it when I'm wrong.
Come in.
When did you come home?
Just now.
Let's have a family meeting.
Set a date and tell me.
Do we need a family meeting?
-What is it about?
-I'll tell you then.
What is this about?
I don't know.
Even if my mom was horrible to you,
don't hate her.
I don't hate her. She's Hae-na's mother.
Hey, do you put Hae-na before me?
Yes, I do. Do you think I'd put you first?
I'll support you
regardless of the decision you make.
Of course, you should.
Don't brag about it.
You sound like
you're going away or something.
This was my way of trying
to be civil about my feelings.
-But you were annoying earlier.
-How so?
You said I can enlist now
when Hye-jun shouldn't.
Are you saying that
because my career didn't take off?
Yes, this is more like you.
Oh, no. Hae-hyo, did I hurt your feelings?
I'm sorry. Have a shot.
Don't talk like that again.
Sure. I'll talk like that again.
Pour me a shot, too.
-Did you drink?
-Yes.
Who were you with?
With the guys. Hye-jun and Jin-u.
Your friends?
Goodness. I can't believe you.
I just don't get you.
Aren't you upset when you see Hye-jun?
Yes, I get upset. I even get angry.
I think, "I tried my best,
but why didn't my career take off?
What does he have that I don't have?"
I come up with nothing.
When Hye-jun and I were out together,
I used to be the center of attention.
But not anymore.
How do you think I feel?
But Mom,
I like myself.
I'm not a loser, at least.
I wished the best for Hye-jun,
and I was truly happy for him
when things worked out.
I didn't let his success
make me feel inferior.
And I still believe that I can make it.
You raised a good son.
You didn't fail.
You were gloomy earlier.
But you seem happy now.
It turns out I raised a great son.
Hae-hyo is very good-natured.
Are you rationalizing your failure?
Once his contract matures with his agency,
I should step in and take the reigns.
Tell him to go back to studying.
He needs at least a master's degree
to get a position at our school.
Yeong-Won-Hae Entertainment.
What do you think?
It's named after our names.
Hae-na can be the legal advisor
for our agency.
Whatever.
You never give up. Goodness.
How can I give up on my children?
Why are you in my room?
I don't have a TV in my room,
but I don't want to go downstairs.
I was with Jin-u.
I'm neutral.
That means you're on Mom's side.
I know that Mom has sway over you
and you fall under her influence.
-Are you any different?
-No!
I'm even worse.
I want to go shopping with Mom.
I want my life back.
I'll support you
regardless of the decision you make.
I bet that's what you said to Jin-u, too.
Right.
It's up to you to choose,
and I'll support you for it.
-Hi.
-Put on your seatbelt.
Okay.
Is there anything I can do to help
with your studio?
Study hard and become a lawyer.
How is that helping you?
That way, we'll both be busy,
so it will be easier
even if we can't meet.
Why can't we meet?
Go back to your life now.
We loved each other.
That's all I need.
Right now,
we aren't strong enough to go against
our parents and our environments
to protect our relationship.
Don't cry.
I'm not crying.
You have an interview after the ceremony.
The ceremony is about to begin.
Please take your seats.
SOCIAL WELFARE SOCIETY
HONORARY AMBASSADOR APPOINTMENT
Every drama you were in
has become a hit so far.
Is there a secret behind it?
More than anything, it was possible
thanks to the viewers' support.
And all the staff and the cast members
did a great job,
so I think that's why it was possible.
I see. Lastly, can you tell your fans
about the plans you have for the future?
Nothing has been decided yet.
I'm just doing my best
to enjoy the present moment.
-Ae-suk.
-Hey.
You're delivering the side dishes today.
She asked me to cook braised hairtail,
so I brought the sauce
and marsh snails for soup.
Okay. You can cook here.
Where is she?
Today is my last day. I'm quitting.
Why? Are you sick of it?
No. Jin-u won't let me work for her.
He keeps complaining.
I started working as a hobby,
so I don't want it to upset him.
I guess Hye-jun wasn't the only one.
Come in.
You're here.
I made braised hairtail
and marsh snail soup.
You should have cooked it later,
so it's good for dinner.
I'm so glad I decided to quit.
I think you need to find another cook.
I can't work for you anymore.
Jin-u must have talked to her.
Okay. Thank you for everything.
She won't even stop me.
Okay. Goodbye.
Please don't be offended by it.
I'm sure you would have done the same
thing if you were in my shoes.
I don't think I'm following you.
Why would I be offended?
And what would I do the same?
I thought Jin-u talked to you.
Her ego must have been hurt
because Jin-u asked me to quit.
But she's twisting her words.
He did talk to me.
She doesn't seem angry at all.
What is this?
Actually, that's what
I wanted to tell you.
Please don't be offended by this.
My son told me to quit
because this job might be taxing on me
and he's worried about my health.
I get that your pride is hurt,
but let's get this straight. Okay?
Then, goodbye.
Goodness. What was that?
The braised hairtail is done,
so I turned it off.
Thank you. I was waiting for her to leave.
Well…
What is it?
It's nothing. It can wait.
Go ahead. If you don't tell me after that,
I'll be more curious.
I think I need to quit.
Why are you doing this to me?
I'll give you some time.
Try to find someone else.
Did you plan it with Gyeong-mi,
so you can make things hard for me?
It's sad that she quit,
but I can handle it.
But I can't lose you.
That's why I wanted to keep working here,
but it's because of Hye-jun…
I have nothing to say to that.
He wants me to quit
because it's too much work for me.
I know that you have money,
and I know it won't work
even if I offer you more money.
Is he the only one that matters?
Do I not mean anything to you?
What's she saying?
It's not like we're dating each other.
I'll finish my work quickly and go home.
Do whatever you want.
But just don't quit.
My gosh. Who is this guy?
Did you just finish?
You're doing great, Yeong-nam.
You look dashing.
Aren't you glad you listened to me?
This is only part-time.
My father doesn't have a lot of work yet.
I'm sure he'll do well.
Don't discourage him
like you did to Hye-jun.
I won't do that.
Here.
What's this?
My father did an ad for a health drink.
I got a box.
-I put it aside for you.
-Thanks.
I would invite you to my home
and have dinner,
but we have a family meeting.
Dad.
Hey.
Hello.
Gyeong-jun, when are you getting married?
If you ask such questions to singles,
you get a fine nowadays.
It starts at 10,000 won.
I won't ask.
-You did. Pay up.
-Gosh.
Bye, Yeong-nam.
-Bye.
-Thanks, Yeong-nam!
Sure. Bye.
-Did you take a shower?
-Yes.
Why are we having a family meeting today?
Tell me first.
Why?
Well, you know…
Is this about buying a car for Grandpa?
Does he want a car?
No. I just thought
you called for a meeting
to upgrade the car Dad has.
I can just do it.
We don't need a family meeting for that.
Do you want a car?
Gosh. Why would I want a car?
I'm a mere employee.
I like SUVs.
Buy it yourself.
-How will I do that?
-You're working, aren't you?
Hye-jun, you definitely
need a financial advisor.
You have to make investments.
This house wasn't a good investment.
You should've bought one on the other
side. Redevelopment takes forever.
Then, I would have taken out a loan.
You're supposed to buy a house
with a mortgage loan.
I don't like loans.
Remember what Dad said?
There's always interest to pay
even if you don't work.
Can't I go back to school?
Go ahead. Why are you asking me?
It's your life.
I don't want to work.
What do you want to tell me?
-I want to be adopted as your son.
-Gosh.
I'm just jealous.
Let's go upstairs and eat.
It's been a while
since we all had a meal together.
I hope we can have family meetings often.
What is it about?
Yes, I'm curious, too. What is this about?
I'm going to enlist.
Did you get drafted?
-No.
-Hey.
Postpone it until you can.
Why would you go now?
I have to go anyway.
He didn't go when we pushed him,
but he wants to go now.
But things worked out because
he didn't go when we pushed him to.
You have to work while you can.
You should be working now.
You'll lose the momentum if you go.
What momentum?
What? I mean…
Fine. Let's say you took a break
from eating jjajangmyeon.
Do you want to continue eating it?
No, it'd be soggy.
Why would you use that example?
Am I a jjajangmyeon?
You became famous overnight,
and you don't have a strong fan base now.
When you come back, you'll get old
and might have to start from the bottom.
It's not just about that.
You worked so hard
to achieve what you have now.
People finally recognize your talent
and are supporting you.
This is fun for you.
I want you to join the military
after enjoying it as much as you can.
Once you come back from the military,
you won't be young anymore.
You don't have to be
in your 20s to be young.
He has a point.
I'm in my 70s,
-but I still feel young.
-Grandpa.
Father.
-If we're against it, will you not go?
-No.
Why are you asking us then?
I didn't ask.
I just announced that I was going to.
You can be so stubborn at times.
-He takes after you.
-What have I done?
Look at him. He always tells us
after he decides.
He makes all the decisions.
So Gyeong-jun takes after me.
And Hye-jun takes after Yeong-nam?
-No.
Don't you want me to resemble you?
And you? Don't you want to resemble me?
You're overreacting, Dad.
You should have happily accepted it.
He has the most power here.
Why would you…
I don't have the most power.
Grandpa is right here.
Hey, all power derives from money.
Where are you going?
-It's over.
-Dad.
You'd want me to resemble you, right?
What good will come from that?
You should take after your mother.
You completely spoiled the mood.
I know you didn't mean it, but it's nice.
They should take after me?
I meant it.
Hye-jun doesn't take after me.
He takes after you and Father.
He resembles you a lot in many ways.
Stop it.
Things worked out for him
because he doesn't take after me.
I want him to continue living
a happy life just like Father.
You don't hate Dad, right?
Why would I hate him?
Dad did everything he could to raise us.
"Us"?
No.
I didn't always enjoy being his favorite.
At times, I was jealous of you
because you had freedom.
I guess you're right in a way.
But I do feel distant from Dad.
You're supposed to build intimacy.
You can't be close overnight
because you want to.
LEE MIN-JAE
SUPERSTAR SA
Let's discuss the contract next Friday.
You startled me.
My gosh.
Why are you here at this hour?
I forgot something.
You could have picked it up tomorrow.
It will go bad.
Chi-yeong.
Do you really not
want to be an actor again?
No.
I don't want to give up on food,
and I hate memorizing lines.
-Pick up Hye-jun tomorrow.
-He told me not to come.
He's driving here.
He didn't renew it yet, right?
He goes to places alone a lot.
Ms. Lee, stay on your toes.
-Bye.
I can still make a living
with what I've got.
Sorry, am I too early?
I'm Lee Jin-a.
Jin Seo-u recommended you to me.
Oh, it's fine. I should have come earlier.
Jin Seo-u is…
She was in The First Human.
Right. Come on in.
Thank you.
-Do you like it?
-Yes.
By the way,
why did Jin Seo-u recommend me?
I heard Sa Hye-jun asked her to do it.
Didn't you date him?
I think he called you his girlfriend.
No, we didn't date.
JJAMPPONG ENTERTAINMENT
LEE MIN-JAE, SA HYE-JUN
I'll keep rooting for you even if
you don't want to renew the contract.
-I want to enlist.
-What?
We can postpone it again.
You can enlist next year.
You're about to renew seven ad contracts.
Director Mark James said
he'll send you a script.
You might debut in Hollywood next year.
Let's wrap things up.
I can't stop you, of course.
But why now?
Because it's the soonest.
I've put my name on the map.
A two-year hiatus
doesn't scare me.
We'll talk again when you're discharged.
Min-jae.
I've thought about it.
Jjamppong is better than jjajangmyeon.
What?
We'll renew it for three years
including my time in service.
No, 4 years. And a 30 to 70 split.
-You take care of all expenses.
-Deal.
Sir, why didn't you answer my calls?
I must've been in the elevator. What's up?
Reporter Kim Su-man called.
What's she saying now?
She wanted to ask about
the debt scandal surrounding Do-ha's dad.
She received many tips.
Tell her to hold off on it
and not to write an article yet.
Yes, sir.
PARK DO-HA
Hi, Do-ha.
What is it that you even do?
Did you see the article?
The article is already out?
Kim Su-man, that woman…
DEBT SCANDAL SURROUNDING
PARK DO-HA'S FATHER
You must be very satisfied
with the article you wrote.
It's been a while.
I always read about what you're up to,
so I feel as though I see you every day.
My articles grab people's attention,
don't they?
You see, Do-ha…
I don't really care about him.
If he falls hard,
I can find another celebrity to manage.
But you picked the wrong target.
I don't want Do-ha to suffer any damage.
You don't feel guilty
about letting others suffer.
But you're not like me.
Do you want to turn out like me?
We need to talk. Come to the library.
I'll read while I wait.
-Let's get out of here.
-I want to read more.
Sorry, I'll get going then.
Did something happen?
No.
Then why are you going home suddenly?
I'm sorry.
You said you had something to tell me.
What is it?
-Nothing important.
-What is it about?
I'm enlisting.
You already told me.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
Right, I did.
Jeez.
The bus is here. Sorry.
More than anything, it was possible
thanks to the viewers' support.
And all the staff and cast members
did a great job,
so I think that's why it was possible.
I see. Lastly, can you tell your fans
about the plans you have for the future?
Nothing has been decided yet.
I'm just doing my best
to enjoy the present moment.
Thank you for watching our interview
with Sa Hye-jun.
They're comfy.
You have to go to Pohang for a shoot?
-I'll tell you about it tomorrow.
-Okay.
-Mom.
-Yes?
All right.
I've decided to focus on the fact
that you're a wonderful person.
I love you.
I love you too.
I'm joining the Marine Corps.
I'm at the barbershop now.
This early?
I'm beating you to it.
Are you serious?
Why the heck are you doing this?
Do your parents know?
Your call will be directed to voicemail…
Why isn't he picking up?
Is he at the shoot?
He's so neat.
He organized his room before he went out.
"To Mom"?
It's for me.
Mom.
You helped me realize I was arrogant
to think I could succeed on my own.
I've now accepted that my background
is also one of my strengths.
Enlisting was my own decision.
I'm joining the Marine Corps.
Take care.
From your son, Hae-hyo.
-Hi.
What are you doing?
Getting together some stuff to give you
before I enlist.
Nice, this is from a designer brand.
Wear it on your grand opening day.
Thanks, friend.
That's not everything.
What? There's more?
Buy equipment for your studio.
Hye-jun!
You're so thoughtful.
Cash is the best kind of gift.
Are your parents here yet?
I wish he had already done it.
He should've just gotten it over with.
He didn't listen when I suggested it.
-Why enlist now?
-Well, he'll be fine.
I think 21 is the perfect age.
Hye-jun, you look radiant.
You're brightening up the whole room.
I wish my mom was here.
If she was here, she'd be all over him,
pestering him to take pictures with her.
Father, say a few words.
What's there to say?
I'm just happy that everyone's here.
Your stature has improved significantly.
Did you have to say that
right at this moment?
It's okay. It's true.
Oh, Mr. Sa. How's your shoulder?
My shoulder?
My shoulders are totally fine.
I know that is not the case
and that you almost needed
another surgery.
-I know too.
-Me too.
Mr. Sa, we all know about it.
Hey, I told you not to tell anyone.
Why didn't I know when everyone else knew?
All right, let's eat.
Oh, Hye-jun. You should say a few words.
Once you enlist, we won't be able
to get together for a few years.
Hey, he can go on leave.
Don't you know?
I already served in the army.
I wanted to hear his voice.
These days,
you can even use your cell phone.
-It's paradise compared to the old days.
-Totally.
-We were cut off from the outside world.
-That's right.
Hey. We also have lots to say
about this topic.
That's right!
We had to serve for 30 months,
but it's only 18 months now.
Dad, I had to serve for 21 months.
I WILL START A LIVE VIDEO
AT 10 P.M. ON SEPTEMBER 7
THERE'S SOMETHING I WANT TO SAY
TO ALL MY FANS. PLEASE JOIN ME
I should just enlist too.
Or maybe I should stop working with you.
You and Reporter Kim Su-man
used to be close.
But she's attacking you now.
She's attacking you, not me.
Because she's jealous of you.
Why is a reporter jealous of me?
Because you're successful.
People refuse to give me credit
for my hard work.
They think I made no effort.
My dad put me through hell.
Now, people are trying
to take me down using my dad.
It's all because you're too handsome.
People only give value to things
that were gained through effort.
You didn't have to work
for your good looks.
Some things can't be obtained
no matter how hard you work.
Well, that is true.
Even plastic surgery
won't give you this face.
Exactly.
We'll postpone your enlistment
for as long as we can.
The world will be your oyster
once Hye-jun joins the army.
And when he comes back,
his young, fresh charm will be gone.
You'll enlist
when you're about to lose such charm,
so you'll be fine.
I'm sorry.
Can I get your autograph?
Why are you sorry?
I don't want to interrupt your alone time,
but my grandkid is a huge fan of yours.
I want to make him happy.
I'm sorry.
What's your grandson's name?
Kim Him-chan.
Thank you.
CONNECTION PENDING
BROADCASTING LIVE
Hello. It's me, Sa Hye-jun.
This is my room.
Growing up, what I wanted the most
was my own room.
And that wish finally came true
a little while ago.
Now that I have my own room,
I have more time
to have a conversation with myself.
I thought about who I'm most grateful to.
It's you guys.
Thanks to your love and support,
I've come to appreciate
what society can do for us humans.
I am joining the army
to complete my military service.
I promise you I'll come back
in good health.
REALLY?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
DON'T GO
2 YEARS LATER
Can you organize the client list again?
I'm on my way to the broadcasting station.
I'll be back by five.
When's the show supposed to air?
In two weeks.
INCOMING CALL
DIRECTOR LEE HYEOK
Su-bin, the director is calling.
Okay.
Hello, An Jeong-ha speaking.
An outdoor shoot?
Sure, no problem.
-We have to get there before they do.
-Don't worry. We're 30 minutes early.
-Are you that excited?
-Yes, I'm thrilled!
I've always wanted to work
with the writer of I'm Sorry, I Love You.
It's finally happening.
Don't be too chatty.
I have to attend Grandpa's award ceremony.
I've already told them
that we have to leave in an hour.
You're very good at your job. I approve.
All right, let's go in.
THE 15TH RESTART ACADEMY AWARDS
The Restart Academy Award Ceremony
has a long history.
We will now present the Achievement Award.
-Are you nervous?
-He worked tirelessly
-I'm fine.
-across many different fields.
Do you want some water?
-No, I can't go to the washroom.
-I am honored to have worked with him
-I'm here.
-over all those years.
We chose him as the winner of this award
especially because the advertisers
love him very much.
The winner is Mr. Sa Min-gi.
He's our oldest model.
Please give him
another big round of applause.
Thank you.
I wasted
a big portion of my life.
But I was lucky enough to have my son.
My son had to put up with a lot
because of me.
Yeong-nam, if I ever won the lottery,
I was going to give you all the money,
but it hasn't happened yet.
I now know
that I shouldn't waste my life away.
I plan to live each day to the fullest
so that I can repay my son
for all the trouble I put him through.
I'm not sure if I can fully repay him
before I die,
but I'll do
my very best.
ACHIEVEMENT AWARD
I dedicate this award
to my son,
Yeong-nam.
Stop crying.
I didn't even cry that much.
You've been crying
since the award ceremony.
It makes you look like a terrible son.
You've been very good to Father lately.
What's Hye-jun doing?
Hye-jun? Why?
I have something to say.
What is it?
I'm sorry.
I regret it very much.
I wasn't there for you
when you were going through
a rough patch.
It's all in the past now.
It was
because of my insecurities.
What I regret the most
is hitting you.
It wasn't because I hated you.
I wanted to support you
but didn't have the means to.
I was so angry at myself
that I couldn't take it.
Because you are
so perfect and competent,
I felt that there was nothing
I could do for you.
I was scared.
I'm sorry too.
Why are you sorry?
You never did anything wrong.
Since graduating from high school,
you've been financially independent.
I resented you a lot.
That's okay. You can resent me.
It's my own fault. Don't be sorry.
I know
that you did it for my own sake.
Then it's all good.
I really care about you a lot.
I'm just not good with words.
All the resentment is gone now.
I'm at peace
now that I know you approve of me.
I always wanted your approval.
Shall I give you a hug?
-No, thanks.
-Right, not a good idea.
In your 20s,
you learn to detach yourself
from your parents' influence.
Are you going out?
I'm seeing my friends.
You guys haven't changed at all.
Jealous?
-Get going.
-Bye.
Now, we're entering our 30s.
The age at which you can no longer
blame others.
Look at you sitting so quietly.
Is that your seat?
No, sir. You can sit.
-What's with you?
-I'm just being nice.
Why are you being nice?
Can I
do a photo shoot with you at my studio?
-You can.
-Seriously?
-Yes.
-I didn't think it'd be this easy.
It's just a photo shoot.
Right? Why was it so hard for you
to bring it up?
I'll do it too.
What? You guys are nuts.
Are you sure? You're both very expensive.
-Is he losing his mind?
-Maybe.
We should be paying you.
Oh, you're right.
Your hair has grown a lot.
Hey, I was discharged
shortly after you were.
He always wants to emphasize
he went first.
Yes, I do.
Do you want to see my abs?
-No!
-No, what are you doing?
The training's got me ripped.
-Go away!
-I'll show you.
-Are you crazy?
-Don't.
You should train with me.
I can't. I'm shooting a romance drama.
-So you need a hot body.
-I have my eyes.
-What the…
-I'll show you.
-Show me what?
-Look!
-Goodness.
-One!
-Two!
-That's it?
-You're done?
-Is that it?
-Just two a day.
You were bluffing.
-That's more than enough.
-Hey, Jin-u.
LOVE COMES WITH THE RAIN
Looks like there's another shoot.
Let's have a look
before the director gets here.
Sure.
Hello.
It's been a long time.
Those shoes.
They're so comfortable.
Are you going to tell me not to wear them
because we broke up?
I won't, of course.
I hope you don't think
I'm still not over you.
Do you think I'm wearing these shoes
because I'm still hung up on you?
You think and talk a lot
in such a short amount of time.
You don't like it?
I don't dislike it.
When were you discharged?
Didn't you know I was back?
I'm sure it was all over the media.
My work keeps me very busy,
so I don't have time to watch TV.
-You always know what to say.
-I sure do.
You still have to win all the time.
I'll keep losing if I lose once,
so I'd rather win.
You obviously win all the time.
No, I lose all the time.
It's been so long. How have you been?
The same, you know.
How's your studio doing?
It's doing pretty well.
-Do you have many celebrity clients?
-Do you want to come?
I'm going to say no.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING RECORD OF YOUTH
Subtitle translation by Won-hyang Son
RECORD OF YOUTH
#TOP ACTOR HYE-JUN
#HYE-JUN'S RETURN
THE KING RETURNS
RECORD OF YOUTH
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs