RECORD OF YOUTH
THIS PROGRAM HAS BEEN SELECTED AS AN
"EXCELLENT BROADCAST CONTENT" AND IS SUPPORTED
BY THE MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS, TOURISM
AND THE KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
“I can’t believe I got this lucky.
This is such an exciting moment
of my life.
Living an honest life paid off.
I should be grateful.”
Scratch all of that. Damn it.
But why was Hye-jun so handsome today?
Living an honest life doesn't mean
I'll be happy in life.
Nasty people who don’t care about others
always win in this life.
But I’m so glad
that I decided to be your fan.
Are you my fan?
What?
Do you like me?
No.
You probably have to say that.
I understand.
No, I’m really not your fan.
Okay. I'll believe you.
But I have better photos, you know.
Come on.
Okay. I got it. I said you’re not my fan.
-I wasn’t going to say anything.
-Gosh.
You can say it.
I’m Won Hae-hyo’s fan.
Pardon?
I want Won Hae-hyo.
Look. There are two people.
How could you be sure that I’m your fan?
Right. Why was I so sure?
Were you hoping I'd be your fan?
No, I wasn't.
I was mistaken that you were my fan.
I can see how it could be misleading.
I feel less humiliated now.
I hate misunderstanding people.
No way.
-Hae-hyo.
-I'm your fan.
-Can we take a photo?
-Oh, my.
-You're so handsome.
-You're so hot.
-Can we take a photo?
-With my phone, please!
-You're so handsome.
-One, two, three.
-My gosh.
-You're so handsome.
-Can we take a photo, too?
-All right.
That’s the last one, and let him go now.
I’m his mother.
Please don’t get any wrong ideas.
-You're beautiful!
-Bye.
-Ma'am!
-I love you.
I'll be your daughter-in-law!
-What did you need to give me?
-Congratulations.
-On what?
-Did you not hear yet?
You got the role.
You’ll finally be in Choi Se-hun’s movie!
But how did you find out?
-I called them.
-You're such a Mama Bear.
No, I'm just taking care of you.
You’re my creation.
I’m investing all I’ve got in you.
You should invest in yourself.
Who knows? I might betray you later.
I doubt that you can
once you find out
everything I've done for you.
-I need to move out.
-Hey.
I need to get back in now.
Aren’t you happy? You got the role!
I thought you would be really excited.
It’s complicated.
Is it because of Hye-jun?
You must have been nervous earlier.
Why?
You met your star for the first time.
And you got to touch him, too.
It wasn't direct contact.
So you don’t get nervous
unless it's direct contact.
No, I was nervous.
Do you know how nervous I was?
I’ve been nervous since last night.
Hae-hyo is a good guy.
I approve of your choice.
How old are you?
Is it rude for me to ask that?
I’m 26. We’re the same age.
No wonder I felt like we could be friends.
We’re the same age.
Should we speak casually, then?
Sure.
I need to get back in now.
But why did you come here?
Were you looking for me?
What happened earlier wasn’t fair.
You didn't steal her client,
but she misread the situation.
Yes, it was totally unfair.
I know how that feels.
You don’t have to look at me like that.
But why did you use that photo
as your wallpaper? I’m in it, too.
That’s confusing, you know.
I clearly realized today
why I am a fan of Sa Hye-jun
out of all the celebrities.
He has a special ability
to connect with people.
RECORD OF YOUTH
EPISODE 2
-Good work.
Hey.
I took a million photos today.
How many do you think I can use?
It’s up to your photography skill.
Why would he say it like that?
Hey, you are bad at this, too.
Let's see who wins.
-I'll win.
-Jinx.
-Jinx!
Buttercup!
You still act like elementary school kids.
We did meet in elementary school.
-But I met you in kindergarten.
-Fine. Good for you.
I'll remove your makeup. Sit.
Okay. I’m sorry.
You should be getting off work.
It’s okay.
Give me the cleanser. I’ll do it.
-Why are you speaking casually to her?
-Say hi, guys.
We’re friends now.
I’m Kim Jin-u.
You’re so sociable.
Don’t you ever get shy?
No, never.
-What’s your name?
-It's An Jeong-ha.
"An Jeong-ha"? You want to be stable?
You have a fun name.
"Won Hae-hyo"? What do you want?
You have a fun name too.
You’re in! She’s one of us.
Let's be good friends, Jeong-ha.
All right. Let’s go and have
a meal with our new friend.
We're up against Japan today.
We can eat while watching the game.
-I'm buying with the money I earned today.
-Did they already pay you?
They will. I’m using it in advance.
That's so you.
I have something to take care of.
Decide where we’re going.
Where are you going?
Great job. The space you have here…
-is to my liking.
-Thank you.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
-Can you spare me a moment?
-What?
Okay. Can you wait for me over there?
No, you guys talk. I’m done here.
What’s this about?
Can you pay me directly for today’s show?
That’s a hassle. Why?
-Did you end it with your agency?
-Yes. Pay me fast.
You got it, punk.
Hye-jun.
Don’t you have anything to tell me?
I heard this car
goes up to 374 horsepower at max.
It can reach 100km per hour
in just 4,6 seconds.
You must drive faster
with a car like this.
No. I should be on the Autobahn, then.
Do you want to drive?
Sounds great.
Isn’t this your first time here?
Yes, it is.
Aren't you hungry?
I am.
Let's have a simple, delightful meal.
It's scallop, your favorite.
I like everything on this table.
-Can I eat it?
-Sure.
You can open the wine bottle.
When are the others coming?
No one is coming.
You know how this industry works.
That's how they all start.
They have sponsors.
Sir.
-I respect you.
-Respect is a form of love.
But sponsorship is a business.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
I thought you wouldn't come
if I told you it would be just you and me.
My love for you is too big
that I was even willing
to deceive you like this.
It's not about money.
The first time I set my eyes on you--
I think you should stop here.
Let me finish.
I don't want to stop
now that I developed feelings for you.
I won't stop even if you turn me down.
I don't want to hurt you, sir.
If you need to talk to me, go ahead.
You’re so cold.
That’s what makes you hot, though.
-Do you need money?
-I always need money.
If you listened to me five years ago,
you wouldn’t be
where you are now.
I don't hate the life I have now
although I'm not thrilled about it.
I’ll be your agent.
If you want to be an actor,
I can sponsor you
until you become an actor.
I'm sorry.
This is your last chance.
I’ll give you a week to think it over.
Are you okay?
I told you I’d do it.
I should at least be able to do
one-third of it, if not half.
I’m a burden to you.
No, you’re not a burden to me.
To be honest, I’m partially responsible
for your shoulder injury, too.
I know you don’t talk about it,
but I know.
It looked like your shoulder was doing
okay for a while. Are you stressed out?
Hye-jun got the draft notice.
It would’ve been better
if he'd already done it.
Once he comes back, he’ll be 30.
I can’t get any sleep because of him.
Jin-u isn’t exactly doing better, either.
That’s it. Go home.
I won’t be able to focus with you here.
Then let's split the pay
by three to seven.
I’m the boss here. I’ll take care of it.
Go to the hospital.
Don’t just put on pain relief patches.
Okay?
Okay, I got it.
Do you like it?
Your son sent the flowers
to make you feel better,
so I tried my best.
How beautiful.
You’re so good with your hands.
I even won an award
at a drawing contest in middle school,
but nothing came of it since my mother
passed away when I was young.
It’s better for children
when their mothers live long.
-You should live a long life, ma’am.
-Hey, that’s a curse.
-I’m going out.
-Okay.
This is great.
GYEONG-MI
-Hey.
-Ae-suk, Yeong-nam went to the hospital.
His shoulder must've acted up again.
That darned shoulder!
Then, Jang-man must be doing all the work.
He must have been stressed out
because of Hye-jun.
I heard he’s going to
the military this time.
We don't know yet.
He auditioned for a role.
If he gets it, he’ll postpone it again.
I hope he gets it.
If he goes now,
his career would be halted.
And all of his efforts would
come to nothing.
Hopefully, it will work out.
You don't sound interested at all.
Hae-hyo's mom has been helping him
with his career,
so he even filmed a commercial.
He got it because he's good.
Gosh. You're so naive.
He must build his career on his own
to protect it.
It must be hard for Hye-jun.
No one in his family is helping him.
All right. Let's start our class now.
Ae-suk, I must go.
It's time for me to dance.
Lucky you. You have time for dance.
Gosh, this is good.
She's my daughter-in-law and all,
but she’s too good for my son.
It’s so nice to stay at home.
I would have to pay for everything
if I go out.
You were home.
Yes. I like home-cooked meals.
I thought you liked dancing.
If you didn’t eat yet,
sit down and join me.
I’m good.
Does your shoulder hurt again?
Did you go to the hospital?
Hospitals aren't free.
Health is more important than money.
I’m going to die in the end.
Why is that so important?
Not everyone is
awfully health-conscious like you.
If I get sick,
it will only make things worse for you.
This is the least I can do.
You’re a smooth talker, aren’t you?
Why don’t you be one, too? Seriously.
The way he talks to me
makes me want to steal his food
and throw it out.
RECYCLING BIN
Father will like this.
Is there a men’s jacket?
He needs a jacket to go to work.
This will fit.
But if I say I bought it,
he won’t believe me.
And I'm sure he won't wear it
if I tell him the truth.
He doesn’t deserve this.
My goodness.
Damn it.
Dad.
What is it?
Do you need help with the patch?
It’s turning into a chronic condition.
Will you be able to work?
I work because I have to,
not because my body can take it.
You just wait.
When I win the lottery,
you won’t have to work.
You always hope to get lucky.
That’s why you’re living like this.
You always lecture me
whenever you get a chance.
Do you think
I have nothing to say to that?
Yes. That's why you’re not saying
anything back. I know you.
Don’t say something like that to Hye-jun.
How can you call your son a burden?
I was there to stop you last night,
but you’re not supposed to say something
like that to your son.
Words have power.
Did you think I wanted to say that to him?
You never took care of your child.
All you did was go out and play.
You wouldn’t know how to take care of one.
You’re too aggressive.
You’re almost 60 now.
Instead of embracing my mistakes,
all you ever do is criticize me
at every chance you get. Seriously?
That's why you’d never get lucky.
Got that?
You can put it on yourself.
How dare you talk to me that way?
You could just put it on before you go.
Come on.
No one can understand me.
Starting off on the wrong foot
can ruin you completely!
How could you not know that
when you have experienced it firsthand?
Look at me.
I’m not stubborn like you.
I realized my mistake
and came back right away.
People must accept their mistakes
to have a successful life.
If anyone is going to lecture me,
he should at least have a successful life.
Someone with a failed life like you--
Hey, forget about the patches.
Let’s go to the hospital.
I don’t care about the cost. It can’t be
more important than your health.
This is why
you’ve been poor all your life.
Unlike you,
I won’t be a burden to my children.
Where is everyone?
Outside.
-Why are you still here?
-I still have work left.
Why didn’t you say that earlier?
Then, I would have ruined the mood.
I’m a nobody.
That's not true.
Are you going back to the salon?
No, I do free makeup lessons
on the street in my free time.
You’re so diligent.
Usually, my fans are diligent.
Your fans are pretty good.
Seeing how you're quick to agree,
you're his fan.
I see you're still close with him. You’ve
been friends since elementary school.
Isn’t it hard to stay friends that long?
You know that we’ve been friends
since elementary school?
You live in the same district,
but different neighborhoods.
You said you’re Hae-hyo’s fan.
Did you look into me too?
You don’t want to answer that?
Right. I’m a nobody.
That's not true!
Why are you yelling at me?
That makes me almost believe
that I'm a nobody.
Right. Why did I yell?
Why are you asking me that?
It was you who yelled.
I wasn't asking you why.
I was talking to myself.
But think about it.
You say something like that
when you are belittling yourself.
I don't want anyone to say that.
That's why I was strongly
showing you my disapproval.
You said it first.
I was just responding to what you said,
so you don't feel bad.
You can't stand being unfairly treated.
How did you know?
I just found out when you corrected me.
Thanks.
FOLLOWERS, 553K
He has 553,000 followers.
If I could,
I want to buy 10,000 followers,
but he’s not on any projects.
It'll look suspicious.
I'll hike it up when the articles
about the movie get published.
INCREASE THE NUMBER OF FOLLOWERS
FEE: 1,357,000 WON FOR 3,670 FOLLOWERS
YOUR PAYMENT IS BEING PROCESSED
PAYMENT SUCCESSFUL
You’ve been lounging around
now that your exams are over.
I told you to stop eating chips.
You’ll get fat.
Sure.
You have a knack for torturing people.
What are you up to?
Nothing.
If it's nothing, why did you close it?
-Is it…
-What?
I heard having a boy toy is trending
among housewives in Gangnam.
Watch your language.
Your father can be boring,
but I’m very ethical.
Whatever.
-Should I set up a blind date for you?
-That’s so lame.
Then, find a guy
when you go to law school.
-I’ll handle it.
-Suit yourself.
But you can’t just marry whoever you want.
Everyone in the family must approve.
I shouldn’t talk to you
for more than ten minutes.
My stress level is rising.
I’m going to a department store.
I saw a cute pair of sneakers from Chanel.
Are we leaving now?
I'm the one who'll stay by your side
no matter what.
You’re a smart girl, so I’ll stop here.
Is that how you want to get away
with your favoritism?
You're all about him.
All I get from you is
some expensive stuff.
You just wait. Once I'm done
with Hae-hyo, you're next.
-Aren’t we going to the department store?
-I have to change.
You’re shaking your leg,
so something must be up.
What is it?
-I got the role in the movie.
-Tell him.
If you don’t,
he will keep waiting to hear back.
It’s not that easy.
He said he'll join the military
if he's not cast.
Seriously. When I asked him to serve
in the military with me, he said no.
He was preparing for a show
with Gucci, so he couldn't.
Should we tell him to call the studio?
They are closed today.
-You should tell him.
-No, I can’t do that.
I didn’t get the role.
It’s best to hear it from you.
-Then, what do I do?
-Tell him when he’s in a good mood.
I don't know when he'll be in a good mood.
Hey, the match against Japan.
What if we win the soccer match?
-That's awesome.
-Yes.
Nice.
Hey.
Now, give it back.
I’ll carry it to the bus stop. It’s heavy.
It’s fine. I carry this all the time.
You’re so independent.
I have no one to rely on.
That's a surprise.
I thought you grew up comfortably
because you said you were Hae-hyo’s fan.
Why is that?
Aren’t you drawn to people
who are similar to you?
Well, that’s the case with me.
Are you coming?
I’m coming!
See you later then.
Later? There’s no later.
That kind of empty formality isn’t nice.
Give me your cell phone.
Come to our salon.
I’ll give you a celebrity discount.
You’re such a cool fan.
Usually, other fans would skip work
and follow him.
Then, my routine would be ruined.
I should have a stable life myself
before I support someone.
Is that how you got your name?
No, it's because I never decide on things.
-You don't let anything slide.
-If I do, it becomes a habit,
so I don’t.
It sounds like you always win.
I've been losing.
After I quit my office job,
I've been losing a lot.
So are you venting about that on me
when we are total strangers?
You're brutally honest.
People do say I'm straightforward.
SA HYE-JUN
He's not what I had pictured in mind.
-Why are you staring at me?
-Just because.
-Until when will you stare at me?
-Until you leave.
Then, I should go.
Your stare is uncomfortable.
I was talking to a guy, but why does it
feel like I was talking to a doll?
-What should we get?
-Did you wait long?
-Yes, very long.
-I'm sorry.
Jeong-ha, get a grip.
Now, he's real.
Are you still reading that?
I asked my friends,
but they said the contract period
is too long.
Then, don’t sign it.
How can I work with you
if you don’t trust me?
Do you know
how much money and time
I have to invest to help a rookie?
But my friends said if my cut is only
30 percent, it’s not a good deal for me.
Who are your friends? Seriously.
Kids these days are
so calculative and materialistic,
but you’ve got no grit.
How can you succeed with that attitude?
CONTRACT
I’m kind of indecisive.
I’ll think about it again.
You definitely need me.
How could you survive in this industry
when you’re that indecisive?
Others will definitely deceive you.
My mom said I’m not even
good enough to get conned.
-Bye.
-Fine. Leave now.
Who is that? Did you sign that model?
Why would I sign with that loser?
-Why are you here?
-Why do you think?
I came here to check if you paid Hye-jun.
What’s up with me lately?
Only weirdos are coming my way.
Should I proceed with plan B?
Don’t you know anything about Hye-jun?
Do you think he’d ever be a burden to you?
And you still stole
from such a nice kid like him?
I’m trying to make ends meet,
so that's what I did.
He won’t survive. He’s too soft.
He’s too innocent
to be in this kind of industry.
That’s the casting director from Dalman.
They want Hye-jun
for this season’s fashion show.
-That’s great.
-So do you know what I said?
I told them that he retired.
Hello.
Father.
You’re late. That's not your usual route.
I went grocery shopping.
I’m cooking pollack soup.
It’s Yeong-nam’s favorite.
Find anything good?
I found a great suit for you.
-I’ll get it dry-cleaned.
-Anything for Yeong-nam?
I found a jacket,
but I bet he won’t wear it.
I’ll wear it first and give it to him.
I’ll say I bought it.
Father, you’re so smart.
When I hit the lottery,
I’ll buy you a house.
Thank you, Father.
No, I should thank you
for accepting such a lousy hope.
I could never hate you.
There hasn’t been a single woman
who hated me.
I hope Yeong-nam would express
half of what you express.
Okay. Let's go inside. Let's go.
Goodness.
What time is it?
If you’re in pain,
please go to the hospital.
The doctors don’t do anything.
Do you know how expensive a shot is?
Getting proper treatment is cheaper
than taking medicine
and putting on relief patches.
I’ll pay the medical bill.
Stop acting so pathetic over money.
Pathetic?
How could you say that to me?
You’re the one who should know
when to shut your mouth.
I know Jang-man is a close friend,
but don’t talk about our kids.
He’ll find out anyway.
When Hye-jun comes home,
I’ll put an end to this.
Starring in a movie won’t change his life.
-Who knows?
-I’ll eat my hat if that happens.
Stop encouraging him
and don’t say anything.
-Go, Korea!
Kim Min-jae is dribbling.
One more try.
-Yes.
-Shoot!
That was so close.
-Go, Korea!
-Shoot!
-Come on!
Shoot!
-Lee Seung-woo!
Hwang Hee-chan!
Go, Korea!
-Go, Korea!
OUTDOOR PERFORMANCE ZONE
If you have any questions, you can ask me.
Hello.
I don’t wear makeup.
But when the fine dust level is high,
my skin feels a bit itchy and dirty.
There’s a way you can block out
fine dust particles with makeup.
I’m filming a video right now.
If you don’t mind being on camera,
I can teach you.
I’m bad with my hands.
Do you think I can do it?
-Hello.
-Hi.
I'll show you how you can block out
fine dust particles with makeup.
Your skin tone…
Let me check your skin first.
Son Heung-min must be over the moon today.
He deserves to skip his military duty!
He only has good days coming for him.
Good for him.
Isn’t that such an honor as a man?
The real honor should go to young men
who dedicated two years of their lives
to protect our country like me.
Have you had chicken
for all three meals in one day?
-When avian flu breaks out--
-Samgyetang for breakfast.
Braised chicken for lunch.
Fried chicken for dinner.
-What about swine fever?
-Spicy pork for breakfast.
Braised pork ribs for lunch.
Pork belly for dinner.
-I'll throw up.
Hey, you experienced
the military indirectly through me.
I’m sure you’ll adapt well over there
even if you go now.
Am I going to the military now?
The movie studio called.
I didn’t know how to bring this up,
but it’s better to get it over with.
You’re so cruel!
Did you have to tell me that now?
-You jerk. Why did you do that?
-You told me to do it.
-How can you do it now?
-It was your advice.
-Hye-jun.
Same day, same moon
It's 24-7, every moment repeats
My life is in between
Jobless twenty-somethings are
Afraid of tomorrow
Follow your dream like breaker
Stop pitying yourself.
Stop it. I've had enough of this.
You guys ruined my precious moment.
I don’t get a lot of chances to be happy,
worry-free.
He told me that telling you
when you’re in a good mood was the best.
Did you really have to tell on me?
I like the stories of BTS songs.
When I listen to their songs,
it makes me want to live a good life.
Hey, guys. You guys can live those lives.
Of course, that probably won't happen.
Why don't you finish him?
-Just crush him. Do it.
-It hurts.
-You're crushing him.
-Hey.
-You jerk.
-I crush him, and he crushes me.
Do you want to do it, too?
All right. When you contour
your face like this,
your facial features stand out.
And as for this T zone,
use a highlighter.
I bet you have a boyfriend.
I don’t date since dating requires
a lot of emotions and affects my life.
But I’m a fangirl.
Who is it? Let me join you.
I’ve been on a break from that.
It’s a secret.
But I met him this afternoon.
No way.
Do you need me to comfort you?
That was enough.
I know for a fact you'll make it.
I’m not saying this
because I'm your friend.
You know how objective I am, right?
-Let’s go home silently.
-Sure.
When you have a lot on your mind,
silence is the best companion.
Perfect timing.
If this is a girl, I’ll marry her.
Let's eat ramyeon.
-Are you getting married?
-You're crazy.
I’ve got to go.
Don’t think about anything.
Just for today. Bye.
You ought to think about your life.
What did I tell you five years ago?
I said you wouldn’t make it on your own.
If I can’t do it on my own, I should quit.
Why aren’t you ambitious?
Do you want to just die a nameless model?
Screw you.
He’s here.
You drank a lot.
Did you go to an after-party?
I didn’t go there.
I drank with Jin-u and Hye-jun. I’m tired.
It’s a good day.
Why the long face?
Mom. Do you know anyone
at the movie studio?
How would I know people from there?
Why are you asking?
They may have a different role
for Hye-jun.
Is this about Hye-jun again?
Is he your brother?
Why are you so eager to help him?
I won’t help even if I can.
Fine. Forget I said anything.
-Is Dad home?
-He's sleeping.
I was so happy and waited for you,
so we could celebrate with a drink.
But this is disappointing.
It sounds like
you still want to have a drink with me.
But I’m going to bed.
Hey!
You don’t seem bothered at all.
Whenever I think about his school,
I'm still furious.
What are you still furious about?
You startled me.
I thought you were sleeping.
I must have had too much caffeine
for the day.
I told you I wanted to send Hae-hyo
to a private elementary school,
but you sent him to a public school.
Look at his friend. He’s best friends
with the housekeeper's son.
Men ought to experience people
from various economic classes.
Sticking to just one class will
narrow down his perspective.
Stop with your Confucian ideas.
Birds of a feather flock together.
Hye-jun is going to be a roadblock
to Hae-hyo one day.
He should be dancing and celebrating
because he got the role,
but he can’t enjoy it because of Hye-jun.
Why must he go through that?
That’s just his hobby. He’ll quit later.
Why are you getting so worked up?
Who says this is his hobby?
Taking over the school will be his hobby.
Being a celebrity will be his main job.
By the way, you’re slacking off lately.
You've been dropping honorifics.
How many times did I tell you couples
must be polite to each other?
That's so vulgar.
People tell me that they are envious of me
because I have everything.
But they have no idea
how painful it is to live with a husband
whom you can’t communicate with.
Goodness.
Hey, I want to do Arena's
photoshoot with Hye-jun.
They want you.
They won't like it if Hye-jun joins.
Then, tell them I won’t do it.
This photoshoot is for rookie actors
who used to be models.
I’ll cover all the additional costs.
All right. I’ll talk to them.
By the way,
you got more followers on Instagram.
Let’s hit one million!
FOLLOWERS, 557K
I got 3,000 more followers in a day.
HOW TO DO FINE DUST-FREE MAKEUP
Today was a perfect day.
I should record a day like this.
All right.
Today was a perfect day.
Mr. Won Hae-hyo, this way.
Okay.
-It was exciting.
-So you always do this.
You always try to steal clients.
It was unfair.
We're the same age.
Should we speak casually, then?
Sure.
-It was surprising.
-What happened earlier wasn’t fair.
You didn't steal her client,
but she misread the situation.
I know how that feels.
It was touching.
People do say I'm straightforward.
And it got real.
#A PERFECT DAY #EXCITING
#UNFAIR #SURPRISING #TOUCHING
You have so many problems.
You said you were sick.
Why are you doing that now?
He got a job.
I can’t afford to buy him a new house,
but I should install a new door.
It’s nice and sturdy. You know?
Gyeong-jun’s life should be
just like this door.
When I get paid this month,
I’ll buy you a present.
What about me?
Of course, you get one, too.
-Really?
-Let's go to sleep. Stop.
Thank you.
My goodness. Gyeong-jun is the best.
No, I'm not.
How pathetic.
Do you think
you should be drinking right now?
Just let it go today.
How will you survive in this world
if you’re that weak?
I don’t need your input.
My life is miserable enough. Stop it.
When I was your age,
I worked at construction sites
to feed my family.
You just need to take care of yourself.
How can you say you have it bad?
If I tell you,
will you understand me?
When have I not been understanding?
I didn’t get the role.
Good! Now, you can go to the military.
You end up in the military anyway.
Look at me. I went to the military first.
Poor people like us
should get it done as fast as possible.
Stop bragging about yourself now.
He wouldn’t have said that
if your brother wasn’t worried about you.
The military duty is like homework.
We all have to go at one point.
But until I finish that homework,
it will be on my mind.
Who do you think it'd bother more?
It’s my life. Wouldn’t it bother me
more than you guys?
I didn’t tell you to become a model.
When you were trying to become a model,
he got into Seoul National University
without having a private tutor.
Your brother did it
even without any help from us.
Studying is the easiest thing
in the world.
I started working way before he did
-and became a top model.
-But no one on the street
will recognize this top model.
What?
That’s the end of your luck.
Just come back to your place
and face reality.
You’ve been working for seven years,
but how much money did you save up?
You and I have to make a living
for ourselves.
I won’t sacrifice myself
because I'm the eldest
-of this poor family.
-I don’t care if we’re poor.
But must you criticize me like this?
People chew me out.
I get chewed out even more at home.
You said you’re my family.
You want the best for me.
-Family can’t solve everything.
-Then,
don’t tell me what to do with my life.
I have never asked for money from you
after I graduated high school.
Why are you looking down on me
with your assumptions for my future?
Are you playing the victim right now?
If you think I’m playing the victim here,
you’re a psychopath.
When I said I didn’t get the role,
wouldn’t normal people try to comfort me
and see my pain?
"Good. Go to the military now."
-No human would say that!
-How dare you?
Are you saying that I'm no human?
You ungrateful child.
How dare you say that to your parents?
Hey. If he’s an ungrateful child,
you’re just the same
given how you treat me.
Why are you making this worse, Father?
Why do you always pick on Hye-jun?
He didn’t get the role,
so he can’t do what he loves to do.
How could you say those things?
You should comfort him first.
-Unbelievable.
-Grandpa, if you butt in like this,
Dad can’t discipline him properly.
Hey, Hye-jun is 26 now.
Back in my day,
he’d be old enough to marry.
He’s living his own life.
You don’t need to teach him.
Grandpa, let’s go inside.
Yes, let’s go to our room.
They deserve each other.
Look at this shabby door.
You installed a new door
for his bright future.
But do you want us to live a shabby life
with this shabby door?
If you were fixing his door,
you should have fixed both doors
or shouldn’t have done it at all.
You always play favorites.
What's wrong with this door?
That wasn't me.
I only caused trouble.
I'm sorry for inconveniencing you.
Thank you for taking my side.
Your dad is going to kill me tomorrow.
I’m the cause. So I’ll handle it.
People don’t change.
I always caused trouble,
and your grandma always took care of it.
I like you because you’re honest.
What did you do today?
-Did you go dancing?
-No.
I’m sick of it now. I want to make money.
You couldn’t do that when you were young.
How can you do that now?
If you mean that,
you’re just like your dad.
Sorry.
I just meant you should have fun
with the money I give you.
How could I do that?
You worked hard to earn it.
Can you get a job for me?
You know a lot of people
and go to a lot of places.
Okay. I’ll look into that.
I want to give some money to your dad.
He came home early today
because of his shoulder.
He won’t go to the hospital
to save money.
Gosh, it’s so upsetting.
Don’t cry.
Okay.
Why are you crying?
SA YEONG-NAM
I have never had a room for myself.
At this moment,
I needed a room to cry out by myself
without worrying about my family.
Having my own room and my house…
I dreamed of having my own house
by doing something I liked.
I will reject the reality
that won’t give me what I want.
-Where are you going?
-On a trip. I’ll travel around Namhae.
Before I go, I have great news for you,
so I came here in person.
-Make it quick. I have to go somewhere.
-I can't.
Hey, Daniel. It's me.
How are you?
Yeah. Hye-jun can work for you
Quit? No. He did okay.
He just switched agencies.
Which agency?
My own.
So from now on,
you just need to contact me.
I started my own company.
The name?
My company name is…
JJamppong.
Yes, it's called JJamppong.
"JJamppong"?
Jjajangmyeon is better than jjamppong.
-Jjamppong is better than jjajangmyeon.
-I feel bad, though.
I can’t go.
-Why not?
-I can’t afford a plane ticket.
I would need a place to stay, too.
I can’t do it alone. It’s in three days.
I would have to get on the plane today.
It’s impossible.
-Hey.
-Thanks, Min-jae
for going out of your way for me.
Hey, it was so hard to book this.
I can’t cancel this.
So why did you lie?
Eyes on the road.
Be careful. Gosh.
I need to serve in the military
at the beck and call of our country.
Military? When are you going?
Next month. That will be
my turning point. I’m quitting.
Drop me off over there.
Okay.
Have fun. When you come back,
I’ll buy you something delicious.
Hye-jun. Hye-jun, wait.
Damn it.
-I didn't expect to see you soon.
-I cannot accept your offer.
You don't like to beat around the bush.
You got to the point.
I respected and admired you.
Thank you for the offer.
Okay, if that's what you want,
I understand.
-Let's have lunch together.
-I have plans.
You're very busy.
I guess you easily spare your time
for other people.
Or did you make up plans
that you didn't even have?
I lied.
-I don't think I can have lunch with you.
-Why is it so complicated?
Do you think you're that important?
Am I a joke to you?
Is it because I'm being nice to you
after you rejected me?
You’re so dense.
You can’t succeed
with that brain of yours.
That’s why you’re still at the bottom.
If criticizing me makes you feel better,
go ahead.
This crossed my mind when I looked at you.
There’s a reason you’re not successful.
Look at Hae-hyo now.
You two started out together.
Since he has support,
things are working out for him.
You’ll probably die
at some construction site
just like your father.
Remember today.
I was polite to you to the end.
What…
Gosh, it hurts. It hurts.
Why aren't you on your trip?
I did something crazy, Hye-jun.
Min-jae, people can make mistakes
when they are cornered.
If you apologize,
I’m sure they'll understand.
I used to book all the tickets
at the agency.
This is a piece of cake.
I even booked a place for you to stay.
-Am I going to France, too?
-A direct flight to Milan costs twice.
-We'll land in Milan via France.
-Min-jae.
If you have plans, cancel.
It leaves at six.
Go home and get your passport.
I can’t tell them
JJamppong was made up!
But…
What kind of brushes do we need?
We need shading, blush
and foundation brushes.
It’s like you had the answer ready.
I always know
what we have in the inventory.
You know, Jeong-ha?
I could never like you.
If you don’t like me, then don’t like me.
I wasn’t going to say this
because it’s childish.
Then, it’s better that you don’t say it.
Hey!
Control your feelings. Think about
how you’ll affect your juniors.
I’m a good judge of character, indeed.
Now, you’re showing me your true colors.
Why? Did something happen
when you had a meal with Hae-hyo?
How could you not invite me?
I was there, too.
I didn’t go. I had other things to do.
How could I not invite you?
I shouldn’t hear that from you after you
humiliated me in front of other people.
Everyone has a bitchy side.
You’re not the only one with that.
That hit the spot!
I won’t hide now.
You might get caught in the crossfire.
I just focus on you,
so it’s comfortable for me.
How was meeting Sa Hye-jun?
I told him to come to our salon.
I hope he does.
And he can bring Won Hae-hyo.
If Hae-hyo comes,
Jin-ju will bully me even more.
I hope he doesn’t come.
“Hae-hyo”?
You only met him once.
Are you trying to brag?
You must get to know someone
over a long time.
You're pretending to be his friend!
I'm not pretending. We became friends.
No way.
It’s all thanks to Hye-jun.
You look like
it’s your first time on a plane.
It is my first time.
You have a knack for surprising people.
I never had a chance to live for myself.
I think this fashion show is for you,
not me.
-Orange juice, please.
-Okay.
-Water, please.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
It's good.
If we were in Korea, we could’ve drunk
at the convenience store.
We’ve been here only for two days,
but it feels like it’s been a month.
It must be boring for you
if you feel it’s been that long.
It’s like I'm dreaming.
I don’t have to worry
about making ends meet
and want you to do well on the stage.
And when you did well,
it made me happy, too.
What is this feeling? It’s flustering.
You feel that way when you’re in love.
I must be in love.
-Not with you. With this process.
-Okay.
Helping people succeed
and stuff like that.
So I told you to be my agent.
Do you really want to quit?
I don’t want to, but it's only logical.
Why did you decide that?
I didn’t get the role in the movie.
I really wanted to work
with that director.
It was my last chance.
-Then, who got the role?
-Hae-hyo.
Hey. No. That’s not right.
I know both you and Hae-hyo.
Of course, he’s great,
but you’re special.
You can move people’s hearts.
You even moved mine.
It’s all over, anyway. Cheers!
I love it.
Why did you sleep on the plane?
-Was it delicious?
-Totally.
-You slept, so you didn't get to eat.
-What did they serve?
Bibimbap.
-Hello, Min-jae.
-It’s been a while.
Congratulations on getting the role.
Thank you. I’ll take Hye-jun now.
Do you want us to drop you off somewhere?
No. There’s a direct bus from here.
Are you heading to the hair salon?
Yes. He’s been pestering me
to change the salon.
You won’t regret it.
All right, guys. I'm off now. Bye.
Thank you.
-See you.
-Bye.
-Let's go.
Before you go, I’ll write down
the brand and color of the foundation.
Okay.
-Hello.
-Hello, welcome.
I heard a lot about you from your mother.
You should have come sooner.
I strongly recommended coming here.
Thank you.
I'm friends with Jeong-ha.
I didn't know
you were a friend of Jeong-ha.
And his friend is my friend as well.
My gosh, this is nice.
You said you’d give us a discount.
You guys look so close.
Did you meet before the fashion show?
No. She’s really friendly.
And she’s your fan.
What? Really?
Why didn’t you tell me that before?
Are you my fan?
-No.
-It's okay. You can tell him.
-You're so shy.
-And you have a big mouth.
That was a bit harsh.
Are we close enough
to exchange such remarks?
Sorry.
Hey, she seems flustered.
Don't make a joke sound so serious.
My acting has been improving lately.
Did I get you?
-What's wrong with you?
-I'm sorry.
What's so funny? Let me join you guys.
Let's go. I know a lot of jokes.
-Ask Jeong-ha to take care of you.
-I want my hair washed.
Come this way.
Sit here. Someone will be here.
Don't feel uncomfortable around me.
You don’t need to be careful around me
because you're my fan.
I’m really not your fan.
Why do you keep saying that?
It’s embarrassing me.
This is so frustrating.
Why can’t you say
that you’re my fan when you are?
I’m Hye-jun’s fan.
-What?
-I couldn’t tell him the truth
because I was embarrassed.
You saw it, too.
-You weren't embarrassed in front of me?
-No.
-You're funny.
-Don’t tell Hye-jun.
Why must I do that?
You’re Won Hae-hyo.
“Won Hae-hyo is warmhearted and kind.
Models who know him said…"
Okay, stop it. Did you look into me, too?
"…he does a lot of favors
as he’s softhearted.”
Okay. Fine.
Wait here.
-Where are you going?
-To the restroom.
I see. It's that way.
Are you happy to see Hae-hyo?
Please don’t butt in my business.
Can you do other stuff than makeup?
Yes. I can kind of do everything
that requires hands.
Can you cut hair?
I can use hair clippers
for soldiers
and kids under seven years old.
The photoshoot is in two days.
You should come then.
-It’s a photoshoot for Arena, right?
-Yes.
You should beat Jin-ju.
You should beat her at least once.
If you lose even with my help,
you’re a fool.
He must think
I've been losing all the time.
I'll win this time.
Good. Try to look livelier.
I couldn't explain it.
But deep down in my heart,
I felt something rising up.
I figured out what it was.
You and I shine in our own way.
Do you know why you didn’t get the role?
The director liked you at first,
but Hae-hyo has more followers than you.
So they went with him.
You lost because of popularity,
not because of your acting.
I fooled myself that not comparing myself
and competing against him was virtuous.
Now, I have no regrets.
Are you done?
What? So you don’t even call
before you come now?
I need to do something.
Right here?
Can you cut my hair with the hair clipper?
Do you want to go back
when you were seven years old?
I’m joining the military.
Subtitle translation by Won-hyang Son
RECORD OF YOUTH
-Have you ever been on a date?
-Of course I have.
Do you think I enjoy going off at Hye-jun?
Hey. Aren't you even going to greet me?
You saw me too.
What am I going to do
when you join the military?
-I'm going to miss you.
-Just wait 18 months.
You must be upset because of Hye-jun.
If he joins the military,
his career will be over.
It was just a phase.
Don't give up until
you exhaust all the possibilities.
Success is doing what you like and eating
delicious food. There's nothing to it.
I just want to be a humble star.
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs