RECORD OF YOUTH
THIS PROGRAM HAS BEEN SELECTED AS AN
"EXCELLENT BROADCAST CONTENT" AND IS SUPPORTED
BY THE MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS, TOURISM
AND THE KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
I…
I would like to ask the rescue squad
on standby
to immediately start searching
the point of the fall you just saw.
I’m sure there are survivors.
You can save all of them.
Please hurry and find them.
Mr. Park No-gyu.
You wanted an apology from the President,
but you hung up. Is this it now?
Is it?
You were going to kill anyway, right?
I like it.
His version is different
from Ha Jung-woo’s.
As I told you before,
I think Hae-hyo’s version is better.
What’s this guy’s name?
Let’s be real. We don't even know
his name. Why cast him, then?
What’s his name?
ACTOR PARK DO-HA'S GREEN ROOM
-He’s inside, right?
-No one is allowed inside.
I’m not just anyone.
I’m the makeup artist, Lee Bo-ra.
What?
You just touched me.
This is sexual harassment.
Move.
Care to go over the facts?
Don’t let anyone inside,
especially Lee Bo-ra.
She’s like a leech.
I'm really sick of her.
By the way, you look familiar.
Where have I seen you?
I got it. Just move out of my way.
You still want to go in?
I’ll be the one
who ends this relationship.
-Can't I go in?
-No.
I must follow my orders.
But there’s an exception
if I'm physically unable to stop you.
We dated for five years.
It was hard to process our breakup,
so I know I’ve been clingy.
But did you really have to treat me
like some trash?
So what do you want from me?
Let's break up.
I’m ending this relationship, not you.
Whenever I see you, I want to punch you.
Even if you do deserve to be punched,
I shouldn’t be violent
because I’m a good person.
You’re completely full of yourself.
Hey!
Hey.
Hey. What do you think you're doing?
Didn’t I tell you to not let her inside?
I tried my best to stop her.
Your best?
-Blood?
-You looked familiar,
so I looked you up earlier.
You’re a model.
It looked like you had a decent career.
But what happened to your life?
What happened?
What? What’s wrong with my life?
What? I can't talk casually?
I looked you up, too.
It turns out we’re the same age.
So let’s forget about honorifics.
You started it first.
You’ve got to be out of your mind!
My dream is to have what this jerk has.
Even a jerk like him can make it here.
But I don’t have
much time left.
FOLLOW
RECORD OF YOUTH
Yes. That's it.
Look into the camera. Gaze into it.
Okay. That's it.
Great job. Nice.
Good.
-There you go.
-Yes.
Here we go. It's the last one!
Okay! We're done.
You need to exercise.
Stop calling me in the middle
of the night for a run.
We have our reasons.
Your cholesterol level is high.
Please take care of yourself.
I’ll take care of my health.
So you just take care of yours.
Or why don't we just take care
of ourselves?
Wake up, man.
But there’s one thing
I have the upper hand over you guys.
It’s not just one. You have about three.
You sure have a way with words, don’t you?
You didn’t even serve in the military.
That was Jin-u's daily mention
of his military service.
That must be Hye-jun. He posted a photo.
I bet 500 won he didn’t.
Hey, you got a lot of followers now.
You have more followers
than Yoo Seung-ho and Choi Jin-hyuk.
I don't know why. I didn't do anything.
Excessive modesty can be annoying!
I’m not being modest. It’s a fact.
Do I owe you 500 won?
But what happened to his face?
Did he get beaten up at work?
THE MOST DEMANDING JOB
Why would he get beaten up?
#PART-TIME JOB #SOMEDAY
A silver spooner like you wouldn’t know
the sorrow of a dirt spooner.
That’s too brutal, man.
Aren’t they supposed
to announce their decision for the role?
What if he doesn’t get the role?
Must you ask? He’s got me.
I’ll take care of him.
Can you take care of me, too?
-Sir.
-You said you wanted to be on your own.
-Come on.
-Mr. Kim, go away.
Mr. Won.
-I bet 500 won it's your mother.
-Do you think I only get calls from her?
-Who is it?
-What are you doing?
Are you here to play?
Do you think
you and Hae-hyo have the same jobs?
You owe me 1,000 won in total.
It's not her.
Hey, Mom.
You have a photoshoot.
Why aren't you here?
Where are you?
You were supposed to get your hair done
at the hair salon I go.
I said no to that.
I don’t like your hairstyle.
It looks lame.
Forget it. Stop trying to sound hip.
Let’s talk at home. Bye.
Gosh.
What’s taking Jin-ju so long?
She’s talking to the salon director.
Can I serve you beverages?
She's taking too long.
Can you just do my makeup?
I don’t want to wait.
I'm not ready to do that yet.
She’ll be here soon.
Just do it when I tell you to.
You did my makeup before.
I just did the base makeup
before Jin-ju did--
You’re so chatty.
Should I just leave, then?
Then…
What are you doing?
I'm sanitizing my hands.
I like that.
Some makeup artists touch your face
without washing their hands first.
I knew you were different
when you did my makeup the other day.
You're not like the others.
Thank you.
What kind of meeting is this?
Is it a formal occasion?
It’s a casual meeting.
Then I’ll make you look
effortlessly beautiful.
You have beautiful eyes.
Keep telling me that I'm pretty.
It puts me in a good mood.
In five minutes. If I say it again now,
it won’t sound sincere.
Gosh, you’re so witty!
I’m sorry the talk ran long.
I’ll take over once she’s done.
I want her to do my makeup today.
"An Jeong-ha"?
Pardon?
I’ll assist
after I finish the base makeup.
I said I didn't want that.
You’re slacking off lately.
I hate waiting.
I’m sorry, Professor Kim.
Go on.
Okay.
Take care.
-Have a good weekend.
-Bye.
Are you happy?
Pardon?
You think you’re better
because you worked at a big company?
Ma'am.
Do you have any respect for me?
You must think you can do whatever
you want because the director likes you.
I’ve been working in this industry
for ten years.
I've never seen a bitch who steals clients
becomes a good makeup artist.
If you ever try to steal my clients--
I’m sorry to interrupt you,
but I told her I couldn’t.
She was persistent.
-So I had no choice--
-“No choice”?
That’s what they all say.
They all didn't have a choice.
Drop that crappy excuse.
If it happens again,
I’ll make you realize that you had it easy
with your office job.
She scolded you again, right?
That’s her inferiority complex.
I’m telling you. That's why she does that.
Why would she feel inferior to me?
Because you’re good.
Thanks, Su-bin.
It’s been over a million years
since someone complimented me.
Really? Then, do you like me
more than Sa Hye-jun?
Not that much.
-Okay. You sounded firm.
-Yes.
-You’re such a diligent fangirl.
-I am.
Jin-ju is going
to the Homme fashion show tomorrow.
Tell her you’ll go with her.
I’m sure he’ll be there, too.
I don’t want to force it.
We’ll meet when it’s time.
And I’ll do my best until that day comes.
He might be gone from this industry.
He’s a popular model,
but he’s not doing well as an actor.
Hey.
That’s the truth.
I heard he was born with a silver spoon.
He lives in Hannam-dong.
I bet he doesn’t need to
make money from his job.
Hey, you’re so mean.
I take back my thank-you.
Hye-jun does live in Hannam-dong,
but he wasn’t born with a silver spoon.
He works really hard. And he’s kind, too.
Jeong-ha, the most pathetic thing
a fangirl can do is complimenting
a celebrity’s personality.
How do you know he’s kind in real life?
We have a customer.
Get back to work.
Why are you so grumpy?
Some people might think
you’re his girlfriend.
Please come down quickly.
Now that she brought him up,
let me take a quick look at his face.
Hye-jun.
Fangirling over you
is what keeps me going.
How are you hanging in there?
MY BIAS
HEADING OFF TO A WARM PLACE #KOTA KINABALU
My friend's dream protects him.
But my dream is
like homework that costs a lot of money.
TRANSACTIONS
ACCOUNT BALANCE
SA MIN-GI, BOOKSTORE, SUBWAY, BUS
BALANCE
85,500 WON
Are you out of your mind?
You are the one who’s out of your mind.
You still didn’t pay me for
the last fashion show and previous gigs.
I stopped Park Do-ha from suing you.
I did nothing wrong. This will
get me two weeks in the hospital.
And I made sure I didn't fight back
even for self-defense.
Besides, deflecting the conversation
doesn’t work anymore.
Hye-jun.
As you know, the agency isn’t doing well.
Imagine how bad it must be.
I can't even pay you.
Stop trying to make me feel bad.
This isn’t your first time.
How can you always pay me late?
Why do I have to beg you to pay me?
When other models left,
saying you were an asshole,
I told them that you would have paid them
if you had the money.
I trusted you and decided to stay.
So why did you trust me?
This is why you’ll never make it here.
You’re too naive.
That’s why I’m managing your finances.
Gosh, this money talk…
Did I scare you?
Come on, it’s us. It's just money.
Can money get between us?
I can’t believe this.
You should pay Hye-jun for his work.
You said you were quitting.
If you’re done packing, leave.
You’re pathetic.
How can you prey on these models?
Until when do you think
you can keep this up?
You’re pouring it out
now that you’re quitting.
You think we won’t cross paths?
Ms. Lee Min-jae.
This is a small world.
You think we won’t cross paths,
but we will.
We all work in the same industry.
Just leave quietly.
I'm leaving this industry,
and I won’t ever see you again.
I’ll do a good deed while I'm at it.
I’ve been itching to do a good deed
while working here.
You’re full of crap.
I see. You like crap.
Which crap should I start with?
Should I talk to the press first?
Or your wife?
No. Should I head
to the Labor Office first?
Are you threatening me?
If you think I’m threatening you,
it means you have a lot of crap.
This is why I respect you.
You sure know your place, so you’ll
continue to be on this successful path.
So you’d better pay Hye-jun.
Don’t be a cheapskate
who steals from kids. Okay?
No, not okay.
Let’s see which one will get you
to change your mind.
It’s probably your wife.
You’ll see her tonight.
-What is this?
-I had to clean up
whenever you broke up with them.
Don’t you remember?
So what will you do with them?
With these photos?
NEW MESSAGE TO MR. LEE'S WIFE
If you don’t pay him,
I’m moving onto plan B.
-What are you doing?
-I opened the door.
Exactly. Why are you doing that?
Be my agent, Min-jae.
-What?
-I need someone like you.
Let’s talk after you get the money first.
It’s so easy to win you over.
This is why you get conned.
The con artists are the problem,
not the victims.
That kind of perspective
gives an excuse to the con artists.
And that's called victim blaming.
Aren’t you a smooth talker?
I said I'm leaving this industry.
I’m not stopping you.
But I work in a different industry.
Min-jae.
Min-jae, I'm not done talking to you yet.
Please?
That was cool.
You made my heart race for a second.
What? Min-jae.
Who are you going to trust
other than your husband?
Hold on. I’ve got to go. I have a client.
I have to make money
to feed our family.
Okay.
Why are you back?
Look at this. Are you happy now?
We should finish our conversation.
What conversation?
Our contract can be terminated
if either party requests it.
-I'm sure you remember that.
-You must think
you’re some big shot model.
Let’s write a cancelation of the contract.
Suit yourself.
How could you bite the hand
that feeds you?
Don't you know that I did everything
in my power to help you?
If you say you did this to help me
one more time, I’ll punch you.
Okay. Fine.
Let’s split up, then.
-But I can’t pay you.
-You can just have it.
It’s a small price I’m paying
to get away from an asshole like you.
You’ve been a model for seven years.
You became a top model
which was the peak for you.
And who made that happen? It’s me.
How do you think you can make it
as an actor without me?
It won’t work out for you.
What is it?
What?
Do you want to punch me?
I’m saying this for your sake.
I won’t punch you.
You’re not worth it.
Do you think you and Hae-hyo
are in the same boat?
Do you think
you can be like Hae-hyo?
Hye-jun.
Isn’t that what you’re insecure about?
Let's do push-ups first.
Go up.
And come down.
Inhale and come down.
Exhale and tuck your tailbone.
Open up your chest a bit as you inhale.
Exhale. Keep breathing.
What are you doing?
I’m showing you that I’m not like you.
Hae-hyo is my friend.
I've never wanted to be like him.
As if.
LEE TAE-SU
SA HYE-JUN
What a load off my chest this is.
Seriously, having you--
I could have put you in jail.
Stop talking.
Even if you take this to court,
you won’t get the money.
I’d rather pay the fine
instead of paying you.
Do you know why I don’t want the money?
Because I know you won’t pay me.
To get that money,
I have to get my hands dirtier than yours.
And I don’t have time for that crap.
You'll never make it here.
You’ll be Hae-hyo’s sidekick
for the rest of your life.
Have a good day, my grandchild.
What are you up to?
I'm having fun.
He texted me back right away.
I can call him then.
GRANDPA
Hey, Grandpa.
What are you doing?
I’m having fun, too.
Nice.
Do you want some money?
That’d be great.
Did you make a lot of money?
No.
Then, you shouldn’t.
I can make money later.
That’s not it.
I’m telling you. You’ll make it.
I’m sure of it.
I’ve never seen a kid as talented as you.
That’s why Dad always scolds you.
Your dad is scary.
Come home early. I’m nothing without you.
Mr. Sa Min-gi,
when did you become such a coward?
Grandpa, you outrank Dad.
It's quite the contrary.
Hye-jun, we ought to face reality,
you know?
Nonetheless, you’re the best!
Grandpa, you're indeed
a good judge of character.
I know your acting career
hasn't been going well,
but a gem is bound to shine.
And you're a gem.
I should give you
more allowance next month.
Thank you.
Now that I talked to you,
I'll go have some fun!
What? Yes. Okay.
Did you switch shifts?
Nice to see you. It's been a while.
Same here. You should take orders.
Why?
Look over there.
What are you going to do?
I'm taking orders today.
I'll go first.
-Me!
What would you like?
Can you recommend me one?
How about Italian BMT?
I like it.
Okay.
Everything looks the same.
I don’t see anything better
than the last season.
The dahlia is too long. Cut it a bit.
It stands out more
and is prettier because it’s long.
Okay.
Oh, right.
I forgot to put it in the hamper.
-I need you to hand-wash something.
-Wait.
Can’t you see that I changed to leave?
How would I know if you changed or not?
I see. So your time is up, right?
It won’t take long to wash it.
I have to go home early today.
Can’t you just do it?
I’ll do it next time I come.
Today was my oldest’s first day at work.
We’re celebrating today.
We even invited our neighbors,
so I have to go grocery shopping.
You have to throw a block party
when you get a job these days?
If it’s that hard to get a job,
how did he get a job?
He has a lot of qualifications.
College diplomas from prestigious schools?
I’m not jealous at all.
Even if he works at a conglomerate,
he'll work like a dog.
Which company? If you had told me,
I could've recommended him for our school.
He’d be better off unemployed
than working at that school.
He got a few offers, so he just chose one.
So which company is it?
If you want to brag, go ahead.
Don’t stall time.
You would've been done with the laundry
had you just told me.
So we’re back to that.
Goodness, I should hurry.
Oh, my. Look at her deflecting.
How could she say no like that
when she's been working for me
all this time?
People say we all have to do things
that we don’t want to.
But that’s all a lie.
It’s not like this is the first time
I realized the world isn’t fair.
This life is already a bust.
Complaining won’t do me any good.
GROUP CHAT: HUSBAND
Don’t forget we’re having dinner today.
I didn’t forget. He’s checking it again.
I’ll be late.
Why is he coming late?
His dad is going to give him an earful.
I can’t mediate
when he won’t cooperate with me.
Be on time no matter what.
“No matter what”?
It’s okay to be a bit late.
It's no big deal.
Well, he said he had work.
Is he done with work?
BE ON…
Tell me if there’s anything you want
to eat. I’ll tell Ae-suk to cook it.
I’m sure she’ll prepare a great meal.
I envy you.
Now that Gyeong-jun got a job,
you only have Hye-jun to worry about.
He’s the problem.
He has his head in the clouds.
But when he was on TV and in magazines,
you’d still smile while complaining.
Did you think I was happy about it?
I just thought he was able
to make a living out of his looks.
If it didn’t work out at all,
he wouldn’t have false hope.
If it didn't work out for seven years,
he must quit. He can't seem to give up.
I hope he tags along and learns the trade.
If Jin-u was as handsome as Hye-jun,
I would've helped him with all I've got.
Why would you want him to do what we do?
If he knows a few skills,
he won’t at least starve.
Hey. Come on.
I told you I would lift everything.
I just feel bad.
You’re good at planning.
Do you want your son
to follow in your footsteps
when you injured your arm from this job?
I injured my arm because I was overworking
myself to pay back my father’s debt.
He has to fulfill his military duty, too.
Whenever I think about him,
I can’t get any sleep.
I can’t support him much longer.
What? Ae-suk is working, too.
And I can’t let her keep working there.
She brags about making money.
Rightfully so.
You should treat her like a queen.
You punk.
I’m leaving!
Wait.
Let me pay you for overtime.
It’s okay.
Why? I put in enough money.
It’s 50,000 won.
My daily fee is 100,000 won.
I only hand-washed a shirt.
I stopped you from going home.
I want to pay you for your time.
That's all.
I said it’s fine.
Hello, ma’am!
Hi, Hae-hyo. It’s been a while.
You’ve gotten more handsome.
You look more beautiful, too.
I never saw you because I come home late.
Hye-jun is always late these days.
He won’t tell me what he’s up to, either.
-But he talks to you all about it, right?
-Of course.
I tell Hye-jun everything including things
I keep from my mom.
What is it that you're keeping from me?
I didn’t know you were here, Mom.
I’m late. I’ll get going now.
-Bye, ma’am.
-Bye.
“Ma’am”?
How could you address her like that?
Why would you do that?
She’s Hye-jun's mom.
How should I call her?
“Ae-suk”.
Mom, instead of pretending
to be young superficially,
think like one with an open mind.
Stop looking down on her
with your absurd idea of hierarchy.
I never did such a thing.
And what aren’t you telling me?
Why do you tell Hye-jun but not me?
Don't tell me you're seeing someone.
At this rate, you’ll be writing
a movie on it.
The Stalker.
Hey, what about dinner?
You have a fashion show tomorrow.
I’ll get you a salad.
You’re so creepy!
Stop stalking me!
Don't get fresh with me.
Do you think you got here all on your own?
What do you mean?
Why are you looking at me like that?
I want to show people
that I got here all on my own.
I want you to respect that.
I completely respect that.
So don’t worry.
-Ma'am.
-It's Kim I-yeong.
I really hate it
when you address me like that.
But I can't call you by your name.
This is for your wife.
Thank you.
I’m pushing for Hae-hyo,
but the director won’t budge.
If you say that
as soon as I give you a present,
it looks like I'm bribing you.
But then, the world is
all about give and take.
By the time Hae-hyo becomes a star,
half the credit goes to you.
Only half?
I should work harder.
MILITARY DRAFT NOTICE
RECIPIENT
SA HYE-JUN
-Ae-suk.
-Yes.
You’re so early. I didn’t even start yet.
I came early, so I could help.
After a full day of doing house chores
at someone else's house,
you come home and have to cook a feast.
Children are such hassles.
You're right. Children are such hassles.
Has she been quiet lately?
She throws a fit once or twice a year.
But she’s been quiet these days.
She ought to.
She begged you
to come back after you quit.
That's why you went back there.
She just got used to me.
I’m sure she can find someone else
if she wanted.
Stop being so humble.
What is this?
Did Hye-jun get the draft notice?
There will be blood today.
Are you going home after this?
Yes. What's up?
What are you hiding at home?
You’re always eager to go home.
How about pork belly at my house?
I love you, Jeong-ha.
Goodness.
-Clean up.
-I love you.
-What are you girls laughing about?
-Jeong-ha.
-Yes?
Do you want to go
to the Homme fashion show tomorrow?
I know it’s your day off,
so it’s fine if you don’t want to.
No, that sounds great.
Jin-ju can do it by herself,
but it will be too much work for her.
Thank you.
Thank you. I’ll try my best!
I know you try your best.
-Just do a good job.
-Okay.
-I'm leaving now.
-Goodnight, ma’am!
Goodnight!
I guess you and Hye-jun
are destined to meet!
-Oh, my gosh!
-No way.
Your face is red.
-No!
-Goodness.
This is for Table Six.
And this is for Table Eight.
-Okay.
-Tables Six and Eight.
Okay.
Here you go.
Excuse me.
What do you need?
You're so handsome.
-Thank you.
-We come here to see you.
Do you want more vegetables?
-Yes, please.
-Yes.
You're so popular.
Why didn’t you go to my house?
So we can go together.
-Two servings of pork belly?
-And bibim naengmyeon.
We need to start leveling soon.
-What should I do?
-It's not ready yet?
Honey, come and take the plates!
Okay.
I’ll do it. You’re a guest. Stay here.
No, we’re not. Are we guests here?
We’re having this meal thanks to you.
Let him do it. He’s better at it.
He’s right, Dad. Let Gyeong-jun do it.
Now that you say it, I don’t want to.
You're always like that when people ask.
That’s how everyone is.
Same here. What about you, Yeong-nam?
I wouldn’t want to do something
if someone orders me to do it.
That’s how we all feel.
We’re all the same.
I told you to get the plate.
Why are you still here?
-You’re so chatty.
-I’m coming. I’m sorry.
Why would you do that?
You’re the man of the hour.
Honey, you do it.
Don’t do anything.
You’ll only cause trouble.
I agree.
“Why are you only making me do it?
The world has changed now.
Is it because I’m a woman?
That’s anachronistic thinking!”
I’d rather do it myself.
Is that true, Jin-ri?
Yes. I’m very interested in building
my own life and living independently.
You sound very smart.
Your father must be happy.
Try living with her, then.
Gyeong-jun, you're good at this.
Honey, you should do it.
Give me a bigger one.
Goodness.
-Take this, then.
-Okay.
Should I go out or not?
I should go out before they come for me.
They might think I'm a hassle.
Let me see.
WE ROOT FOR YOUR EVERY MOMENT
-Come here. Gyeong-jun, sit down.
-Okay.
Goodness.
The meal is ready now.
Okay. I was exercising.
I didn’t ask.
I respect your privacy.
Goodness.
So the entire neighborhood knows
that I’m walking on eggshells.
Until when will you waste your life?
What do you mean?
I thought about what I could do for you.
Why don’t you work here
as a manager instead of a part-timer?
You know that
I can’t work here permanently.
How long do you think you’ll stay young?
Learn the business and save up
some money. It's a nice deal.
If you do well, I'll let you take over
after your military service.
Thank you for the offer.
Come on. Are you turning it down
even before you've given it some thought?
I'm sorry.
Take advice from people
who are older than you.
I'm speaking from experience.
The elders always have a point.
I used to listen to them, too.
But I've learned it the hard way
that people only look out for themselves.
Hey, I thought about
giving you the restaurant.
How is that looking out for myself?
Hye-jun, I didn't peg you
to be so cynical.
I wasn't talking about you.
I was making a general statement.
-Right?
-Yes.
There's no way you'd see me that way.
So you should listen to the elders.
I want you to reconsider.
Why aren't you answering me?
Okay.
Okay. Good work today.
-Bye.
Good work today.
What took you so long to change?
Did the owner say something?
I have a lot on my mind.
What should we do on a day like this?
What should we do?
No.
No way! I’m not doing that!
-I'm not doing that! I won't!
-You don't have to.
I told you I won't do it!
Gosh.
Hey, stop him! Hurry!
Why are you here?
I live in this neighborhood.
Is it a problem?
Of course, not.
Won Hae-hyo, that traitor.
I called him to stop Hye-jun from running.
Wait up for me, you annoyingly tall jerks!
He always talks when he runs.
I guess he can't run without talking.
Gyeong-jun, does it mean you’ll help us
if we want to take out a loan?
I mostly handle companies,
so I don’t know much about that.
Even if you did,
you must not do favors for your friends.
I’m sure he can handle it himself.
Why would you say that?
You can never be too sure.
All right. Let’s raise our glasses again.
Yeong-nam, why don't you give a toast?
I don’t have anything to say.
Of course, you do.
Your son grew into a fine young man.
If my son had turned out
to be this successful,
I’d be bragging about him
even to my distant relatives.
Sir, you just dissed him.
What? “Diss”? What’s that?
To borrow our term, it means to criticize.
Jin-ri.
You should elaborate.
That way, he won’t misunderstand.
I didn't misunderstand.
He clearly dissed me.
-Honey.
-It's true.
I’m his son. Aren't I?
If I had been successful,
he would have bragged about me,
but he can’t because I’m a nobody.
Gosh. Respect.
You’re so dope, Mr. Sa. Awesome.
Jin-ri, what’s wrong with you?
Yeong-nam, she’s gotten weird
after starting college.
She only speaks the truth.
Goodness.
Fine. It's a good day.
Let's laugh about it.
Everyone, raise your glasses.
Let’s congratulate my oldest son
for getting a job.
Jin-ri, raise your glass.
I’ll pour you a drink
for making me laugh today.
-Here.
-Thank you.
I wish Jin-u and Hye-jun were here, too.
-Yes.
-Cheers.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
I bet people with bad karma
in previous lives become models.
You can’t even eat what you want.
Life isn't just about eating.
To some people, it is.
-Me?
-But we don’t tease them about it.
We don’t tease them. We respect them.
Look at your teamwork.
That's so cool.
-Hey, girl!
-She might scold you.
Why?
Yes.
Guys, get in!
I’m bored.
-No!
-I’m getting in.
I’m in! Move out of my way.
Does he even have any pride?
What’s the point? She’s your sister.
By the way, she grew up a lot.
She’s past that point.
She stopped growing.
Now, she’s getting old.
Bye, guys.
Look at him all happy.
Let him be.
She’ll leave him in front of my house.
Looking at Hae-na makes me
think time is fair.
I thought I was the only one getting old,
but she is, too.
How can time be the only fair thing
in this world?
What's going on?
The reality has been
hitting me hard.
Get off.
-Get off?
-Get off.
-Really?
-Really.
-Don’t regret it.
-I will
regret it.
Let’s go somewhere else.
No.
If you don’t want to, I don’t want to.
I like your attitude.
-I should give you a reward.
-What?
Wait.
Now, tell me.
What gave you a hard time today?
If I talk about it, it’ll upset me again.
Tell me when talking about it
doesn't upset you.
Did people from the movie audition
call back?
No. Did you get a call?
No. I was wondering if you had gotten it.
Do you think one of us will get it?
Yes.
I agree.
If you get it,
I’ll still congratulate you.
Of course.
I’ll do the same.
But if I don’t get it this time,
I’ll join the military.
I think I tried enough.
We were supposed to go together.
You know what people say.
They say when you get old,
your friends change
depending on how much money you have.
That's not true for us. We knew
things were different in the first place.
If we change,
it doesn’t mean it’s about the money.
It means we lost our innocence.
Why are you staring at me?
I love you, Hye-jun.
Stop it.
Stop it. Hey, quit it. Come on.
You're crazy.
I’m going to do it one of these days!
Bye.
I look completely fried.
What a line.
Wait. Should I stay quiet?
-It’s okay. I can edit it out later.
-Okay.
I’m sure there were times when you were
surprised to see yourselves after work.
But you have plans after work.
Don’t worry. You can fix your makeup.
I’ll teach you a simple method.
Don’t I look much better?
Remember my tip.
Apply glitters under the eyes.
Then, use eyeliner and a lip tint.
Ta-da.
I’m meeting Hye-jun tomorrow!
I’m hungry!
Hurry.
Can I eat now?
Dig in.
I totally approve of this mix!
The delicious juice of the meat
and the savory flavor of the cheese!
And kimchi neutralizes the greasiness!
After this, I’ll make you fried rice
with kkakdugi. It’s really good.
When I first met you, I thought
you were such a cheapskate.
You always wanted to eat at your house.
That’s how I bought this house.
Of course, the bank owns
most of the house for now.
How could you take out a 30-year loan
when you don't even know
what might happen tomorrow?
I don’t get you.
That’s because you never had to live
without a house.
Owning a house gives you
a sense of stability.
That’s why I even named
my YouTube channel, I Like Stability.
If you want stability, get married.
No, I won't.
Will you say no even if Sa Hye-jun asks?
Even he can’t change my belief.
Then, how are you his fan?
Only the thought of love makes you happy.
I don't want to be in love,
but I want to be happy.
Love and alcohol go hand in hand.
Do you have alcohol at home?
No. I don't drink
when I have work the next day.
You're doing everything you want.
Yes, I am.
When I quit the company,
I decided to live for myself.
You should live for yourself, too.
Our country is too family-oriented.
HAPPINESS DAY BY DAY
SA YEONG-NAM
Look at you humming.
You must have had a good time.
I was working.
Working?
What on earth are you up to?
What are you doing?
So you don’t want to answer me?
I’m making a new door
for Gyeong-jun’s room.
You're home.
Hye-jun.
I need to talk to you.
What is it?
Your dad can’t know.
Just tell me. I’m really tired today.
It won’t take long.
MILITARY DRAFT NOTICE
What are you going to do?
You have to go this time.
I should.
I’m glad to hear that.
But Mom,
I auditioned for a movie this time.
If I get that role,
I’ll think of it as my last chance
and postpone it one last time.
Just go.
You have to fulfill your duty anyway.
Why are you eavesdropping?
I can hear everything in this small house.
Don’t butt in my life. Just live your own.
I’m already living a good life. You know
that you’re the burden of our family.
Why would you say that?
You don’t say it,
but I bet you agree with me.
I only said it out loud.
What…
Is that true?
That’s not true.
My own family was judging me
behind my back?
Hey, everyone gets judged.
You think we're any different?
Do the same standards apply to everyone?
Everyone is different.
Gyeong-jun,
I think you have a nasty personality.
I agree that you got a job
because you are smart,
but what have you done for the family
after getting a job with your smart brain?
Yes, he contributed to the family.
Why are you butting in?
What's wrong with you?
It's nothing.
Go to your room.
It’s not nothing. Because you keep
babying him, you’re spoiling him.
I got it. That's enough.
-You’re home.
-Yes.
Did you eat?
I did. What about you?
I did. What happened to your face?
It's nothing.
I heard the draft notice came.
Why did you hide that?
Hide what? I just saw it, too.
Anyway, go to the military now.
How can I go now? It’s night.
You know I didn't mean literally now.
What will you do with your life?
Will you keep wasting your good days
for a dead end?
Let me ask you a question, too.
Do you also consider me
the burden of the family?
-Why are you asking me that?
-I want to judge my family, too.
I thought our family was special,
but if you have been judging me
behind my back, I should change my stance.
You are no different than strangers.
We're talking about the military
and your future. Don't change the subject.
I need to know if you are
truly concerned for me
or if you’re worried
that I'll be a burden.
I must know to answer accordingly.
That’s no way to talk to your own father.
I’m telling you this, so you could live
a good life, not a bad one.
You worked as a model long enough.
At first, you liked it,
but look where it got you now.
You earn just enough for your allowance.
You don’t need to look further.
Just look at your grandpa.
Take a good look at him.
When he was young,
people complimented on his good looks
and said he ought to be on TV.
People kept encouraging him.
That got him thinking
he could be a singer or an actor.
That’s how he got there.
Hye-jun is different.
Why do you keep comparing him to me?
How is he any different?
I think he’s just like you
when you were young.
If you didn't get scammed
with all of my savings,
-we wouldn’t be living like this.
-I know. I'm sorry.
That’s why I don’t even squeak.
I’m the burden of my family.
It’s not you, Hye-jun.
Why do you keep protecting him?
Whenever I see his face,
I feel so frustrated.
Whenever I see him trying
to become an actor like you,
my heart stops beating.
That’s enough. Stop it.
-Darn it.
-You should get some sleep.
How do you expect me to sleep
when you have upset me?
What's wrong with you?
Stop it.
Why should I stop? He turned out like that
because you keep protecting him.
He can hear you.
So what? He should face reality.
You give me no choice.
Honey come here. You, come with me.
Gosh.
Goodness.
-Mom. I--
-Stop. Let's talk here.
My father and you are the ones
ruining Hye-jun's life.
He should learn to face hardships in life.
Mom.
This is his turning point.
If he makes a wrong decision,
he'll turn out like Grandpa.
What's wrong with your grandfather?
Must I really spell it out for you?
He's warmhearted and has a gentle soul.
Goodness.
-It's so fake. Do you think she meant it?
-I doubt it.
So what do you want to do, then?
He's already having a tough time.
What are you bothering him?
How could he think of making a living
by just walking on some platform?
When he was on TV, you used to
brag about him to your friends.
I thought he was going to be famous.
I also had a pipe dream, back then.
Let bygone be bygone.
We must face reality.
Protecting him won't solve anything.
You do live up to my expectations.
You take after me.
You're so good at taking care of yourself.
Anyway, we must wait
until Hye-jun makes his own decision.
We always gave you a chance
to make your own decisions.
So your brother deserves the same chance.
Goodness.
I’m sure there were times when you were
surprised to see yourselves after work.
But you have plans after work.
Don’t worry. You can fix your makeup.
OBSCURE
I'm finally going to meet him tomorrow.
I'm nervous.
I'll tell him
that I've been his fan for a long time
and I root for him.
NEW POST
NIGHT MAKEUP, CHEESE PORK BELLY, EXCITED
Square your shoulders. Gaze intensely.
Guys in the back, keep your distances.
Switch the first and the second models.
Great. Walk with more rhythm.
Great, Hye-jun.
Sir.
Okay.
Gaze ahead. Gaze farther.
Try to look nicer than that.
Yes, where is that?
Jeong-ha, can you organize mine, too?
Okay.
Let’s get our makeup done.
-Hello.
-Hi.
Mr. Won Hae-hyo, this way.
Okay.
I’ve heard a lot about you
from the professor.
-"Professor"?
-Professor Kim I-yeong.
She stopped teaching a long time ago.
Is that so? Well, once a professor,
always a professor.
Why didn’t you call my name?
Oh, I see.
Let’s nourish your skin first.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
How come I don’t get a face pack?
You have good skin, so you don’t need it.
EFFORTLESS HAIRSTYLE AND MAKEUP
It’s done.
Thank you.
The salon director is asking for you.
It’s almost done. But can I finish this up
after I briefly talk to her?
Sure. It’s fine. We have a lot of time.
Thank you.
I’ll be out. Come out once you’re done.
Wait for me here.
She said it won’t take long.
I’m done with my makeup.
I feel bad taking up the spot.
Can he stay here?
He can.
Yes, Mom.
What? You’re here? Why?
Can I sit in the chair?
Yes.
You want me to come out now?
But are you always this quiet?
-No.
-Okay.
I have to go out.
She has something for me.
Go, then.
What about this?
It's done. You can go.
Gosh. My lips…
Can you finish this up?
You're not my client. I can't do that.
Should I pick it up for you?
She wants me to come.
By the way, you're too cold.
It looks like you work at the same salon.
Do you have to divide clients?
I guess you guys aren’t on good terms.
No.
Wait, no. That's not it.
Does she have a nasty temper?
If you were her, would you answer that?
I'll do it.
I'll do it for you.
She’s not mean at all.
People say…
I’m not saying that’s everyone.
Some people say that
I’m not good
at making people feel comfortable.
I’m the opposite.
People love me
because I make them feel so comfortable.
Yes. It’s not just people.
When the dogs see you,
they are so happy that they start barking.
What?
Good dog. One more time.
Stop it.
So you always do this.
You always try to steal clients.
I thought it was a mistake last time.
You agree the first mistake is
considered unintentional,
but after that, it's a nasty habit.
It’s not what you think. The client--
I’m sorry. She and I made a promise.
I told her I would humiliate her
if this happens again.
I have to keep my promise.
-Well--
-No.
You know if you side with her,
you’ll make it more difficult for her.
I'm sorry.
People will think I’m the mean one here.
"She should let it go.
Why is she doing that?"
But you know how evil you are.
I'll contour your face
and do shading.
“I can’t believe I got this lucky.
This is such an exciting moment
of my life.
Living an honest life paid off.
I should be grateful.”
Scratch all of that. Damn it.
But why was Hye-jun so handsome today?
Living an honest life doesn't mean
I'll be happy in life.
Nasty people who don’t care about others
always win in this life.
But I’m so glad
that I decided to be your fan.
Are you my fan?
What?
Do you like me?
Subtitle translation by Won-hyang Son
RECORD OF YOUTH
I was nervous.
Do you know how nervous I was?
Hey, Daniel. It's me.
I did something crazy, Hye-jun.
I can start again.
Look at Hae-hyo now.
You two started out together.
Since he has support,
things are working out for him.
If I can’t do it on my own, I should quit.
Now, you can go to the military.
You said you’re my family.
You want the best for me.
-Family can’t solve everything.
-Then,
don’t tell me what to do with my life.
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs