RECORD OF YOUTH
THIS PROGRAM HAS BEEN SELECTED AS AN
"EXCELLENT BROADCAST CONTENT" AND IS SUPPORTED
BY THE MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS, TOURISM
AND THE KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
Dad.
Yes?
I agreed to be in a movie.
You darn imbecile!
Dad throwing the meat proves
that this is crazy.
I thought you had come to your senses,
-but you're back at it.
-Honey!
-Get over here.
-You can't live my life for me.
What? Let go of me, darn it!
Don't just say you wish me luck,
but let me do what I want.
How is it that you couldn't go a few days
without being tempted again?
Let go of me!
There, I let go.
Let go of what?
You. I'm done with you.
What are you staring at me for?
I let go as you wished,
so do whatever you want.
I'll do whatever I want as well.
And what exactly would that be?
As if you care about what I want to do.
Where do you think you're going?
We're not done here.
Go to your room.
Your dad and I need to talk.
Who should I listen to?
-Me.
I'll listen to mom.
That sneaky little brat.
I like that he isn't dispirited.
What's wrong with you?
Can't you see that this will ruin him?
If you let him do what he wants,
he may end up
living off other people forever.
Put that in your prayers, why don't you?
How can you say that as his parent?
I only worry because I'm his father.
That's a crappy way
to worry about someone.
Who will believe in our children
if we don't believe in them? Look outside.
There is a long line of people
waiting to criticize them.
But he's a man.
He must marry and provide for his family.
That's not an easy task.
Why is it only a man's job
to provide for his family?
Are you saying that you provide for me?
I work for a living too.
Where on earth would he find
and marry someone like you?
You lucked out yourself, so why can't he?
I want to let Hye-jun choose his own path.
Just like you said, it could ruin him.
But at least he would have
the chance to do what he likes.
Have you lived your life
doing what pleases you?
No one can live
by only doing what they want.
Life isn't a joke, you know.
You were a smart kid
who received good grades.
But you spent all of your adulthood
only focusing on earning money.
Let's…
Let's give our children
some space to breathe.
It's the only reason I'm working.
I may have to do manual labor
until the day I die,
but I want our children
to have a better life than mine.
Life rarely goes the way you plan it,
but I don't want to be the one
who shuts down his dream
before he gives it a chance.
I won't let you be the one either.
You'd better not regret it then.
Life is all about the right timing.
Don't you dare resent me
for not putting a stop
to this madness.
Why wear those to bed?
I want to look pretty in my sleep too.
You're a hard woman to understand.
Then love me instead of
trying to understand me.
Did Hae-na get into law school?
The results aren't out yet, but she's in.
Just like me, she got good grades.
It's not just good grades
that gets you into law school.
What else do you need?
You leave the kids to me
and only check in from time to time,
but you should know that
there's more to it.
I have to say
that you're quite good at asserting
the role you play in this family.
-Must you be so mean all the time?
-You should be used to it by now.
It bothers me more now that I'm older.
I endure everything
that bothers me too, you know.
I'm jealous of the happy couples.
As if that changes much.
Honestly, there's no big difference.
You're not aware of
the issue at all, are you?
This is why I obsess more over the kids.
Even though you do,
you'll come back to me eventually.
I do hope that day comes.
Where are you going?
The kids aren't home yet
which means I must manage them.
What are you up to?
Mom.
What is all this?
Thanks.
There's no need to thank me
because I'm only being selfish.
This is so that
you don't resent me later on in life.
I could be harsher on you
than your dad, you know.
Then I love my selfish mom.
RECORD OF YOUTH
EPISODE 4
Wait. I almost forgot.
Is he disappointed by my lies
or is he burdened by the fact
that I like him?
Why hasn't he texted?
My problem is mine to solve.
I wronged him by lying,
but then I told him the truth.
That means the ball is in his court now.
SA HYE-JUN
Talk about being rude.
Unbelievable.
SA HYE-JUN
Hello?
Were you working out?
-No.
-You're out of breath.
I was just on my way out.
-Where?
-Somewhere to busk.
What about after that?
I'll be heading home.
Got it.
What exactly did you get?
Now I know that you're free,
I can ask if we could meet up.
You could have asked me that first.
I didn't want to cut
straight to the point.
That does seem abrupt, I guess.
But I don't mind that at all.
There's something we need to sort out.
Can you afford to chat right now though?
No, I need to get going.
By the way,
did your grandfather find work?
Are you off to see the director?
No, my manager.
Everything will be good for you now.
If you get to be in that movie,
you will blind everyone
and outshine the leading actor.
You sure are blinded by the love for me.
That's why I have a gift for you.
What's this?
You want to be a model.
-When did I say that?
-You said you wanted to earn money.
You get paid for modeling?
Who would hire someone like me?
A lot do, apparently.
We live until we're 100 now,
so you're not categorized as old.
-They say it's a blue ocean market.
-Is that so?
I have a feeling
that this is right up your alley.
If it doesn't pan out,
you can still socialize and exercise.
Get a refund on this.
Why spend money to play and exercise?
-You're scared.
-Of what?
Of failing.
You always say that you'd have tried it
had you been my age.
So you're scared about failing.
Right.
I love that you're honest.
You can do this, Mr. Sa.
Mr. Sa, get a refund. I can't do this.
-Request one yourself, then.
-Come on.
You're not allowed to say
that you would've succeeded
had you been my age anymore.
I don't like how strict you're being.
I'm not particularly fond
of your actions either,
so let's stay true to our words.
But, hey!
What…
SA MIN-GI
What brings you here unannounced?
Get in.
Damn, I'm done waiting. So what'll it be?
I'll do it.
Nice!
A movie star
shouldn't carry things like this.
-Stop it.
-Come on.
You're my artist, you know.
Others won't treat you well
if I don't treat you well myself.
I like that attitude.
Good. Then let's talk about yours.
Mine is always good.
That needs to be changed.
Be less self-centered and more objective.
That's odd.
I'm too objective if you ask me.
Correction.
You are too objective about yourself.
Are you sure you know me well?
Yes, I do. I know you.
It's just that…
I didn't know you'd say yes.
It was too out of the blue.
This means I need to do it too
and I don't think I can.
I know I gave you an earful,
but you said you were giving up,
so I did too.
What?
Hilarious, right?
Even I find it hysterical,
but I'm also happy as hell.
You're scaring me, you know.
Are you in your right mind?
Of course, I am!
CONTRACT
What I hate the most is
when people do business
solely based on
their personal relationship.
I'm done with that too, you know.
I've been there, tried it, and failed.
Most rookies strike a 50-50 deal,
but since you need the money,
we'll divide it 70-30 in your favor.
It lasts seven years? That's too long.
This includes
the term you serve in the military.
This is more than a sweet deal.
Everything's in your favor.
I thought you hated
things getting personal?
I do, but I know
what you're going through.
We'll divide it 50-50
and the contract will last a year.
Anything can happen
and I won't be dead weight to you.
That gaze.
How can I go against you
when you look at me like that?
When it matters the most,
you always get your way.
Do I? I doubt it.
You don't? Unbelievable!
If only the directors knew this.
Anyway, I hear your demands,
so I'll draft another contract.
Let's get smashing!
You won't date anyway, so that's good.
You never know.
I thought you were still hung up on Ji-a.
Why did you two break up anyway?
You made a nice couple.
Ji-a.
HYE-JUN
Just a second.
-Yes, Hye-jun.
-I came to the library to walk you home.
Sorry, but I need to study late.
The law school entrance exam is coming up.
But you normally head home at this hour.
I'm kind of in the zone today.
Got it.
But I said I'm at the library,
so aren't you curious…
as to where I am?
Why didn't you come up to me?
I could ask you the same thing.
You put on this show for me to witness.
You're making me sound mean.
No, I think you're a clever woman.
You planned this just to break up with me.
What you wanted
was for me to head home
quietly after seeing you
and deal with the pain alone.
You've changed.
I was fooled the first time,
but I won't be this time.
Don't doubt my love for you.
I'll only remember
the moments that I loved you.
You can sit here, professor.
Is Ms. An here today?
It's her day off.
Why didn't you tell me about it?
Your manager made the call, right?
Ms. An is still a junior,
so she needs to be requested beforehand.
Besides, I'm in charge
of all our top clients.
Let Jin-ju style your hair today.
Please wait. I'll get back to you
after Professor Kim.
Actually, do Hae-hyo first.
He has a photoshoot soon.
I'll get my hair washed.
Go on.
Must it be no one else but Ms. An?
I see you value comfort over competence.
You know, you've been
quite talkative lately.
It doesn't seem all that professional.
I wasn't able to enjoy tea
with my son this morning.
Could you perhaps set that up?
Of course. Please know
that I am greatly fond of you.
What's bothering you?
I'm telling you this now
instead of waiting until we're at home
because I don't want
to be frustrated all day.
Jeez, you scare me.
I understand that you want
Ms. An as your makeup artist.
But if you want it to be her
and only her though,
you need a good enough reason.
Can't I even choose my own makeup artist?
-Do you like her?
-I do.
Why else would I request her?
So you like her as a makeup artist.
-And?
-Others won't see it that way.
You heard Jin-ju's comment just now.
Why let people gossip about you?
This is a place
where many people come and go.
-I'll change salons.
-Quitting's the easiest way out
and should be the last resort.
Do you know why
I don't want to be in your boundary?
Because it's safe
and you're at an age that seeks danger.
What else troubles you?
I have chubby cheeks
which makes my face look big.
I see.
Then let me take care of that issue.
Let's see.
Here. I added shadows to your face.
I'll compare the before and after
once I'm done.
Everyone, go ahead and look.
JIN-JU
I'm sorry about this,
but can I take one phone call?
-Sure thing.
-I'm sorry.
Yes, this is Jeong-ha.
There's a staff training session
after hours today.
But it's my day off.
I know that, but you should
attend the session.
Shouldn't you have told me
about the training session yesterday?
You think you're a hotshot
now that you've been promoted.
Just know that it only applies
to Won Hae-hyo,
not all the clients in general.
-I wonder why only he requests you though.
-Ma'am!
This is the only way to show you
who has seniority at the salon.
Don't you agree?
I can't wait all day.
Of course.
Well, I have plans this evening.
Jin-u, where's the catering service?
Is there an iron here?
Yes, in the office cabinet.
What are you doing
still sitting here then?
Hey, didn't you hear me?
Traffic can delay the delivery
10 to 20 minutes.
What the hell?
Gosh.
Did you seriously jump out of the way?
You should've prevented it from falling
with your own body.
Do you honestly think
that you're more valuable?
Do you have any idea
how expensive this is?
I'll pay for a new one.
I was going to
take it off your salary anyway.
Can't you properly sort out the wires?
Incompetent piece of shit.
Please don't swear when
you don't even pay me the minimum wage.
I'm teaching you my skills
that money can't buy you classes for.
Its monetary value--
You work all the jobs that are profitable,
-so what are you teaching me?
-Exactly that.
-Nothing's important than money.
-Then pay me my proper wage.
-Today will be your last day then.
-Fine.
I said today's your last day.
-You should work for now.
-I'm reporting you to the labor office.
Jin-u!
Today's my last day, so I'll get to relax
I'm working on my own from now on
You seem happy.
Why should I be upset?
I wanted to take a break.
It all worked out.
I heard quitting is
the easiest thing in the world.
Well,
that only applies to people like you.
I quit only after going through
thousands of moments
that made me wanted to quit.
Do you have to draw a line
between you and me like that?
I was humiliated in front of you.
Don't I deserve to be a bit grumpy?
I have another appointment after this.
Please wrap this up in 30 minutes.
Or I'll just leave.
-I'm leaving too.
-Jin-u.
I know you.
-What do you know?
-That you're all talk.
-Goodness.
-Come on.
I'm sure you know
that I like to crack jokes.
When people laughed at what I said
earlier, I wanted to keep going.
If you want to crack jokes,
make jokes about yourself.
Why would you insult me?
Right. I get that you're mad.
Have I ever dropped honorifics to you
in front of other people?
I addressed you politely and with respect.
But whenever there are people,
you go nuts and insult--
I'm sorry.
I do that because that's how I was taught.
My seniors used to kick me in the shin.
Back in my day,
that's how people learned.
-They only paid me for transportation.
-Good for you.
So are you going to leave?
Did you just yell at me again?
No. I was asking you a question.
Jin-u, do you think you can sleep at night
after leaving me?
Yes, I can. I'll sleep like a baby.
Hold on. Wait. Jin-u.
If you leave like this,
I have to stop the shoot today.
Do you know how much I'm losing?
I don't care.
I'm your college alumnus.
Do you think you can find
another alum in this field?
I shouldn't find another one.
If I meet another alum like you again…
I'm going to punch that guy in the face.
Hi.
SENIOR MODEL ACADEMY
Excuse me. What brings you here?
Well, I…
Okay. So my grandson
got me this.
I see. You came early, sir.
The beginner's class starts next week.
-Here you go.
-Okay.
You and I will be in the same class.
You have a great grandson.
My grandchildren don't even know
what I'm up to these days.
Why is this guy acting as if he knows me?
How old are you?
NEW MESSAGE
MIN-JAE
You're not ambitious enough.
My gosh, that again.
Why don't you make a song out of it?
Let's get serious for a minute.
I'm talking about the direction
my agency should take.
Go ahead.
The present shows a small glimpse
of your future.
The present will be your future.
-Isn't that forcing it?
-No.
If you don't change now,
your future won't change.
I like your honesty and innocence,
but you can't defeat others with that.
Why must I do that?
I'm only competing against myself.
I'll win against myself.
Why would you compete against yourself?
Why would you punch yourself?
If you get hurt,
who will cover your bills?
It doesn't make sense.
You have a point there.
Yes, I do. You're supposed
to compete against other people.
But I don't want to
trample on others to win.
You don't hate competing.
You won't even start because
you're scared of falling behind.
Overcome that fear.
So what do you suggest that we do?
You're here. That's a lot of bags.
What are you watching?
Soccer.
My manager said I wasn't ambitious enough.
She told me to watch the highlights
so I'll get an adrenaline rush
and get competitive.
I like men who aren't ambitious.
My gosh. I know that you like me.
It's all right.
What? That I lied to you?
When did you become my fan?
That arrogant look on your face.
I should've let my fantasy stay as it is.
I shouldn't have met you.
Was meeting me disappointing?
No. I told myself that
I was a great judge of character.
You're bragging about yourself.
Of course, I should compliment myself.
I chose you out of countless celebrities.
And when I met you in person,
I found out you're a really good guy.
How could you be so certain
that I'm a good guy? You just met me.
Are you a bad guy?
I'm a good guy.
See? I was right.
My mom once told me
men who call themselves bad guys
are the real bad guys.
They can lie about everything but that.
Your mother won't meet a bad guy
since she knows that.
Don't you think she knows that
because she met a lot of bad guys?
Yes, I got that.
I'm hungry.
-What do you want to eat?
-I don't eat out often.
Okay. Let's go.
Where?
You want to go to your house.
You said you don't eat out often.
Why my house?
I might want to go to your house.
Shall we go to my house?
What are you doing?
Thank you, Your Majesty.
That's too much.
I really wanted
to say something like that.
It's comfortable now that you know.
I shouldn't have asked if you were my fan.
I don't have some grand values in life,
but I don't want to be a liar.
Then I lied the moment we first met.
That made me feel so suffocated.
-Dig in.
-Okay.
This is good.
Tteokbokki is my comfort food.
Why are you patting on my back?
Is this the wrong one?
Drink this.
What's up with your eyes?
-What about my eyes?
-They look too sweet.
I was just looking at you.
Good for you.
You can win over people's hearts
just by looking at them.
You sound hyper than usual.
It's the side effect of lying to you.
Imagine how badly
I must have wanted to meet you.
And I have tons to tell you.
-You can tell me everything today.
-Not when I'm sober.
When you make a bomb shot,
the way you mix them
and the ratio are important.
People tell me I make the best bomb shot.
You already told me that twice.
Are you already drunk?
How could you have such a name too?
I really don't know
what I should do with you.
When you don't know what to do,
don't do anything.
Okay.
INDOOR TENT BAR
Why aren't you drinking?
At least one of us should stay sober
in case something happens to us.
Nothing will happen to us.
I'm just preparing myself just in case.
You seem to complicate your life.
In that case, I'll drink some more.
It's mine.
You said you're not drinking.
Even if I'm not, it's still mine.
I don't like losing my things.
You're not losing it.
You're giving it to me.
You might think
mixing drinks isn't that big of a deal,
but it's a lot of work.
I gave it to you.
I've never heard of a Sa except Lady Sa
in Record of Lady Sa's Southward Journey.
-Have you read that book?
-The soap opera of the Joseon Dynasty.
You're even smart enough
to figure that out.
Isn't it unfair how you have the looks
and the brains?
-Will you keep doing that?
-No.
Sa Hye-jun.
Who will I forgive?
I will forgive you.
I will forgive your sins.
You know what?
When you're having a hard time,
you pretend to be more cheerful,
so other people won't find out
how you really feel.
I know. That's what you're doing now.
You got me.
If I were to meet you in person,
I really wanted to thank you.
You're late.
It's midterm week soon.
I stayed behind to help
my student get ready for it.
The light.
You know I'm sensitive to lights.
Okay.
NEW MESSAGE
MOM
It's Da-on's birthday this Saturday.
You're his sister. Get him a present.
My dad is a carpenter.
My parents are not rich.
Some people assume that we're rich
when I say we live in Hannam-dong.
I have an ordinary family.
We fight and make up. We keep repeating
the cycle of fighting and making up.
Initially, I became your fan
because you were handsome.
But then, I started to emphasize with you.
I liked that we were the same age.
Fangirling over you was therapeutic.
It feels like you're talking
about someone else, not me.
It's not you. It's the fantasy I created.
But still, thank you.
I'm happy that I was able to help someone.
I believe fans and stars
shouldn't have real-life relationships.
On top of that, we forged
a new friendship out of all relationships.
I decided
to stop fangirling over you.
I won't do it.
Gosh, I just lost a fan
when I don't have a lot to begin with.
I'm sure a lot of girls are
following you around.
Just because they follow me around,
it doesn't mean they are my fans.
It's hard to get them to stay
with just looks.
So you know that you're handsome.
There was a time
when I didn't like my looks.
Gosh.
Did you buy new shoes?
Well, yes.
-What are you doing?
-I still think the other color--
No, they are better in that color.
Why are you in your brother's room?
This is the only computer in the house.
Don't just stay home
because the exam is over.
Go and get a part-time job.
You can come to the site with me.
I'm looking for a part-time modeling job.
Your handsome face worries me the most.
It's easy to idle your life away
with that face.
People know how precious money is
when they work their ass off for it.
You think you can do anything you want
because you get paid for just walking.
Is your father handsome too?
I'm not sure.
I guess you could say he's cute.
He's short.
Then, you must take after your grandpa.
Yes. I resemble my mother a lot too.
Then, let me sum it up.
Your father is
not that handsome
and short.
But your mother is beautiful,
and your grandpa is handsome, right?
You're so funny.
It must be hard on your father.
Why? That's not true.
Your father knows too well
about the value of having a handsome face.
But he's refusing to see it.
Why?
Because he's not handsome.
Is he that ugly?
Stop it. I'm starting to like my dad.
And I've been hating him lately.
What's going on now?
There's something I didn't tell you.
What is it?
I talk a lot when I'm drunk.
No. It's not serious or anything.
This behavior lasts the first 30 minutes
after I get drunk.
I just behave a bit differently
for the first 30 minutes.
How differently?
Try to walk straight.
How can I be
on a straighter path than this?
I knew it would be challenging,
but this is freaking hard!
When I quit my office job,
I was confident that
I could make my dream come true.
You're so stupid, An Jeong-ha.
You dream when you go to sleep.
JIN-JU
Not going to answer it?
I can put up with everything, you know.
But the clients like me.
And they want me to do their makeup.
Why is she twisting the truth?
I was just doing my job.
Why? Because it's fun.
But why is she making me look
like a bitch who stole her boyfriend?
Hey.
That's enough now.
Come on.
I think
I must have done something wrong.
There must be a reason
behind Jin-ju's hostility toward me.
I probably gave her a reason to hate me.
No one in the world
would bully others just for fun.
Your 30 minutes are up.
It was my fault.
I will forgive your sins.
Jeong-ha.
Are you embarrassed of me?
Yes.
Where…
Where are you going?
Hey, wait up for me. Wait.
Wait up.
Isn't this a nice song?
Yes, it is.
By the way,
I really enjoy holding your hand.
But could we take things a bit further?
We're adults, you know.
I thought about that too.
You did?
Of course.
Then, should we start today?
I don't think it's marinated thoroughly.
I think it's pretty good.
Don't you like it, honey?
Yes. I do. I shouldn't eat
so late at night. Why did you buy this?
You could've skipped it then.
Don't blame him.
Why hasn't Father come home yet?
It's nice that it's just us three.
Whenever I think about Grandpa
and Hye-jun, I get a headache.
Same here.
You guys make the best pair
when criticizing them.
Of course, he's my son.
What?
Where were you? Why are you so late?
I'm going to start something too.
Start what?
Can't I even talk now?
Don't even talk about that.
Whenever I hear you say that,
my heart skips a beat.
Grandpa, you're too old to start anything.
Stop stressing Dad out.
Just take it easy, please.
Well…
Come in.
Father, can I come in?
Yes, come in.
Did you have dinner?
Have you ever seen me skipping a meal?
No, never.
And I really love that about you.
I'm sure there are other things
that you love about me.
Father, I like you
just the way you are now.
I just want you to stay healthy.
Starting something new
can be stressful, you know.
Also, shouldn't you get another checkup?
No, I'm fine.
And it's just for checking whether
the body is functioning okay or not.
I don't want you to fall ill, Father.
Even you don't want me to do anything.
I'll be good to you.
You're always good to me.
Where's Hye-jun?
I'm sure he's out
doing the things that he wants to do.
I know I told him to do what he likes,
but I'm still conflicted.
You guys…
You guys really undervalue
the importance of good looks.
Hye-jun will make it big. I know it.
I just don't want to worry about him.
SEODAEMUN
Oh, boy.
Gosh.
Hey, are you done drunk talking?
Yes, I think so.
I don't think you are.
No! I said I'm done.
What? I think it's raining.
It is raining.
Let's run. Come on!
-My gosh.
-Gosh.
-Over there.
-My gosh.
I enrolled my grandpa
at a modeling academy.
So you took my advice?
I sure did.
It also helped me reflect on
how my opinion on him wasn't any different
from others' when I said I loved him.
I like people who reflect
on themselves and their past mistakes.
But I don't like people
who are unpredictable.
I like people who keep their words.
I don't like people who make me anxious.
There's someone who's self-reflective
but unpredictable.
He keeps promises but makes you anxious.
Then what will you do?
I won't like him.
I guess you like disliking people.
What do you like?
Even the qualities that I like
bother me sometimes.
I think it depends on the situation.
When I'm in love,
I like everything about that person.
Whoever receives your love
will be very happy.
No. Don't get me wrong, please.
I wasn't saying I want to be loved by you.
I didn't say anything.
I'm very picky.
I told you what I like and dislike.
To date me, the guy has to satisfy
all those requirements.
That's a given.
Do you know how many people
don't think it as a given?
Jeong-ha.
One of the best things about you is that
you admit it when you're wrong.
I'm sorry. I'm not that picky.
But I'm difficult.
An obsessive fan
with a bad drinking habit.
Do you know what that means?
Sadness.
I've never loved anyone in my life.
I'm in trable.
He never spells anything right.
Help me.
What's going on?
Jin-u is not picking up.
Did something happen?
He fought with Mr. Yang.
If it's about Mr. Yang,
I'm even more confused.
-Why is he there?
-Right?
OBGYN CLINIC
What's he doing?
What do you think? We've been fooled.
You prick.
-What's up?
-I don't want to get this shot alone.
-No one's going to shoot you.
-What are you talking about?
You need to get beaten up to a pulp.
Gosh, stop it.
Here.
Get vaccinated against cervical cancer.
But how?
I don't have a cervix.
I know, but it's effective. Do it for me.
-Hae-na, please.
-You won't do it?
I will do it.
I want to see those three stamps soon.
What? Three?
You have to get it three times.
We're dating secretly at the moment.
Knowing that we might get caught,
we should minimize other risks.
I don't want to end up
with cervical cancer.
I'm clean. Seriously, please believe me.
I don't believe anything without proof.
Those stamps will serve as proof.
Your girlfriend sent you here?
-He has a girlfriend?
-Yes.
-No.
-You knew? Only I didn't know?
No. I said, no. Why believe him, not me?
Because he thinks I'm more trustworthy.
Hey, this vaccine isn't only for women.
Even if the guy gets it,
it's equally effective.
-Break up with her.
-Why?
She's manipulating you.
You've never done this for a girl before.
It's just a vaccine.
I said, it's not just for women.
-I think it's someone we know.
-No!
Why yell? Is it someone we know?
Are you seeing Hae-na?
Jeez, are you crazy?
I guess you haven't lost your mind yet.
You at least seem to know
that you can't date your family member.
Mr. Sa Hye-jun?
-Yes?
-Please come to the treatment room.
What the hell?
You're our leader.
The leader must do everything first.
You traitor.
Betraying me, already?
-Are you next?
-No, you're next.
One, two, three.
#FRIENDSHIP #LOVE_REQUIRES_PREPARATION
Let's have lunch together.
I'm meeting up with Min-jae.
Go and eat without me.
-Where are you going with Min-jae?
-She's my manager now.
What? What does she even know?
She knows enough to work as a manager.
I'll speak with my agent.
They rejected me though.
So no thanks.
Hi!
I'll see you at the read-through.
And you. I want you to stay away from me
for a while.
Bye!
Sit in the back. The backseat.
I'm worried about him.
He doesn't discuss things with me now.
He always makes important decisions
on his own, you know.
Min-jae worked as a bookkeeper
and a marketing associate.
She can't do this kind of work.
She knows how to manage money
and advertise. That's enough.
-You think so?
-Yes.
Let's try to be positive.
Anyway, I'm happy we're in the same movie.
-Who got the lead role?
-Park Do-ha.
Wow. It'll be a hit, without a doubt.
Director Choi Se-hun and Park Do-ha.
Hey, let's not speak too soon.
Let's go eat something. Buy me some tripe.
Why should I?
Have you forgotten
about the gift I gave you?
How could I forget that?
Gosh, that hurt.
That fussy prick. He seems totally fine.
-He's just like his sister.
-What?
Buy me a steak. I want a steak.
This is the classic blue I bought.
I told you about it the other day.
That color won't really work for us.
I thought our celebrity clients
might need it as it's a trending color.
Try to find more vivid colors.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I missed the training
and didn't answer your calls.
I was waiting for you to bring it up.
Look at you unabashedly admitting
that you ignored my calls.
I knew you wouldn't come.
Of course, you wouldn't listen to me.
The director and the male clients
got your back.
I have to say, that's a skill too.
I wanted to be someone
who's always reachable,
and that's how I've lived my life.
I don't like people who are unpredictable.
I treat others
as I would like to be treated.
Not answering my calls
isn't that big of a deal.
But why lecture me and talk like
you're better than everybody else?
We just don't see eye to eye.
Since I'm a nice person,
I'll try to be understanding.
Professor Kim
has an appointment at 11 a.m.
It's too tight.
I have another client at 11:30 a.m.
She'd like to get it done by Jeong-ha.
What?
Me? Why?
Yes. You'd react like that, of course.
You act like you know nothing,
but you steal my clients
and act all naive and innocent to my face.
I've seen many girls like you.
Hello!
-Hello.
I'm early, aren't I?
There was no traffic at all.
-Should we wash your hair first?
-No.
I'm going to have a word
with Jin-ju first.
I hope your feelings aren't hurt.
I just wanted to try
getting it done by Jeong-ha.
-Of course, whatever you'd like.
-Thanks.
I'm always so comfortable
around you, Jin-ju.
-That's why I keep coming here.
-Thank you.
I'm just so curious.
I always thought my son valued competence
over comfort.
But you said that wasn't the case.
You're not the type
to say something like that for no reason.
So I wanted to check.
Oh, have the sandwich.
You have a full day today.
The hair and makeup salon,
an interview, and two auditions.
I booked the salon
you mentioned the other day.
Why bother going there?
Does the term "face genius" ring a bell?
Maybe not an acting genius yet, but I want
you to impress them all with your looks.
I'm playing a corporate heir in the movie.
So for the drama,
I want a character who's poor.
As for dramas,
you'll only get such roles for a while.
-Why is that?
-Protagonists in dramas are usually rich.
For movies, it's the opposite.
That is why you got
the corporate heir role.
The read-through is next week.
You memorized your lines?
-I sure did.
-Great.
-But why meet with the reporter?
-Reporters are people too,
and they also have emotions.
We should keep a healthy distance,
but I'm just trying to build connections
in advance.
You're very good at this.
Who'd think you've never worked
as a manager before?
But why must I sit in the back?
I know that no one calls you a star yet.
But to me, you are a star.
A star should be revered.
Expect privileges and try to be snooty.
I want you to get used to it now
so everyone will think
that you were born to be a star.
Pull over.
-Why?
-Just pull over, please.
Hey, why…
What are you doing?
Let's go.
Goodness.
You are helping me achieve my dream.
I know.
When our values clash,
you'll have to respect my values.
It depends on the situation.
Then you can't call them your core values.
I want to stay humble and modest.
I'm a good driver too.
You don't have to do all the driving.
This is…
what I like about you.
Perhaps I volunteered to be your manager
because you're like this.
But do you know
what this world is really like?
Lee Tae-su closed the agency
after you left.
-Did he go bankrupt?
-No, he practically hit the jackpot.
He sold the company to A June,
got paid handsomely,
and now he's an executive director there.
There's no such thing as karma.
I'll uphold my values no matter what.
Gosh, can you please not look at me
like that?
How can I say no
when you're staring at me with those eyes?
Fine, I respect your values.
But when it comes to business,
you must respect my opinion.
I'll be your spokesperson.
-Sounds good.
-Let's go to get your makeup done.
Let's go!
It's done.
I'd like to talk to you about something.
Sure, go ahead.
There's a hierarchy among the staff here.
Once can be considered an exception,
but not twice.
Hae-hyo is an exception, but not me?
I'm just an assistant.
Makeup for women requires more
detailed work than makeup for men.
I'll study hard.
If I manage to surpass Jin-ju,
you can book with me then.
I can see why Hae-hyo likes you.
You obviously know your place.
And that means you're smart.
I like you.
Thank you.
To apply for the low-interest loan
for small businesses,
you must submit a copy of your lease,
proof of your business income,
and your sales reports.
And…
Is this all? Your credit report
is missing, and it's the most important.
That's impossible. Look again.
-You saw me checking everything.
-No, I didn't.
All right, then. Look.
Here's a copy of your lease.
Hold on. Am I a kid or what?
You said you didn't see it.
-What's missing?
-Your credit report.
Why tell me now?
You never mentioned it
when I asked you over the phone.
You didn't tell me.
You spoke to someone else,
and I'm sure that person told you.
It's the most important document.
The top requirement.
Are you saying I'm lying?
Honestly,
this didn't have to take this long.
And what? "Top"? Why use English?
Right, I didn't have to do that.
But if you brought
all the required documents--
-So it's my fault?
-I'm sorry, sir.
I apologize for the inconvenience.
There must've been some confusion.
I'm really sorry.
MANAGER PARK SU-YEON
PLEASE WAIT A MOMENT!
CS BANK
Are you a client or an employee here?
An employee, ma'am.
So you know your place,
but you're slow-witted.
You've been with us
for three months already.
Can't you be flexible
when dealing with clients?
I believe we must go by the book
in situations like that.
I knew you'd be like this.
You always have something to say.
Why was he assigned to my team?
Ma'am, I'm right here.
I know. I'm talking to myself.
How did you hear that?
It was quite insulting
for something you'd say to someone,
so you wanted me to think
that you were talking to yourself.
Oh, I know.
-You're a ballbuster.
-No, I'm not.
I was a drill instructor
when I was in the military.
My nickname was Trooper
because I kept on going--
-Okay, I heard you.
-Don't get me wrong.
I never used violence--
-Trooper.
-Yes?
Get back to work. Don't make me
have a word with you again.
Yes, ma'am. I'm sorry.
What do you think?
I like it.
By the way, did something bad happen?
You don't seem to be in a good mood.
Really? I'm not good
at hiding my emotions.
I'm too honest and straightforward
that people walk all over me all the time.
-Is she gone?
-Yes.
Hold on.
I almost couldn't breathe.
Why would anyone walk all over her
if she was like that?
Anyone who goes on about being the victim
is rarely the victim.
Do you want another beverage?
No, thank you. Where's the washroom?
Make a right turn outside the door.
Please take good care of Hye-jun.
Did Jin-ju give you an earful?
It was my fault, you know.
It was wrong
to ignore her calls like that.
I like people who reflect on themselves.
Anything I can do to help?
Stay out of it. This is my fight.
Bye.
Can Jeong-ha travel
for appointments elsewhere?
Do you like it?
I should be asking you that question.
I always like what you do.
Why are you so generous today?
Do you pity me?
Don't drink with anyone else from now on.
-Why?
-Because you're so cute.
I've heard that too many times.
-Jeong-ha.
-Fine, I don't hear it often.
I've heard "pretty" a lot more often.
-Happy now?
-Yes.
What?
I said I'd see you at the read-through.
Missed me already?
Is this where you had to go with Min-jae?
I'm like Min-jae's avatar at the moment.
I have to do as I'm told.
Please have a seat here, sir.
I'm starting a new movie,
and I want you to be my makeup artist.
-But I've never done that.
-The salon's okay with it.
That's great.
I'm in that movie too. I may run into you.
If I run into you,
I'll do your makeup too.
That's not cool. You'll be there for him.
Hey, I'm not hiring her just for myself.
Gosh, you.
By the way, where's my manager?
-He's already here.
-Yes, I see that.
-You should've booked a room.
-All the rooms were booked. I'm sorry.
-Next time, book a room.
-Will do.
Hello! I'm not late. You're early.
I have another appointment,
so I left the office early.
My gosh, I guess you're busy.
Thank you for making the time
to meet with me.
Hae-hyo got a role
in Director Choi Se-hun's new movie,
so I wanted to have lunch
with my favorite reporters.
I'm not late, right?
No, Reporter Kim.
-Reporter Yoon got here first.
-I see.
Let's eat something delicious.
What about expensive small dishes?
This is on me.
I'll do it.
I've never hated anyone this much
in a while.
Things keep getting tangled.
I don't know what to do.
When something gets tangled,
cutting it off is easier
than untangling it.
If one of us has to stay,
it'll be me, of course.
-We'll get this and a bowl of rice.
-Sure.
-Anything to drink?
-No.
-Got it.
-Thank you.
There's a class theory
that's popular among my generation.
Depending on how much financial support
you can get from your parents,
you're categorized as either
a gold or dirt spoon.
This is for table 13.
And according to that standard,
I'm a dirt spoon.
Here's the food you ordered.
I've always loathed that theory.
So? Have you thought about it?
I have a read-through tomorrow.
Oh, gosh.
So it's a no?
But I want to keep working here
for as long as I can.
Be stubborn.
That is the privilege of youth, after all.
The theory is all about money.
The emotional stability
I inherited from my parents.
Honesty and sincerity.
It completely overlooks such values
as well as my motivation for success,
which I cultivated
while watching my parents struggle.
What's Park Do-ha doing here?
He got the lead role. You didn't know?
No. I was busy trying
to analyze my character.
Why did he come with Mr. Lee though?
He is signed with A June Entertainment.
My gosh, you two. What brings you here?
We're here for the read-through.
After you.
What the hell?
-After you.
-Let's take the next one.
Good call.
Stop them.
Going up.
When you left, you probably thought
you'd have an easy road ahead.
Things are going great for him.
That's why he got the role.
Had he stayed with you,
he wouldn't even have gotten paid.
It would've been awful.
Min-jae, why are you butting in?
Hye-jun, are you mute?
I'm his manager,
so consider me his spokesperson.
Manager…
You're his manager?
-Quiet down, please.
-Sure thing, Do-ha.
I have to say,
you'd probably never get married.
How random.
Are we at a matchmaking agency?
Do you think Hye-jun will make it?
His career never took off
even though he was with me for years.
Mind your own business.
Don't tell me you have high hopes for him.
Wake up.
He doesn't even have a fan community.
Fandom means power,
which translates into popularity.
Fan community? What about it?
It's not like the others always had it.
You sound so proud.
You know, it doesn't mean much these days.
You got a role in this movie?
You got the lead role?
I've been staying away
from the Internet, so I didn't know.
You probably got a no-name role anyway,
so we won't run into each other.
You'll be surprised
when you found out which role I got.
I flinched when I saw you,
but thinking about my role makes me happy.
Which character are you playing?
Hey, which character?
Hello.
-Sir!
It was you?
You son of a bitch!
Son of a bitch?
I'm not a thug.
Why would I hit you with a stick?
Hey, that's not your line.
I'm sorry.
I don't know where that came from.
Jeez, it's so frustrating
to work with a total rookie.
-Hye-jun.
-Yes?
I actually like that.
Director, then the focus will be on him.
I'm the lead.
It'll only help your character shine more.
What were you going to do next?
Untying him
and punching the crap out of him
would make my character
look more ruthless.
You think so?
Let's try it. Can you guys untie him?
-Untie him.
-Okay.
Ouch, that hurts.
Becoming like him has been my dream
up until now.
Can you try punching him once?
-Punch him?
-Give it a go.
We met again,
and I've changed.
Today, I finally realized
why I was so eager to become an actor.
To an actor, a spoon is just a utensil.
Subtitle translation by Hye-lim Park
RECORD OF YOUTH
I was so excited today.
So excited that I couldn't even think
about anything.
Have you seen my watch?
You're the only one who would touch it.
-You're talking nonsense.
-But there's a reasonable doubt.
Jjajang or jjamppong?
-Jjajang.
-Jinx.
Are you two dating?
-Min-jae!
It's weird.
Every time I'm with you, it rains.
I just kept thinking
about my character, Su-yeong.
He's like a different person.
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs