RECORD OF YOUTH
THIS PROGRAM HAS BEEN SELECTED AS AN
"EXCELLENT BROADCAST CONTENT" AND IS SUPPORTED
BY THE MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS, TOURISM
AND THE KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
You have to get the right amount.
Not too much, not too little.
What kind of answer is that?
-It's too hard.
-You'll get it once you practice a lot.
Open and close your eyes.
This feels comfortable.
The inner corner isn't covered,
so it doesn't sting.
Then, you should try this, too.
I got it.
You girls are having fun.
Keep having fun with her,
but don't forget I got you here.
If I continue to see you
fraternizing with her,
you'll be following in her footsteps.
Don't you know
how people think of her at our salon?
How do they think of me?
You're so clueless.
You must be only interested in yourself.
You should have braced yourself
for a bad reputation
when you stole my clients.
The director called you.
MAKEUP ARTIST AN JEONG-HA
WON HAE-HYO: MAKEUP AND HAIR
LIST OF APPOINTMENTS
There aren't as many appointments
as I had hoped.
I know you just started.
I'm trying my best.
Of course. You're known as a hard worker.
But you must have a sense
of responsibility to help the salon
retain its clients and flourish.
And that sense of responsibility
leads to good performance.
It may not be fair to others
to promote you this way,
but I figured that it was worth it
even if there's backlash.
Please do a better job.
Okay.
Oh, right.
Professor Kim I-yeong is a VVIP.
Especially take good care of her.
But Professor Kim isn't my client.
Ma'am, Professor Kim is here.
I just wanted some water.
Why did you bring me to the director?
I'd be sad if you left without
seeing me when you came here.
Would you like some tea?
No, I want water. But no cold water.
Jin-ju, bring her some water.
Jeong-ha is her makeup artist.
Why don't we let them have a chat?
I guess there was a miscommunication.
I decided to get my makeup done by Jin-ju.
We rarely have communication problems.
But it seems there was one this time.
Better the devil you know.
But I'm not saying Jeong-ha is
a bad makeup artist.
I'm just comfortable with Jin-ju.
Making her clients comfortable
is an important skill.
Thank you.
I'll get that water for you.
-Jeong-ha.
-Getting your hair done?
No. I needed a pick-me-up.
Have you seen an agent who causes trouble?
I got a brand-new hairdo,
but I still feel shitty.
Yet, I have such a big appetite!
That happens if you're stressed out.
I've never lived for myself
after my father passed away.
I'm finally free after supporting
my mom and my siblings.
But I've never enjoyed my freedom,
so it scares me every day.
And I hide it by acting silly.
When I met you,
I thought you were special.
You were so lively.
Like a wild, untamed beauty.
I'm sure other people feel the same way.
"She's special.
I want to be friends with her."
You're sweet.
I get why Hye-jun likes you.
No.
I know you two are dating.
Hye-jun told me.
Once he's in love with someone,
his love becomes immeasurable.
Min-jae, hearing that
doesn't make me happy.
-Why not?
-That applies to his ex-girlfriend, too.
You must really like him.
You sound jealous.
No. I'm just stating the fact.
His love was immeasurable,
but they still broke up.
And now, he doesn't have
the slightest feeling left.
It's totally over.
Isn't that attractive?
Yes, it is.
And so is everything about him.
Can you
comfort Hye-jun?
I'm sorry.
I messed up.
But can you clean up my mess?
-No.
-Damn it.
I won't be able to make him feel better.
THE PRESENT
I BOUGHT THIS BOOK
BECAUSE I LIKED THE TITLE
"I also want to be a present to you."
That's so cheesy.
JEONG-HA
HYE-JUN
Hi, Jeong-ha.
He's crying.
Did you catch a cold?
No.
You sound like you have a cold.
I'm glad you don't though.
He's not talking.
Is he still crying?
I'm bored. Want to hang out with me?
Sure.
I know how it feels
to get your heart broken.
You're really good.
No, this looks awful.
Mastering the basics is the hardest,
and you did it on your first try.
I see talent.
You do take after me, you know.
She takes after you?
Ridiculous.
What good will it do?
Jeong-ha is still here. Be careful.
Jeong-ha, go out now.
I need to talk to your mom.
No, stay here.
She must know what's happening too.
Does playing with her fulfill your duty?
You can't even make a living.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize. Go out and make money.
Get a manual labor job if needed.
You need to do anything you can.
Why must I take odd jobs and get insulted?
Even if I go to the employment center,
people won't hire me.
It's because they know
how irresponsible and weak you are.
Let's go.
Go with your mom.
I'm okay.
Let's go.
Will you disappoint me like your dad too?
Do you want me to die?
Hey, you crossed the line.
How can you say that to her?
This is the reality Jeong-ha is facing.
I'm going crazy
because of your incompetence.
I'm teaching her
she must be independent in this world.
I'm warning her.
She can't live like us.
He's not coming. Don't look back.
Only we can protect ourselves.
My mom taught me the harsh reality
when I was nine.
And my dad taught me how to hold
-a pencil when sketching.
-Like this?
Yes.
-They both loved me.
-Go ahead.
And love
brought me sadness from the beginning.
YEONGNAM REPAIR AND BUILDING
Here.
Why are you so nice to me?
Because you're my boyfriend.
Be nicer.
Ta-da.
That's why I got this.
Read this later.
Did you read it?
"When you are utterly focused on your job,
you won't be distracted, but happy."
How's that going for you?
I'm good at driving.
Then, you must be happy.
Are you happy?
Not yet.
Then, what about you? Is it going well?
I'm good at talking.
-So are you happy?
-Yes, I am.
Me, too.
When I love this man, it makes me
want to become a better person.
And this man has a name.
Sa Hye-jun.
That was cool.
Searching for the stars
Sparkling in the night sky
I see your eyes blinking
Oh, how beautiful they are
I finally take the steps
After hesitating over and over again
And I will never forget
How you held my hand
RECORD OF YOUTH
Thank you.
I can walk just fine.
Gosh.
What are you up to these days?
I'm trying to help you, Grandpa.
Dad was shocked after hearing
you fainted from overworking.
I'm all right.
I'm trying to help, you know.
What's all this?
Why didn't you clean this up?
This is Father.
-Right. That's Grandpa.
-What…
-This must be it.
-What?
He's been going to a modeling school.
Gosh, Grandpa looks like
a real model in the photos.
Hey. Do you think so?
Are you happy?
You reek of alcohol.
My goodness. This is a nice jacket.
Father.
Are you here to cause trouble for me?
No parents want to cause trouble
for their children.
Didn't I tell you I'd never see you
if you cause trouble again?
I want to be a proud dad to you.
I call you Father, not Dad.
But your children call you Dad.
Just like you, I want to be called Dad.
It sounds more endearing than Father.
Our relationship is not like that.
I regret what I did
hundreds of times every day.
"Had I been a better dad,
our family would have had
better lives now."
I want to go back to the past
and try again,
but I can't do that.
I was supposed to live a diligent life
from the beginning.
But I didn't know that.
-Don't talk to me as if you care.
-Yeong-nam.
I might not have been
a good father to you, but before I pass,
I want you to acknowledge
I tried my best to become a good one.
Why do you want that from me?
You've lived your life however you wanted.
No one can live like that in this world.
You punk.
That's not fair.
Gosh.
Is Father really going
to a modeling school?
Call Hye-jun.
He's not home?
I hit him because I was so livid.
You hit him? Did you hit our son?
He kept saying he did nothing wrong.
He was the one who paid
for Father's tuition.
-That hurts.
-Why would you hit him?
Do you think I'm happy I did?
Is that why you were drinking?
To make yourself feel a bit better?
Are you even curious
about where he could be now?
He's old enough to take care of himself.
He wasn't cast for the drama in the end.
Gosh.
They already gave the role to him once.
Why did they take it back?
Why would he put up with that?
Seriously. I wasn't going
to compare him to Hae-hyo,
but if he were born into
a rich family like Hae-hyo,
he would've been famous long ago.
But he got struck out with us.
Don't talk like that.
Go out and find Hye-jun.
Dad, you have me.
Hye-jun seems amicable
and doesn't seem to hold grudges,
but he can be really stubborn at times.
Like that's going to change anything.
I hit him once
when I was in middle school,
and I can't say a word to him now.
He goes berserk.
He doesn't even forget it.
He won't forget what I did, then.
Dad, you're too softhearted.
How will you live without me?
What am I going to do? I'll miss you.
I can always come.
Why isn't he home already?
He has to help me move tomorrow.
Sol, mi, mi
Fa, re, re
Do, re, mi, fa
Sol, sol, sol
-I'm tired.
-Next one is really easy.
-Re, re, re,
-The spring breeze
-Re, mi, fa,
-Flutters
-Mi, mi, mi, mi,
-The flower petals
-Mi, fa, sol,
-Smile beautifully
-Sol, mi, mi
-And the sparrow
-Fa, re, re,
-Chirps away
-Do, mi, sol, sol
-And dances
-Mi, mi, mi
-To its song
-Finish.
-You had to finish the song.
I finish once I start something.
What a show-off.
No, I'm just good.
I agree. You're cool.
What is it?
This is comforting.
Let's go, cheetah.
Yes, cheetah!
There's nothing wrong with it, you know.
-Sol, mi, mi, fa, re, re
-What a clumsy baby.
-So what if I am?
Sorry about that.
Thanks.
What?
There's something I want to do,
but I need your permission first.
You have it.
I thought about it,
and you're always allowed.
Can I be too?
Do whatever pleases you.
We should've taken the cart.
I can't believe this long walk.
We haven't been
out on the field for a while.
I thought it'd be nice to have a chat too.
You love to chat.
Doing what I really want
is how you get me in a chatty mood.
You always do whatever you want though.
-Hold on.
-How can I possibly…
Can you pull over?
Is it someone you know?
I know them.
Hello, Mother.
You're a douchebag.
Mother,
don't you think that's a little harsh?
Mother, my ass.
How can you possibly
manage my son's career
when you don't even know
what's appropriate?
I'm not interested in
what you have to say.
You can't insult someone
over some chump change.
When it comes to money,
even a penny matters.
You keep failing
because you know nothing about money.
End the contract with my son
and get out of our lives.
Do so, and I'll back off.
Mr. Lawyer, go ahead.
I didn't think we'd cross paths again,
but here you are.
What a wonderful day.
What the hell? Is he challenging me?
Yes, hello.
When I last saw you, Mother…
Oh, sorry. It's inappropriate
to call you that, right?
Anyway, here you go.
A June Entertainment.
Isn't that Korea's
top entertainment agency?
We're not exactly number one,
but we're at least in the top five.
I'm a director there by title,
but it won't be a stretch to say
that I take care of most of the business.
I see.
A director at A June?
What a joke.
Do-ha!
Come on over and say hello.
She's an acquaintance of mine.
Hurry on over.
Hello.
I'm not exactly up-to-date
on Korean celebrities,
-but I've heard of you.
-Thank you, sir.
You know Hae-hyo, right?
They are his parents.
I see.
We filmed a movie together recently.
He's not so dense after all.
What is this? The duo from hell?
It was great to meet you,
but we should get going.
Well, I wish you a good G today.
Have a good day.
What's a good G?
He and his cheap choice of words.
Does G stand for golfing?
Shouldn't he wish us
a good "round" of golf?
Have a good R!
Was that seriously the takeaway for you?
Anyway, go ahead. I have a call to make.
Sure.
CAN PARK DO-HA MAKE A COMEBACK WITH CATCH?
GO KILL YOURSELF
Sons of bitches.
They still want me to kill myself.
Did you receive hate comments again?
Just don't mind any of them.
You suck at empathizing.
I'm your manager.
My job is to solve issues,
not hold your hand
and sulk with you regarding the matter.
This is because you were too nice.
You should've taught your haters a lesson,
not let them off the hook.
You know what haters say, right?
"I've been having a hard time."
"My life sucks."
"I'm sorry,
but stress got the best of me."
They are all lies.
Haters are just bastards, not sick or ill.
Why can't you just listen to me?
You know,
you're decent at times,
but you also get on my fricking nerves.
You blabber way too much.
Don't forget that your job is to serve me.
There's a line you shouldn't cross.
I empathize with his situation
but he chews my head off in return.
I was going to announce it
and sue all their asses this week
all the while informing the media.
So for now,
let's play a round of golf, Actor Park.
You ungrateful brat.
INCOMING CALL
MS. KIM I-YEONG
Yes, Mom.
Have you heard about Lee Tae-su?
He's a director at A June.
One with shares.
So it's true.
Justice is never served in this world.
-Why?
-I met him at the golf club.
Did you read Mr. Yoon's new script?
Yes, I found it intriguing.
Seriously?
Yes, I liked it.
Who's the lead?
It's not a done deal yet,
but Park Do-ha and Jessica.
Are you and Park Do-ha close?
Not really, but we get along.
He's over-the-top at times,
but easy to read.
Do you want to be in it?
Sure, I do.
Why though?
Got it.
JEONG-HA
The receiver cannot be reached.
You will be directed to voicemail after--
JEONG-HA
Sorry I can't take your call.
I'll call you back a.s.a.f.
A.s.a.f?
Shouldn't it be "a.s.a.p"?
I hate people who can't spell properly.
SUPERSTAR SA
Yes, superstar…
I mean, Actor Sa.
Come to the cafe near my house
in 30 minutes.
But I'm in the middle of a meal.
Is that a no?
As if I'd ever say that to you.
Of course, I can be there.
See you soon then.
You must be enjoying that.
Of course, I am.
The chunks of fruit
make the drink seem fresher.
How delightful, right?
Yes, delightful.
Must you be this way?
This is you abusing your power as my boss.
That's only true
if you were still my manager.
Saying I'd think about it
was my way of asking you not to let me go.
I'm new at this, you know.
Unlike you,
I'm not experienced in this field.
Isn't that worth a bonus?
Only when you show competence.
Then let me show you
just how competent I am.
You know the casting director Song Jae-su?
-Yes.
-He wants a model-turned-actor.
No acting skills required.
Just good looks.
That's all he needs.
This is exactly
what I've been getting you ready for.
I owe my good looks to my parents.
Hand me an olive branch, will you?
-Must I audition?
-An interview is required.
Then set up a date.
I already have. Tomorrow at 3 p.m.
You seem different today.
Did something good happen?
Where are you off to?
To help my brother move out.
All right. It's all done now.
Take care. All those years…
Well, they weren't really great.
May this be our last moment.
Is this all you need?
What about your desk?
A table comes with the house, you know.
Are you that thrilled?
Hye-jun's waiting for you outside,
so get going.
Couldn't he come in
and help with the suitcases?
You're doing just fine.
Why make him do it
when you're still strong enough?
Jeez, Dad. That was ice-cold.
Without you, I'll be all alone.
I'm a loner, I'm a loner
You backstabbing brat.
Grandpa, Mom, and Dad.
-Don't skip your meals.
-Yes, sir!
You're over the moon, aren't you?
Why aren't you upset
when our son's moving out?
You're the weird one here.
He's 28.
We should celebrate his independence.
What are you yelling at me for?
From what I can tell,
she wasn't scolding you.
She was only explaining the situation.
As you know,
she's always had good judgment.
Whatever.
-We'll get going then.
-Sure.
-Drive safely.
-Got it.
YEONGNAM REPAIR AND BUILDING
Dirty cups keep on piling.
Let me take over.
No, I've got this.
I guess you can head straight home
after joining Hae-hyo on set.
Right.
-Su-bin.
-Yes?
What do people think of me here?
Just tell me how it is.
I hate being the only fool here.
They have the wrong idea about you.
Whatever I say can't correct it.
I'd like to hear their exact words.
Only then can I take measures.
It's never ideal to be the messenger, so…
They say you've been selectively
stealing Jin-ju's male clients.
Jeez.
I bet it pisses you off.
It does.
Still, I have a job to do.
-Can you wash the rest as well?
-Got it.
Jeong-ha.
Good luck!
Good luck to me.
Did something bad happen?
No.
I'm just considering it
as something common.
There's no such thing
as a smooth path in life.
So what you mean is that
you're on a rugged path
which is making your life hard.
Why are you driving to set by yourself?
I just wanted some peace and quiet.
Okay, then I'll keep quiet.
How's Hye-jun doing?
I wonder why I'm asking you.
Maybe you think I'll have the answer.
He makes you laugh even on a rugged path.
I guess it shows his competence.
He sure is.
YEONGNAM REPAIR AND BUILDING
-Nice and clean, right?
-Right.
You can come by at times.
Not too often, though.
The inside's even better.
All right.
That's odd.
Wait, do I have the wrong unit?
UNIT 502 PASSCODE: 1388*
-What…
-Is this the right place?
I'm not that stupid, you know.
Jeez, all right. Why won't it open then?
This is unit 502.
-What…
-Let me see.
What the hell?
Why are you trying to get into my house?
You're the one who's trespassing.
And those pajamas.
It's like you're living here.
Because I am living here.
You're the fifth person today
who claimed that this place is theirs.
So how can I not be cranky?
How can we believe
you're the actual owner?
-Nicely asked.
-You've been scammed,
so report it to the police.
Call your realtor.
Right.
Goodness.
Damn it.
The number you've dialed
has been disconnected.
What?
The number you've dialed is…
Why has it been disconnected?
Wait…
What…
-We apologize.
-Damn it.
This can't be.
It isn't!
Lower your voice and get lost!
Let's go.
No, I can't.
I won't take a single step
until I get to the bottom of this.
We already know half of the story,
so let's figure out the rest.
-Hey! But…
-Keep it down, will you?
Hye-jun.
I'm telling you. This is my place!
Wait…
The power of attorney form.
My seal.
A copy of the register.
My contract for unit 502.
The owner was Kwon Nam-hui
and this is the bank account.
TRANSACTION RECEIPT
It belongs to Kwon Nam-hui, too.
Everything's perfect.
I know. You perfectly fell for the scam.
Five people
have signed a lease for unit 502.
How many times must I tell you this?
That Kwon Nam-hui
just has the same name
as the real owner of the unit.
He says this is a dual contract.
You signed a lease
for a unit that is being rented out.
I heard him, you know.
The owner could be an accomplice
who's lying about all this.
The homeowner will be questioned too.
So please head home and wait.
We'll reach out to you.
Does this mean
he'll lose the entire deposit?
Should I give you hope?
Shit…
Gyeong-jun, I'm hungry.
Let me buy you dinner.
As if I'm in the mood to eat.
Can we get two more portions
of pork belly?
Sure thing.
Two more portions of pork belly!
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
And steamed eggs, please.
Steamed eggs, too!
YOU HAVE NEW MAIL
FROM LEE YEONG-SU
BCZTV, THE WORLD'S TOP MCN
Hello. I'm Lee Yeong-su, partner manager
at BCZTV's Korea team.
We would like to offer you a partnership.
Cut. Okay.
-Good job, everyone.
-Good job!
-Bye.
-Good job.
Good job, everyone.
I'll get going then.
Hae-hyo will take you home.
I want to go alone.
-Tell him I said bye.
-Okay.
-Good work.
-Great job.
-Thank you.
Where is she going?
She wants to go alone.
I'm Hye-jun's fan.
Don't tell Hye-jun.
I bet you like him even more now.
I know how great he is.
Right. I do like him more.
So I'm trying
not to develop feelings for him.
I was totally determined not to date him,
but I couldn't resist.
Am I doing the right thing, Hae-hyo?
Hey.
What?
Hey, don't be startled.
What's going on?
I wanted to say bye.
To end the day properly.
Okay, let's end the day properly.
Get home safely. Good work today.
Bye.
Don't go.
It doesn't look that difficult,
but I guess it's hard.
Yes.
It's actually harder than it looks.
Why didn't you tell us?
I wanted to become successful
and surprise you all.
Yeong-nam wouldn't say
anything nice about it.
I was also worried
about what you'd think of it.
You made a great decision.
-Let me try.
-Sure.
-It looks easy.
-Okay.
All right. Exhale.
Flatten your stomach.
-Like this, Father?
-Yes, that's it.
Gosh, it's hard.
My goodness.
What are you doing this late?
None of your business.
Your hearing is too good.
This brat, can't he call and tell us
how the move went?
Why can't you call him?
Not until he calls us first.
He seemed so excited to move out.
Of course, he's very excited.
Think about it in his shoes.
I envy him.
Get out.
You take that.
What are you doing?
Those bastards.
I'm just so angry.
Gosh, I'm really upset.
I can't believe I got conned
by those jerks.
Just accept it already.
The sooner you accept it,
the better it is for you.
I can't go in.
How am I going to face everyone?
But you have to, eventually.
Hey.
I have a job that everyone wants,
but my monthly salary is
what rich kids spend on a purse.
I can't buy a house in Seoul
with that money. I'll never be rich.
I'll live this way and keep struggling
until the day I die.
I just wanted to live alone and feel free.
You know,
I wanted to forget about the family
and about my duty as the eldest son.
And this, seriously?
What did I do so wrong?
What have you ever done
for the family as the eldest son?
I always cared deeply about the family.
If you care with all your heart,
it shows eventually.
Who's talking so loudly
in front of my house?
Oh, hey.
Gyeong-jun, what's going on?
What happened?
Why did you bring your stuff back?
Hey, what is going on?
Ask Gyeong-jun.
I don't want to carry this!
But the thing is…
Why did you bring that back?
Hey! Why are you here?
What is going on?
I don't know. They won't say.
-Gyeong-jun!
-Hold on!
I think
it'd be better to ask this one.
Hye-jun, tell us what's going on.
You guys are making us think
that something bad happened.
It is something bad.
Was he conned?
The realtor received money
from multiple people
for the same apartment and ran off.
They'll look into it for more information.
Who said that?
We went to the police station.
I knew it. I thought it was too cheap.
I can't believe this.
How could Gyeong-jun fall for a scam?
Did he not go over the lease thoroughly?
It's not his fault.
You just fall for it
when someone is determined to scam you.
Those who have never experienced it
think that the ones who got scammed
weren't careful enough,
but that is not true at all.
Look at you all excited
to show off your expertise.
Why did he want to move out now?
I told him to save up enough money first.
It's useless to talk about it now.
Think about how upset he must be.
He's never experienced it before.
He must be devastated.
You're so understanding.
Why can't you be like that to others?
Mom's right.
I think you owe me an apology, Dad.
Hey, an apology for what?
For hitting me.
I also think you should apologize to him.
-Father.
-Even parents should apologize
when they did something wrong.
You know I apologize to you all the time.
It's wrong to put your pride first.
Whose fault is it that I hit him?
One thing at a time.
Gyeong-jun getting scammed, then Hye-jun.
Now, it's about Father.
Then this won't end.
The rental scam is the biggest news today,
so that's that.
Ae-suk summarized it all for us.
Sweet dreams.
SWEET DREAMS
I received a partnership offer
from a multi-channel network today.
At the moment, I'm not sure
if I should continue to do this alone
or partner up with others.
I'll meet them first and let you know.
THE PRESENT
"When you are utterly focused on your job,
you won't be distracted, but happy."
I'm holding on to some complex feelings.
It's March already.
Don't catch a cold.
Thank you for watching Jeong-ha's Story.
Let's focus on the meal when we're eating.
And we should have a conversation.
You always say
we should have a conversation,
but never have anything to talk about.
A real conversation should be fun
even when it's about nothing important.
Find a housekeeper who's a good cook.
The older you get,
the less you should eat to stay healthy.
You eat out every day,
so let's eat light when we're at home.
You cook well. Why don't you cook?
Because I don't want to.
And you want a conversation?
Okay, fine. I'll try to find someone.
Ask Hye-jun's mother.
I'll take care of it, okay?
THE PRESENT
THE MOST PRECIOUS PRESENT IN THE WORLD
THREE WAYS TO MAKE BEST USE OF YOUR TIME
LIVE IN THE PRESENT,
LEARN FROM YOUR PAST, PLAN YOUR FUTURE
THE MOST PRECIOUS PRESENT IN THE WORLD
The most precious present in the world is
living in the present,
learning from your past,
and planning your future.
I'm meeting the director
at the broadcasting station.
What are you up to?
I'm meeting with
the partnership manager at an MCN.
I miss you.
I miss you, too.
Where is Min-jae?
I can't believe this!
You said it'd just be an interview.
Gateway--
If it's the resident role,
that's an amazing opportunity.
Well, I just didn't want you
to get your hopes up too high.
He might not get it.
Whether he gets it or not, the fact
that he can audition for it is amazing.
Hello.
Oh, Hye-jun. You look great.
Can you wait about ten minutes
before you come in?
I've talked to the director.
Wait.
Gosh, seriously!
Seriously, I can't stand him! Song Jae-su…
Right, Song Jae-su.
I even hate his name.
Lee Tae-su. Song Jae-su.
Tae-su, Jae-su!
I hate this!
What's going on?
Hey.
Gateway. You've heard of it, right?
The medical drama starring the top actor,
Lee Hyeon-su.
The role you're auditioning for
is a first-year resident in that drama.
The read-through is done,
and the shoot will begin next week.
It'll be amazing if you get this role.
Then I'll have to memorize medical terms.
There will be a lot to prepare for.
It's mainly about romantic relationships.
And that character doesn't do much
as a doctor.
All you have to do is follow Lee Hyeon-su
around and say, "I like you so much!"
How amazing is that?
You and Lee Hyeon-su in the same frame.
You'll become more popular.
Let me fix this.
What are you doing?
Hey, you need to look sexy.
-Show this off. Come on.
-What's your problem?
Show this off!
What on earth are you doing?
Hye-jun, let's do this. Just this time.
-Come on. Just this once.
-No, no!
-Just this once.
-Gosh.
-My goodness!
-What are you doing?
Thank you for the offer.
And I'm curious.
What's your criteria for selecting who
to reach out to regarding partnership?
Well…
I reach out to whoever I like.
I don't like channels
that are all about money
or determined to become famous
so that they can become successful.
I'm not drawn to them.
I like people who try to create
better content to help others.
And that's why I like your channel.
Thank you.
We'll split the profits 60-40.
Well… I was intrigued
by your selection criteria for a moment.
I like people who want to make money
and become famous
through their channels
because that's just a human instinct.
The terms you mentioned tell me that
you're following such an instinct, too.
But I guess you like channels
that deal with classical content.
Have you had any part-time jobs?
Yes, many.
Like what?
As a bodyguard.
I've also worked at a sandwich shop,
and grilled meat and served
at a restaurant as well.
I still work there
because the owner and I are close.
You sound like the loyal type.
Well, that's something
you should ask my close friends.
-Right.
-That's true.
He's very well-spoken as well.
HAE-NA
Hae-na, honey, it's me.
No. She won't like this.
Ms. Won Hae-na.
This is Mr. Kim Jin-u.
Let's talk about the rights A can exercise
to acquire ownership
over the piece of land.
Of course, this will be reflected
in your final grade.
To fully acquire ownership over the land
from B,
A must evict C
and demolish the temporary building.
But can A claim for removal of disturbance
when the ownership
hasn't been transferred to him yet?
A is not the owner of the land.
Hence, A cannot claim
for removal of disturbance.
The key here is,
whether or not A can exercise
B's rights on his behalf as his creditor.
-You're Jung Ji-a?
-The answer is… Yes, he can.
Ji-a!
-Is the exam keeping you busy?
-Well, you know.
You'll pass it, of course.
We're participating in a mock trial
competition. Can you help us?
I have huge respect for you.
All right. Pick the time and place
and send me the theme.
I'll give you a few pointers then.
Thank you.
I feel like I've known you for years.
What are you doing here?
-Do you know that guy?
-"That guy"?
Ms. Won Hae-na, you're so mean to me.
How could you do this to your honey…
You told me not to say that,
but I'm just so used to it now.
You hurt Mr. Kim Jin-u's feelings.
-Are you two dating?
-No!
He's just my brother's friend.
You're Hae-hyo's sister?
You know my brother?
Yes.
Hey, you showed up unannounced
to see your ex-girlfriend?
That might count as stalking.
"Stalking"? Hey, don't you know how I am?
I'd never do that.
Even criminals say
it's unfair that they got arrested.
Ji-a. To be exact,
this wasn't unannounced.
He did send me multiple texts.
You came here even though
she ignored your texts?
That's called obsession.
I will leave.
Honey, if you want to talk… I mean,
if you want to talk with Kim Jin-u,
give me a call.
Jin-u! Nice seeing you.
You're mean.
We'll put wainscoting panels over here.
And we'll install partitions
in the kitchen.
How many boards do you need?
About two bundles?
Two bundles?
-You're working so hard.
-Oh, hello.
I just wanted to stop by.
-Here, have some of this.
-Thank you.
My son will live here
after he gets married,
but they're busy with work,
so they can't stop by.
Don't worry. We'll do a good job.
Thank you.
Have a good day, then.
-You, too.
-Take care.
Her son must be around Gyeong-jun's age.
Hey, I'm sure
he's not as smart as Gyeong-jun.
I feel like I have to prepare
for Jin-u's retirement as well.
Jang-man.
Look at us growing old together.
We only talk about our kids these days.
Were you aware of that?
You're right.
Goodness.
Gosh. Had I been competent enough,
Gyeong-jun would've never fallen
for that scam.
Nothing in life is going my way.
Let's go out for dinner.
That's one of the few things in life
that you have full control over.
Invite Ae-suk, too.
She won't come.
We'll tell her you aren't there.
Jeez. Have fun without me, then.
Do you know anyone who's a good cook?
A good cook? Yes, I do know of someone.
I'm looking for someone
who can come here twice a week.
Just dropping off
some side dishes would work too.
I'm not sure, but I'll ask.
Thanks.
Ae-suk, how about a drink this evening?
The squid mouth and some peanuts.
Then wrap them like this.
Then dip it in the sauce.
It's good.
Honey, you should eat some too.
I made all this for you.
I'm sorry I ate first.
No, it's okay.
I gave him an earful this morning.
Are you protesting because of that?
No, it's not that. I can't stop
drinking this because it's so refreshing.
Work must have been exhausting.
You two are a match made in heaven.
You'd argue and make up right away.
Whenever Ae-suk gets upset with me,
she sulks for quite a while.
-That's because
-Ae-suk!
you always bad-mouth me behind my back.
Hi.
My gosh, what is this?
We'll get another beer.
You must be upset because of Gyeong-jun.
Why bring it up? It's nothing exciting.
It's okay.
Everyone's bound to find out anyway.
We haven't done this in a while,
so let's drink.
Yes, you're awesome!
Ae-suk, it'll be just the two of you
after your kids get married,
so be good to him.
She's always good to me.
I know I'm not good enough for you.
I'm sorry.
Look at him scoring some brownie points.
Hey, this is heavy.
All right. We're in this together!
-Cheers!
-Gosh.
-I have the most fun with you guys.
You're always full of energy.
Maybe it's because you work.
Yes, it does help.
How about I try doing what you do?
You? How?
Why not? I'm a good cook.
You're too opinionated.
You have to completely cater
to your employer to make things easier.
I'm good at that too.
I see that you really underestimate me.
Hae-hyo's family
is actually looking for someone.
Oh, I want the job.
Don't decide so impulsively.
Think about it first.
I'll pick you up tomorrow morning.
Sure, sounds good.
-Bye.
-Bye. Good night.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Are the kids home?
Seven, eight,
nine, ten.
You won't tell me what's up?
Gosh, what's wrong?
Get off me.
Are you mad at me?
No. Why are you here?
What's taking Hye-jun so long?
He's so head over heels for a girl that
he doesn't even care about his friends.
Yes, I think so too.
What are you guys doing?
Hye-jun.
-What's with you?
-Hear me out--
-Go away.
-Oh, he got dumped.
Seriously?
Who is she?
I'll teach her a lesson. This is so mean.
I ran into Ji-a today.
How?
Oh. I thought I saw her,
but it wasn't her.
She's in law school, right?
-Hae-na's school.
-Let's not talk about her.
Did the audition go well? Gateway.
You auditioned for Gateway?
Lee Hyeon-su is in it, right?
I love her.
I'd love to work with her.
-You're not the only one.
-That's right.
I want to work with her too.
But I have no control over that.
What are you doing?
I want to go home.
You guys are boring.
What's with him?
CASTING DIRECTOR SONG JAE-SU
Hello, Mr. Song.
Hello, we'd like to see Hye-jun again
tomorrow.
I don't want to take him back there
if he doesn't stand a chance.
I don't want to put him through that.
You don't sound so interested in the role.
Okay, then we'll find someone else
for the role.
Mr. Song, wait!
I'm sorry.
I was eating cup noodles,
but I think something's wrong with it.
Thank you. Thank you so much!
Nice.
Oh, my gosh.
Gosh, this is nice.
That was your phone.
It must be Jeong-ha.
Hye-jun, you got the role.
This isn't a dream, right?
You got the role in Gateway.
Only happy days await us from now on.
You look so happy.
-I got it.
-What?
The role in Gateway. Min-jae texted me.
Hey, that's awesome. Congratulations.
Thanks.
Get home safely.
You, too.
Stay there. I'll come.
There's something I wanted to tell you
before today was over.
I got the role.
Because of my face, I think.
I didn't show them my acting.
If you did, they'd be knocked out.
I'm grateful to have you by my side
right now.
Let's go, cheetah.
Where are we going?
Just around the block.
-Hi.
-Shouldn't you be giving me an update?
Right. Male, age 13. Mental stupor.
His pupils are five and three.
No reflex in the right leg.
-Diagnosis?
-We're suspecting ICH
and status epiletip…
Sorry.
I'm sorry. I apologize.
Sorry about that.
It's okay.
Medical terms are so difficult.
My brain is about to explode.
But you're always perfect.
I always try to do a really good job
in the scenes with my juniors.
It's embarrassing, you know.
That's how you'll grow as an actor.
All right, shall we try again?
We'll start again from the beginning.
-Okay.
-I'm sorry.
We'll start again from the beginning.
Specimen.
Why are you still here?
Hello.
The shoot is over.
I can't leave
because I did such a bad job.
So how much longer
are you going to stay here?
Until the shoot next week.
Hye-jun.
Yes?
Go home and wash up.
Then go over your next scene in your head.
It's lame to torture yourself.
Let's not be lame.
Thank you so much.
Next time you see me, just talk casually.
Hae-jin.
Did you finish tidying up?
What is it? You're scaring me.
Can I ask you out?
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi
RECORD OF YOUTH
-I can't see a thing.
-Missed me?
I'm happy I'm dating such a good guy.
He can't really afford to be dating now.
Today, I have nothing to say.
You devoted your life to raise me?
Why don't I recall that?
Lucky you. Everyone likes you
the moment they meet you.
-He's always been good looking.
-Of course.
I feel terrible, you see.
Have you heard of a Charlie Jung?
Congratulations on your career.
I'm happy it took off.
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs