RECORD OF YOUTH
THIS PROGRAM HAS BEEN SELECTED AS AN
"EXCELLENT BROADCAST CONTENT" AND IS SUPPORTED
BY THE MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS, TOURISM
AND THE KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
Get in.
-Do you want to drink this?
-No. I'm a bit nervous.
Why are you nervous?
I'm the one who will be rehearsing.
I'm getting close to my dream too early.
My goal is having my own brand
under my name.
What a grand goal.
That way, I'll get somewhere close.
But what does it have to do
with you being nervous?
We're all nameless makeup artists
when we start.
We must rely on doing celebrities' makeup.
I'm not a celebrity.
Well, I wouldn't say you're perfect,
but you're better than me.
Thank you for this opportunity.
Then, do a good job.
It's been bothering me the whole time.
I'll be good.
You ought to.
Come to think of it,
there's one more thing.
You're Hye-jun's fan.
To keep your secret, I--
There's no need now.
We already talked about it.
-"We"?
-Yes. Hye-jun and I.
So there's only one thing
I should be grateful for.
You're sharp.
That way, I won't owe people.
Feeling indebted is the worst.
Can I drink that?
Of course, you can.
If you stayed with me,
I would've taken you with me
to A June Entertainment.
I bought a building.
Won't you congratulate me?
Congratulations.
Could you please move?
All right. Keep acting snobby like that
when you have the chance.
You're ancient history to me.
I have enough power to destroy you
in this industry.
I don't care.
Did you eat?
-I ate a lot. I'm so full.
-It's Hye-jun.
-When did you get here?
-About 20 minutes ago.
Did you come with Min-jae?
Yes. Are you here for the read-through?
I must understand his character
to do the makeup well.
You have to attend
the read-through to know it?
Yes, I have to.
-Am I invisible to you?
-No, you're not.
You're so nice to her.
When were you ever nice to me?
Jealous much? Are you dating?
-Are you crazy?
-Jinx.
-Buttercup.
-Okay.
Jinx, no buttercups.
-You're so childish.
-I'm talking.
-Hey. On the count of three.
-I'll let go.
-In 1, 2, 3.
Gosh. You guys are so childish.
RECORD OF YOUTH
EPISODE 5
The closet…
The room doesn't feel stuffy.
It's hard to find a cheap studio
like this one in Yeouido.
Paying 450,000 won
with a 5-million deposit is a steal.
There's a maintenance fee.
Is there floor heating?
You get what you pay for.
The previous studio's rent was
900,000 won, right?
Yes.
I see. 900,000 won.
I want some coffee, too.
Nice outfit.
You always dress up
when you go to his house.
No. I always dress up.
Are you happy wearing hand-me-downs?
I can't afford to buy
such expensive clothes.
I'm happy to get them for free.
Why would you be sensitive over clothes?
People with a lot of siblings
grew wearing hand-me-downs.
But she's not related to you.
Sometimes, a mere stranger
might be better than my own sibling.
Look at your brother.
You paid for his school and wedding,
but he never calls.
I'm happy as long as he's happy.
I don't want anything from him.
You should be generous
toward your father, too.
I can't find my generosity
when it's about him.
They are talking about me.
Gosh. I can hear everything
through the walls in this house.
I don't want to hear it.
I'm back.
You should drink black coffee.
No, it's bitter.
Black coffee is better for your health.
I even got us a coffee maker.
Why do you do that?
Instant coffee is the best.
Why do you always stop me?
Being stressed over coffee
will be worse for his health.
You're the best, my son.
It's Saturday.
Where did you go early in the morning?
Well,
I went to see some studios.
-Do you want coffee?
-No.
-What studio?
-Are you going somewhere?
To work at Hae-hyo's house.
You should quit that job.
I'll give you an allowance.
You don't make much.
How will you manage that?
I have a nice job now.
I don't want you to work for her.
If you think about it,
we all work for someone.
"Is that someone a company or a woman?
Is the company big or small?
Do they offer good benefits or not?"
Those are the only differences.
What about Hye-jun?
If I were him, I would hate it.
But that doesn't seem to bother him.
-Since he has high self-esteem.
-No, more like he's got no pride.
I'm different. Look how I want
to take care of you now that I have a job.
If you want to,
save the money for your wedding.
I need a girlfriend first.
I'm moving to a studio near my office.
Dad, I don't want it.
Why didn't you tell me that earlier?
-What?
-Coffee isn't what's important right now.
Dad, it's okay.
I can't keep this from her.
I told you to tell her when you move out.
You'll just end up fighting now.
So you already knew?
Dad approved of it.
Yeouido is close,
but the transportation isn't convenient.
He has to make two transfers.
Making two transfers in Seoul
isn't a big deal.
How much is the rent?
It's 900,000 won a month.
Did you say "900,000 won"?
900,000 won a month?
You make 3,5 million won a month.
How much can you save
after the rent, maintenance fee,
and living expenses?
What about your future?
I want to be happy now.
I might die in a car accident tomorrow.
How dare you say that?
It hurt. I'm just saying.
Honey, he's just like your father!
-Gosh.
-He's just like me.
Yes. He does take after me.
I don't want him to take after me
in that way.
He's nothing like my father!
How much money did you save up?
How can I? I just started working.
You had a part-time job in college.
Did you spend it all?
We paid for your tuition.
We're his parents. That's our duty.
Don't brag about it.
Come to think of it, he's always been
this way ever since he was young.
Hye-jun only spends the money he has.
But he doesn't.
He spends way more than he earns.
He's an impulsive buyer, too.
-Is he?
-Come on, Dad.
Which one of our family members
is proud and pretentious?
He wants to live comfortably on his own
without any stress.
That's what Father did.
When he was young,
he neglected his family.
Why do you keep saying
I take after him? Dad!
No! Never.
Mom, I'm an adult now.
I don't need your permission.
I'm just trying to leave on a good note.
Let's have a family meeting.
Why bring in the family?
I'm moving out with my own money.
Then, just move out.
-Where are you going?
-I have to go to work.
I never expected anything
from my children.
Now that you have a proper job,
I thought you're all set.
But look at what you're doing.
I might have to clean up
after you until I die.
Mom.
Gosh, what's wrong with her?
Dad, you weren't helping at all.
No, I was helping you.
But you said she'd be happy
if you told her to quit her job.
She's not happy.
-Something is up.
-Like what?
GIRL WITH A PEARL EARRING
You're reading that book a lot.
It's always a nice read.
"Girl with a Pearl Earring."
What is this book about?
An emotional affair.
A girl whose family went bankrupt
works for a rich family as a maid.
At the house, the head of the family…
You punk. I have been
too nice to you, haven't I?
Why are you mad at me?
You're talking nonsense.
Yes, but there's a reasonable doubt.
Mom's behavior is so odd
that it makes me suspect her.
What's odd about that?
It's been 10 years.
Of course, she's attached.
Exactly. Why work there for a decade?
Isn't that odd to you?
She even quit once because it was hard.
But she went back.
I'm sure there's a reason
behind her working there.
You punk.
My job brings me deeply
into someone else's private life.
I find out things that I wish I didn't.
REGISTRY OF ACCEPTED STUDENTS
WON HAE-NA
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR ACCEPTANCE
TO SEOHAN LAW SCHOOL
-Hae-na.
-What?
You got in.
I know.
-Where are you going?
-Out.
Who are you hanging out with?
You know all of my friends.
Hae-na.
You got into law school
which is a happy occasion.
Shouldn't we celebrate it together?
We must celebrate it as a family.
I will. Set up a date.
Am I your secretary?
You're the one who wants to.
Forget it.
Take your first step without our blessing.
-You're home, Hae-na.
-Ms. Han.
I got into law school.
Gosh, congratulations.
But I knew you would get in.
Nonetheless, congratulations.
What do I need to do to set it up
without making you my secretary?
Why the change of heart?
I want my parents' blessing
when I take my first step.
You take after me.
You're not too proud
and are always practical.
Which restaurant?
I'll book it.
When you're obedient like this,
I make sure to reward you for it.
You're so simple.
Well, that's what I like about you, Mom.
-See you later.
-Okay.
Did she just one-up me?
You can't keep a tally with your children.
You let them win
even if you know their agenda.
She's lecturing again.
She's having a field day.
You want coffee first, right?
I'll drink it later. I had coffee at home.
I didn't like this job
when I first started.
While working,
I became aware that we are all equal.
I didn't learn it. I became aware of it.
Placing the object exactly where it was
as if no one touched it after moving it
is the most important rule of cleaning.
-Do you want coffee?
-Yes. I'll drink it now.
Cleaning the entire house twice a month
puts me at ease.
-It's not because I don't trust you.
-I know. That's the thing with cleaning.
Even we bring in a lot of dust
into the house.
Why don't you hire more housekeepers?
I don't…
If I tell her I don't like
other housekeepers, she'd be too proud.
Given the stress I'd get
from bringing strangers into my home,
I'd rather clean it myself.
Here.
That's how it is at first.
Once you get past it, it won't bother you.
I can't seem to get past that.
Sit down and drink.
No. I'm your housekeeper. I can't do that.
You're a bit different, you know.
Usually, I'm the one who draws the line.
But between you and me,
it's you who draws the line.
Have you seen my watch?
Where did you put it?
Probably where I always put.
Then, it must be there.
Where did it go? I looked everywhere.
But I can't find it.
Gosh. You're the only one
who would touch it.
I can only work
until the end of this month.
What? You can't tell me that
all of a sudden.
You still have 20 days left until then.
I'm sure you can find a good housekeeper.
It doesn't smell clean.
Did you wash it with hot water?
You have such a big house.
I have to clean the second floor, too.
Aren't you using too much detergent?
Ma'am, are you not happy with my service?
Get back to work.
My goodness.
She always moves my things around.
I didn't ask her to organize them.
Why did your housekeeper recommend
someone like her?
Do you know anyone else?
I tried, but I couldn't find anyone.
That's why I asked.
No, I'm not that picky.
My previous housekeeper stayed
for over five years.
Ae-suk is working at Mr. Lee's house?
Yes. Tomorrow?
No, I'm visiting Gyeong-jun
in the military.
You don't need to come with me.
Ae-suk.
My gosh. What are you doing here?
I was walking around the neighborhood.
But you hate walking.
I just feel like walking today.
I'll call you back. Okay.
Do you need to talk to me?
I didn't peg you
as such a coldhearted person.
How could you not even call me?
Why would I? I don't work for you anymore.
Come back. Work for me again.
I'm sorry.
I won't be an exclusive housekeeper.
I like working for many families.
My kids grew up.
You don't need to work for me exclusively.
Tell me when you're free.
I'll make it work.
Do you not like me?
Fine. I won't ask again.
I don't hate you.
If only I could ask
if she is not fond of me then.
You'll get 100,000 won a day,
and you can get off whenever you're done.
I'm paying you more
since the house is quite spacious.
If you turn it down, I'll have to think
it's because you hate me.
Housekeeping
at the house of my son's friend
wasn't an easy choice for me.
Why does that even matter
when it's only a job?
But my son encouraged me to take the job
and that's how I learned
that he has high self-respect.
I know that he's a sweet boy too.
Your house is where
I first worked as a housekeeper.
I learned a lot thanks to my fussy boss,
and now I'm in high demand.
I didn't come here to hear
how popular you are.
So she wasn't taking a walk.
She came to see me.
All I'm saying is that
your family means a lot to me.
Will you come back to us or what then?
You came here to see me, right?
If you need me back so badly,
I'll come back.
-Bye.
-Good job today.
-Good job, everyone.
-Good job.
Family meeting at 8 p.m.
regarding Gyeong-jun moving out.
Call it today's agenda.
"Gyeong-jun's independence."
Hye-jun, make sure to come.
It didn't go as well as I'd imagined.
-What's up?
-We're having a family meeting.
My family's having dinner too.
-Hae-na got into law school.
-That's great news.
Let's have dinner some time.
Us first, though. Any suggestions?
What will you have, Jeong-ha?
Are you asking me to join you
or choose what to eat?
Would we leave you out?
What to eat, of course.
Why are you being shy?
Because she's your fan.
She's excited just to be with you.
Actually, she isn't anymore.
She was quick to fall out of love.
That's how I am.
I can fall in and out of love in a week.
Compared to that, I liked you for
quite long. Being the same age helped.
You liked me and that's that.
Don't try to justify it.
Anyway, jjajangmyeon it is.
You know where.
Let's go. Here's our ride.
You should go with me.
Did you just grab her?
I got carried away.
She's riding with me. I asked her first.
She came with me,
so she'll continue to take my car.
I have my own will and preference,
-so I'll ride the car I want.
-Which is mine.
You know you owe me, right?
You'll let me pay you back this way?
Thanks.
I won't cash it in yet.
I'll go with her, you go with him.
No, you ride with him.
I'll go with my manager.
You won't ride with me?
You two have fun then.
You seem to get childish
around each other,
so count me out.
-It's because of you.
-You're easily provoked.
I'm childish, that's why.
What the hell? Jeez.
-See you later.
-Sure.
How have you been?
-I'll drive.
-Where are we going?
To eat jjajangmyeon. You don't know where.
Fine.
Do you drive?
It's harder to find what I can't do.
You didn't seem like the type, but now--
I'm annoying, right?
It's because I'm awesome.
What's wrong with him?
Sister, please understand.
Watching football videos
has been boosting his ego
and making him pretentious.
You'll soon get used to it.
This isn't right. I got in the wrong car.
-It's too late.
-Too late!
-Good job today.
-Sure.
-Take care.
-Bye.
Right.
-You did a great job today.
-Take care.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
I'll see you around.
Jeez.
I think she's a really nice person.
She's so kind.
Do-ha, just honestly say
that you think she's pretty.
How can you know her personality?
You're quite thick, aren't you?
Sorry?
Also, why do you always
call me by my name?
Even some nobody actor
is formally addressed by his manager.
I'll get her number for you.
Come on. When did I ever say
I wanted her number?
That darn brat.
My gosh!
Are you all right? Gosh, I'm sorry.
Why are you so impatient?
You already unfastened your seat belt.
What if you got hurt?
It wouldn't have been serious.
That's because I held up my arm.
Thanks for that.
I might have ended up in the ER.
Accidents can happen anytime and anywhere.
It's good to be cautious.
Do you remember
how you said I'm patronizing?
-No.
-Hye-jun,
you always admitting the truth
is one of your best qualities.
Sorry, I do remember.
Well, you're patronizing too.
Undoing my seat belt early
isn't worth an earful.
You call this an earful?
Want to really get some?
Sure, give it to me.
You're not playing fair.
Are you two dating?
-Min-jae!
All right. You don't need to yell.
Well, that's how it seems from back here.
I do believe that's mostly
Actor Sa's fault.
-His romantic gaze--
-Min-jae, that's enough.
It was fun earlier,
but now it's getting old.
I thought you two were arguing.
We weren't arguing at all.
That was us exchanging our opinions.
Right, that's what it was.
-Saying that we argued--
-You should get an earful.
That's taking it too far.
Right, I guess I crossed the line.
Unbelievable.
I'm hungry. What will you have?
I'll order for you. Jjajang or jjamppong?
-Jjajang.
In the shyest way possible, I say "Jinx."
I didn't want to do this,
but someone said that not doing so
will bring you bad luck for three years.
It's just a superstition.
Jinx.
You've got to be kidding.
It's jjamppong for me!
She really loves jjamppong.
Let me.
You're quite clumsy, you know.
I've never heard that before.
Can I borrow your phone?
Why?
Can't you just lend it to me
without asking?
Fine.
It's not here.
Oh, no.
Where did I put it? In the car?
Let me think.
-It's not the film studio.
-Okay.
So where did I put it?
-Open the car door for me.
-No.
Give me the keys then.
Is that not allowed either?
It is.
Again, you're really clumsy.
That's unfair.
What is?
No one's ever said that to me before.
I don't need constant care.
I'm the one who usually
takes care of others.
Okay, I believe you.
You're not exactly saying that you do.
-How's that important?
-It is.
Why?
Because I don't want to be like my mom.
Why would you bring up your mom here?
She never did anything to earn my trust.
She divorced my dad
after saying she wouldn't
and married a man with no money
after saying she wouldn't.
You sure have a way of telling things
like they're no big deal.
Imagine how hard it would've been for me
to come to terms with it.
I even read up on psychology.
Thankfully, my dad and I get along.
If we didn't,
I would've been socially awkward.
Why would it make you socially awkward?
It was fine in my case.
You clash with your elders often,
don't you?
No, they all adore me.
The owner of the barbecue restaurant
I work part-time at
even wants to leave it to me.
Sure, I believe you.
It's the same as saying you don't!
Fine, I believe you. Happy now?
Yes, and I believe you too.
All right.
Lean forward and
fix the position of the head.
Instead of swinging the club,
shift your body weight by using your legs.
Nice shot.
That's a good one.
You're ready for the field now.
I'll take you out sometime.
Why would I ask you when I have others
who want to take me out?
I'm just happy that
your career has taken off.
Why are you acting so friendly today?
How can you say that?
We've always been good friends.
We've known each other
for quite some time now.
That's true,
but all I remember is how
you thought of me as someone beneath you.
The memory makes me so pissed
that I keep missing.
Tae-su, why recall
what happened in the past?
-Director Yoon--
-Sir.
So tell me.
Want to cast Park Do-ha?
As if I need to answer that.
Just wait.
He'll soon fall for me.
I have a way with people, you see.
I get how people can change
after finding success,
but you're a completely
different person now.
I once
signed a young actor named Sa Hye-jun.
At first sight,
I was captivated by the aura he had.
It wasn't just that he was handsome.
He was sweet and generous too.
Mr. Lee.
I'll stay with you.
I believe it when you say that
-the sun will soon rise.
-Thank you.
I really thought
it was impossible
for someone like him not to make it.
How absurd is it
for his career not to take off?
But it didn't.
It didn't. It was all just a dream.
I was happy while hoping
for his career to take off,
but I realized
it was just an empty illusion.
Life is far from it.
You have a family to provide for.
That's when I realized it.
The world is dominated
by the bad and the ugly.
So what can I do but become one of them?
See?
You need a backstory like this
to justify one's change,
but you're just trying to take
the shortcut now.
Shouldn't you at least apologize
for what you did to me?
Although, I'm not asking for an apology.
I don't want a belated apology anyway.
So are you saying
you'll let me cast him or not?
Only if my company can co-produce it.
I heard about how you were
offered company shares.
Good. Why don't we grab some drinks then?
I've been cutting back.
I want to enjoy this good life
for a long time.
Have you eaten?
-Not yet.
-We have. Wait.
You're on board with me moving out, right?
I don't give a damn, so do as you wish.
Once I leave, you'll get my room.
It's just absurd how a grown man
doesn't have
his own room.
Noted.
I'm saying you should tell Mom
that you want your own room.
What am I, a fussy brat?
It'll help sell my case to Mom.
-Need any help?
-Not really.
Ask your father to join us.
-Dad!
-Ask him face to face.
He doesn't want to see me.
That's absurd.
Parents don't hold grudges
against their kids.
Dad, you're to join the family meeting.
Right, got it. Hey, Hye-jun.
What do you think about this book?
Have you seen your mom read this?
Yes, many times.
Jeez.
-Why?
-Why what?
I mean,
Gyeong-jun says
it's one of those books, you know.
A girl from a poor family works
as a housekeeper at some house.
And she and her male boss…
No, forget about it.
It's embarrassing to ask my own son this.
Dad.
Do you know why Mom likes this book?
Do you?
GIRL WITH A PEARL EARRING
Is it that intriguing?
What?
What is it about?
Don't know. I haven't finished it.
But you've read it so many times.
I'm just like her.
-In what way?
-Look.
When she cleans,
she puts everything back where it was.
Is this why you love this book?
Yes. This has been my rule
since I started housekeeping,
but I didn't know
if I was doing the right thing.
This book tells me that I was right.
-That's why you like it?
-Yes.
I had the same idea as this author.
I may not be a writer,
but I can relate to its content.
Don't I seem intelligent?
Isn't it hard to work as a housekeeper?
No job in this world is easy.
We have it rough from birth,
so all we can do
is find our own fun in life.
Son, the same goes for you too.
No one hands it out for free.
-Honey?
-Oh.
All right.
Hae-na, the law school…
Well, you were a shoo-in.
But I'm still happy.
You're following the path
I have laid out for you.
Hae-hyo, you're following the path
your mom laid out,
which worries me but--
That's not how you give a toast.
It's supposed to be
a speech of celebration.
Let me do it instead.
It's rude to cut people off mid-sentence.
Know that she just
diminished my authority.
One's authority
can't be diminished by others,
so consider it intact.
See how sweet my creations are?
You mean, "our" creations.
That may be true, but you don't own us.
Do you have to draw the line like that?
We'll never think that we own you.
Just live your life well.
Congratulations
on getting into law school.
May you become someone who contributes
to the country and society.
Gosh, that's so dry.
I just want you guys to have fun
and enjoy your lives.
Don't worry even if things don't go well.
You have us. We'll always be by your side.
Both I and your dad.
Cheers.
We rarely do this
even though we live together.
Because we all have different schedules.
I'm against Gyeong-jun moving out.
You can't bring that up so abruptly.
Mom, why are you against it?
He's on salary. There's a limit
to how much money he can earn.
On top of the living expenses,
900,000 won on rent?
Then he'll never save any money.
We can't buy you an apartment,
but you can spend less
if you live with us.
Save enough money for a rent deposit.
You can move out then.
Mom, in the past 27 years of my life,
I've never had fun.
I just need to be responsible
for myself now as I'm single,
so I want to have fun.
Why must you move out to do that?
Are you uncomfortable around here?
Think about Hye-jun.
He needs his own room.
Sharing a room with Grandpa can't be nice.
You're talking as if I'm uncomfortable
sharing the room with Grandpa.
Say what you want to say,
but don't drag me into it.
You said that back in middle school.
Why bring that up now?
We fought since you didn't let me
use the computer.
-But it's true.
-No, it's not.
You put words in my mouth.
You're clouding the issue,
and you got me upset.
I never said I was uncomfortable
sharing the room with Grandpa.
You hurt Grandpa's feelings
and made me look bad.
-When did you get so eloquent?
-It's all thanks to you.
You always lecture me
using difficult words and all.
Why is it that you guys fight
every time you see each other?
You used to care a lot about each other.
I have to say, you're the problem.
How could you talk back
to your big brother like that?
All siblings are equal.
They ought to respect each other.
The young learn from the old.
Embrace and look after
your little brother.
You used to adore Yeong-gyun.
Why bring up Yeong-gyun now?
Because you talked about
how siblings should be.
Why aren't you eating, Father?
I have something to say too.
Gyeong-jun doesn't take after me.
I thought he did,
but I was wrong.
I think
Hye-jun got my looks,
and Yeong-nam got my personality.
Me? Dad!
You just don't know me well enough yet.
What? I've known you for over 50 years.
I used to be vain and pretentious,
but not anymore.
Gyeong-jun wants to move out
so he can live comfortably all by himself.
There was a time
when I wasn't at home much,
but it was never because I only cared
about my comfort and well-being.
I made a mistake because
I wasn't thoughtful and mature enough.
Grandpa.
I'm not moving out
so I can live comfortably.
If I move out, there will be more space
for everyone else,
which means all of you can live
in a better environment.
Hye-jun and I started fighting
because he kept invading my space
as he never had his own.
I couldn't control my emotions
during my adolescent years,
so we fought.
And we're still butting heads
because of the pent-up emotions
from that time.
This isn't anyone's fault.
Poverty is to blame.
Now, I can afford to move out.
And it will solve this problem.
Hye-jun and I will stop fighting.
That is why I arrived at this decision.
You really are our family's brain.
We started fighting
because I kept invading your space
and got you angry?
Jeez, you still don't know
what you did wrong.
We can talk later.
We should focus on the meeting now.
Why must you always rebel
against your older brother?
That's not what he's doing.
Gyeong-jun is all talk.
He's just trying to justify himself
wanting to move out.
I know because I've been duped
by punks like him many times.
They bewitch you with words
and make you believe them.
Grandpa, why are you doing this to me?
Because you're so unbelievably persuasive.
I am very proud of you. But you know what?
Con artists are extremely persuasive.
Dad, aren't you embarrassed?
Are you bragging about getting conned?
You sound very proud.
I already paid for everything.
What are you talking about? How?
By always putting up with you
talking down to me in front of everyone!
Hey.
There's no worse punishment
than having to put up
with your child
talking down to you all the time.
Oh, dear.
Grandpa.
If you want to move out, go ahead.
But the rent has to be lower,
around 300,000 to 400,000 won.
Why couldn't you have been like this
from the get-go?
-So?
-Mom said I can move out.
Gosh, what do we do, though?
Father heard everything we said.
What do we do? My gosh, what should I do?
What did I say?
I bet Grandpa feels
most betrayed by you, Mom.
Your words totally contradict
how you usually treat him.
Are you enjoying this or what?
Why take it out on me?
Grandpa was mean to me.
He basically called me selfish.
He was just stating the fact.
Honey, go apologize to Father.
Why should I?
Gosh, enough.
It happened years ago,
so stop holding a grudge.
I can't. It still makes me angry.
What can I do?
So you'll keep this up?
We're parents too.
What will the boys learn?
We never did them wrong.
I'm not like my dad.
Comparing Dad with him is insulting.
-Hye-jun.
-Yes?
I'm going to become a model.
You've made up your mind?
Yes. I'll become a successful model
and show your dad what his father can do.
You can do it.
I can do it!
You already got your spirits back up.
This is why I love you, Grandpa.
Your grandpa is a charming man,
you little rascal.
Could you give us a minute, Hye-jun?
Father, I'm sorry.
It's okay. People even bad-mouth the king
behind his back.
But you know,
Gyeong-jun really doesn't take after me.
Gyeong-jun takes after me.
Why would he take after his grandpa?
And I don't take after you.
Our personalities are very different.
Don't deny it.
Personality-wise, you're just like me.
-Gosh, you're driving me nuts.
-I just hope to win the lottery
-so that I can move out.
-Dad!
So I'm moving out.
You're happy about that, right?
I'm happy to finally have my own room.
Stop by my office sometime.
I'll buy you lunch.
Okay.
Hey.
I'm trying to be nice.
Shouldn't you bow down a little?
What do you mean?
Why should I?
-You little brat.
-What?
Want to punch me?
I won't let you punch me anymore.
I said I'm sorry.
That doesn't mean anything.
You really hold grudges.
I'll let it all go if you're good to me.
But you keep messing with me.
No, I'm just worried about you.
That's all.
We're in the same boat.
I don't buy it.
I think you always had it easier
than I did.
You had your own room.
NORMAL PERSON
NEW POST #AMOR FATI
#LOVE YOUR FATE
#NIETZSCHE #LIKE
#AMOR FATI
#LOVE YOUR FATE #NIETZSCHE #LIKE
These are all very popular classes.
LEGAL ENGLISH
LEGAL RESEARCH
Ready?
Ready for battle!
Five, four, three, two, one.
Now, go.
ENROLL
REQUEST ENROLLMENT
ENROLLMENT COMPLETED
-We did it!
-My gosh, it worked.
-It worked!
-We did it!
-We got in, right?
-It worked! Yes!
-We got in, right? Gosh!
-Nice!
-Are you happy?
-Yes.
I'll make you even happier.
Ta-da.
Look, there!
-Okay.
-What's okay?
I see the two stamps.
Okay, you just wait. Soon, I'll… You know?
Gosh, look at you all excited.
Gosh, even I'm nervous.
This scene has to turn out nicely.
Did you sleep well?
Yes, I did.
You don't seem nervous at all.
You look too calm.
I just kept thinking
about my character, Su-yeong.
Then he started talking to me.
You're a true actor now.
Your character is speaking to you.
That sounded very insincere.
It showed?
I don't really get it.
I mean, I'm not an actor.
Anyway, I'm happy to hear
that you're so immersed in your role.
I can't be on set today, so I was worried.
I can stop worrying.
What does Director Yoon want?
What do you think?
I bet he wants to give you a role.
His most recent movie
didn't do well at all.
Down and up, you know?
This time, it'll do well.
And guess what!
He seems to be very fond of you.
Don't you think things are going well
for you now that I'm your manager?
So you want credit. I like that.
Hey, Jeong-ha.
My jaw dropped.
Sa Hye-jun got changed.
What about it?
He looks like a prince.
You know what they say.
"The face completes the fashion."
I didn't know before,
but he's ridiculously handsome.
You didn't know all this time?
You do not have a good eye.
-I do.
-You don't.
Why are you here, Su-bin?
Shouldn't you be working?
Oh, I'm sorry.
At least you're saying sorry. You're not
making excuses like someone.
You must be thrilled
about visiting the set.
I'm going there to work.
Then I'll get back to work too.
Wait.
Yes?
Choose your side wisely.
Oh, don't worry.
I started working a year ago, so I know.
My gosh, you guys look so great together.
He'll beat me up today.
Why run off with my money to begin with?
Yes, Jin-seong deserves to get beaten up.
Why run off with someone else's money?
Su-yeong is a corporate heir,
but he's too violent.
Are you sure you can do it?
I can't even picture you hitting someone.
I can't do it, but Su-yeong can.
I don't feel confident.
-Aren't you heading out?
-Yes, in five minutes.
I see. What should I do?
Just watch the shoot and go home?
Well, I'm going to watch
Hye-jun's fight scene with Park Do-ha.
Then I'll go with you.
Gosh.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
No. Hand that over.
This is how you do it.
The chest, the stomach,
and the back. Hit him in that order.
Got it.
Do better. How many times
have we done this already?
I'm trying to make sure
you won't get hurt.
Stop. Look, Do-ha.
When he hits you in the chest
and stomach, respond accordingly.
I don't need to practice that.
I'll try that again.
Okay, go.
I'll finish it in one go.
That's how you do it. Hit him hard.
He's like a different person.
He's an actor indeed.
Was I like this too?
During my shoot earlier.
Yes, you looked like a real actor too.
Exhale.
Keep going. Get a nice stretch.
Now, the other way.
We'll go the other way.
Get a nice stretch.
The other arm.
Rotate your hips, making big circles.
If you're done warming up,
I'll now correct your postures.
-Good.
-Thank you.
-Relax your shoulders.
-Okay.
It's okay. It's very important
to be careful at the beginning.
Are you all right?
Hello.
-Sir!
I'm not a thug.
Why would I hit you with a stick?
Hey, that's not your line.
I'm sorry.
I don't know where that came from.
Jeez, it's so frustrating
to work with a total rookie.
Hye-jun.
Yes. I'm sorry, sir.
I actually like that.
Director, then the focus will be on him.
I'm the lead.
It'll only help your character shine more.
What were you going to do next?
Untying him
and punching the crap out of him
would make my character
look more ruthless.
You think so?
Let's try it. Can you guys untie him?
-Untie him.
-Okay.
Ouch, that hurts.
Do you want to try punching him once?
-Punch him?
-Give it a go.
Director, thank you for thinking
so highly of Hye-jun.
-We'll do our best.
-You know Lee Tae-su, right?
Of course. I used to work
for his company, you know.
He spoke very highly of Hye-jun.
So I looked him up,
and he's pretty good indeed.
Oh, I see.
Who's playing the lead character?
Jessica is our female lead.
And I'm in talks with Park Do-ha.
Jessica and Park Do-ha?
My, such huge names!
Did that hurt?
It did, you son of a bitch.
You're such a thug.
Thugs only inflict pain on others.
Compared to that, I'm incredibly humane.
I'm sharing this pain with you.
You know?
Don't be so cocky.
Without your parents, you're a nobody.
Are you okay?
-Let go.
-Hey, I'm sorry.
Let go.
That was intentional, wasn't it?
You did that to screw me over.
No, it was just a mistake.
Did it hurt a lot?
Let's take a break.
Are you sure this is better?
The director thinks that it is.
Directors aren't always right.
Director, I want to watch
what we shot just now.
-Why are you following me?
-I should see it too.
No, don't do anything.
You're getting on my nerves.
Take it out on me after the shoot.
Right now, let's work.
I don't even want to see you
after the shoot.
Gosh, I don't need this. Get this off me.
Backswing.
-And hit the ball.
-Look at that. Her arm is straight.
It looks easy, but…
Hello, sir.
What's up? You talked as if
you'd never see me again.
What brings you all the way here?
It's for your kids.
What's with you today?
I've realized that
you actually have a warm side.
I met Director Yoon.
He said you spoke highly of Hye-jun.
Thank you so much.
That's right. I did.
He's filming that movie with Do-ha,
and they'll also be in the same drama.
I'm pleasantly surprised by you.
You'll be a great manager.
My gosh!
-Come on.
-Really, I mean it.
Gosh, thank you for the compliment.
As someone with a lot more experience
in the industry,
please help me out and guide me.
Yes, I'll be sure to provide you
with guidance and help.
By the way,
I heard they're still shooting.
Do you know why?
Well, maybe Hye-jun's passion
moved the crew to tears.
What a nutjob.
Gosh, hey.
I can't believe I didn't know
that you were such a nutjob.
Same here. Even I didn't know.
I hope we get along well.
Sure thing.
NEW POST NORMAL PERSON
#FIGHT SCENE #JIN-SEONG #SU-YEONG
#TIRED OF WAITING #SORRY #I HAVE PLANS
HAEHYO_WON NORMAL PERSON
#FIGHT SCENE #JIN-SEONG #SU-YEONG
#TIRED OF WAITING #SORRY #I HAVE PLANS
Hey, you're bleeding!
-Cut.
-Cut!
-Keep this.
-Yes, sir.
Thank goodness
you don't have to go to the hospital.
I'm lucky.
You just like to think that.
HAPPINESS PHARMACY
Don't forget this.
MEDICINE
Keep it in your purse.
Give it to me later.
Aren't you headed home?
-I'll take you home.
-Why?
Gosh, it's okay. You will take me home?
You just got hurt.
Am I dying or what?
You're so dramatic.
I don't like that.
It's too heavy.
Are you all right?
You're okay.
You should've just gone straight home.
Why insist on taking me home?
I insisted?
Yes, you did.
I clearly told you to just go home.
Are you evading responsibility?
Responsibility for what?
I had nothing to do with your injury.
Why are you worked up?
Do you like people who are responsible?
Yes, I do.
So you want to be responsible too?
You sound a little crazy right now.
How did you know?
I think I'm a little crazy today.
Yes.
All the waiting must've tired you out.
I'm not tired.
But I've realized that
no job in this world is easy.
I was very excited today.
So excited that I couldn't even think
about anything.
Does it feel different when you're
the one living the moment
as opposed to just spectating it?
Probably?
Oh, it's raining.
Gosh, it's so weird.
Every time I'm with you, it rains.
You're right.
Why are you standing there? Run!
I want to get rained on.
You'll be cold.
You said you're a rational person.
-I feel like I'll explode.
-Let's take shelter first.
I'm conflicted.
There's something I want to say,
but I don't know if I should say it.
Well… When you're not sure
whether or not you should say something,
just don't say it.
I'll say it.
-To me?
-I think I like…
What?
I think I like you.
Subtitle translation by Won-hyang Son
RECORD OF YOUTH
How about a movie?
And being together right now
doesn't feel real, either.
He'll be in a mini-series.
Act like you know nothing
until he tells you first.
I will try to get in your way.
I don't deserve to be your manager.
A manager I can't get a hold of
is the worst.
Want to grab dinner together?
I have plans this evening
with Hye-jun.
Grandpa!
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs