RECORD OF YOUTH
THIS PROGRAM HAS BEEN SELECTED AS AN
"EXCELLENT BROADCAST CONTENT" AND IS SUPPORTED
BY THE MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS, TOURISM
AND THE KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
There's something I want to say,
but I don't know if I should say it.
Well…
When you're not sure, just don't say it.
I'll say it.
-To me?
-I think I like…
What?
I think I like you.
I knew this would happen.
Wait.
I have an umbrella at my place.
RECORD OF YOUTH
EPISODE 6
-All done?
-Yes.
I feel like I can totally count on you
when you fix these things.
So only when I'm good to you?
No, you can't really say that.
This is for the house.
Father hasn't even stepped out of the room
since his early dinner.
Maybe he went out.
Where would he go at this late hour?
Gosh. Oh, boy.
Why am I so tired?
Is it because I used the muscles
that I hadn't used for so long?
What time is it now?
Oh, boy.
Goodness.
Gosh, you startled me!
-You're here.
-Of course I'm here. Where would I go?
Did you go clubbing?
No.
Come on. I can see that you danced.
Honestly, you really don't know me at all.
Where are you going?
To get water. Want to tag along?
Dad, let me say this again.
I'll cut all ties with you
if you cause trouble again.
Trust me just this once.
I won't let you down.
So there's something. Am I right?
No!
There is. I'm sure of it.
Are you done?
Why are you so startled?
Well… Usually, the person who knocks
opens the door, you know.
But you opened it first.
I wasn't expecting it, so I was startled.
What an earnest answer.
-I don't like that.
-Then get out of my house.
Okay.
That's all you?
Yes, my dad drew them for me.
Is he an artist?
No, he teaches drawing classes
for beginners in Daejeon.
He also gives lectures
at cultural centers.
Can I see them?
Sure.
How old were you?
Just after my first birthday.
Here, I sense a certain vibe.
My mom got remarried around that time.
Do you know what's hard
when your parents get a divorce?
I'm not telling you.
Why ask if you weren't going to tell me?
I can't tell you so easily.
Besides, we're not that close yet.
All right. I should get going.
Are you upset?
No, why would I be?
We're not that close, you know.
-You are upset.
-No, I'm not.
-You are.
-Yes, I am upset.
It'd be overwhelming
to be bombarded with information.
I'll tell you everything,
little by little.
Can I take that as your answer
to my confession?
-"Confession"?
-I confessed my feelings to you earlier.
Hold on.
Just a moment.
"Confession"? I thought
I'd only hear that word in song lyrics.
Calm down.
Life isn't a song.
I'm happy with how things are now.
A new relationship
wouldn't be a good idea.
An Jeong-ha, you must resist this.
It's stopped raining.
Then I don't need to lend you my umbrella.
-Hi, Grandpa.
-Hey, why aren't you home yet?
I'm heading home now. What's up?
Hey, my teacher complimented me today.
Good job.
But I have to submit a photo.
They'll send it to an ad agency.
What was it called?
Something that starts with "pro" or "pri."
Gosh, what was it? I wrote it down.
-Portfolio?
-Yes, that's it!
Port… Gosh, why is it so hard?
Anyway, that's what I need.
Don't worry. I got it.
Just follow my instructions.
Okay. I've given you the latest update,
so I'm off to bed now.
All right, good night.
-I should get going.
-Okay.
What are you doing?
-Oh, I'll walk you out.
-Why?
I'll be left alone
if you just shut the door and leave.
But coming home alone is okay?
Yes, that's fine because I'm used to it.
No, I can't let you.
-Why not?
-Then why did I walk you home?
Why did you?
To make sure you get home safe.
I need to end that conversation.
I must firmly say no to him.
Then what's going to happen to us now?
I mean, we didn't finish
that conversation earlier.
You said we should take it slow.
Wasn't it your way of saying no?
No, I like you too.
Then what's after that "I like you too"?
I'm not sure. You tell me.
Dating.
I lost.
I'll do your grandpa's makeup
when he's taking photos for his portfolio.
Am I being too nosy?
No, I'd be grateful.
Then I'll do it.
Now that I'm no longer your fan,
I need someone else to obsess over.
A fan's greatest joy
is to watch them grow.
Do it if you want to.
Thanks.
I wonder if Jeong-ha stood there
until she could no longer see me.
I wanted to turn around, but didn't.
I should have, to lock eyes with her.
MIN-JAE
I heard you got hurt.
I'm at the cafe near your place.
I should've held on to our beginning
for a little longer.
At the time,
I didn't know we'd end up like this.
Hey, what is that?
Do you know how worried I've been?
Why didn't you tell me?
Have you seen a doctor yet?
You have too many questions.
My answer is, it's all good now.
Why did you come all the way here?
To see how bad the wound is
and tell you the good news in person.
I got the role?
Yes, you did. Isn't it amazing?
Things are happening for us.
It's a bit scary
because everything's going so well.
It's because you're a great manager.
By the way, where were you?
I have something to tell you.
I haven't told anyone yet.
WON HAE-HYO
Is it too late? I just wanted to check in.
Don't tell me you're still on the set.
I'm at home. Good night.
That's like, "Don't talk to me."
All right, good night.
Excuse me. Coming through.
-Take care of this for me.
-Sure.
-Thank you. Have a good day.
-Have a good day.
-Hello.
My gosh, look who's here.
You've gotten even more handsome.
Do you have yellow tulips?
Who is it for? Your girlfriend?
They're so beautiful.
The omelet is a little different today.
I put in some tofu and tuna.
I love it when you do this
whenever your dad is away for work.
I can rely on you.
This is the joy of having a son.
Mom, only his future wife
will benefit from all this.
This is good for all of us.
And he was good to me
even when he was dating his ex.
Well, you were fond of her too.
He might marry a girl you don't like.
That will not happen.
I'm worried about you.
Your taste is inconsistent.
-Hae-hyo, what about the syrup?
-Get it yourself.
You already did all this work.
Don't you want it to be perfect?
No, I don't.
That didn't work.
My dear brother, I want the syrup.
Get me the syrup!
Hey, don't do that. Jeez.
Hey, that was weird.
Why change the topic?
-What?
-Who'd date her?
I feel bad for that guy.
She's so self-centered.
But she's pretty.
And she comes from a good family.
She's perfect.
Gosh, cut it out.
Throw some ricotta cheese in your salad.
That has no protein.
Yes, ma'am.
Will you go straight to the shoot
from the hair salon?
Mom, you're really--
I'm your loyal, hardworking assistant.
More like a micromanager if you ask me.
Agreed.
You'd better behave yourself at the salon.
You have to take your career
to the next level.
Don't be the subject of gossip.
But what if I actually date her?
Then people will definitely gossip.
Son, I'm having a great morning.
You made breakfast
to put a smile on my face. Thank you.
I want to stay in this good mood
the whole morning, okay?
Amen.
You seem very excited these days.
-Me?
-I know who those flowers are for,
but just don't do it.
-Why not?
-Because then you'll have to date her.
You're getting too ahead of yourself.
She has to be on board.
Who'd reject you?
I don't want you to end up hurting her.
Congratulations.
You're officially a designer now.
Bring in lots of new clients.
I'll do my best.
And try to get along with Jin-ju.
Yes, I will.
I organized the brushes. Did you see?
I took a glance.
I'm sure you did a good job.
Let me see.
"Designer An Jeong-ha." So cool!
You two seem excited.
Su-bin, you've been promoted to assistant
because I approved it.
I'll do my best. I'll assist both of you
to the best of my ability.
"Both of you"?
Did you really clean this brush?
I've even disinfected it.
Did you use conditioner?
Sorry. I should've trained her better--
Oh, right. She told me to use it,
but I forgot. I'm sorry.
What is this?
Are you girls trying
to cover up for each other or what?
This is ridiculous.
-Go wash it again.
-Yup!
What?
"Yup"? Are you kidding me?
This is where you work.
Su-bin, you told me the other day
that I'm your favorite
and you'll be loyal to me.
Are you betraying me already?
Pardon? No, ma'am.
Right? You'd better keep your word.
Jeong-ha, I never said that.
I know.
I'll go bring another brush.
There's a clean one.
Hey, when did you get here?
Here.
What's this for?
I was getting flowers for my mom.
It smells so good.
-Do you like flowers?
-No.
I do, of course.
You looked sullen, but you're smiling now.
Did you get scolded again?
"Again"?
Do you think I get scolded every day?
I've officially been promoted to designer.
My gosh, that's awesome.
Gosh, talk about perfect timing.
I got the flowers to congratulate you.
It's too late to fool me.
Want to grab dinner together?
My treat, to congratulate you.
Oh, I have plans this evening.
With Hye-jun.
What? Is it a date?
No, not today. I'm helping his grandfather
with his portfolio.
"Not today"? So you two
will go on a date tomorrow?
Maybe?
You two… Seriously?
I was totally determined not to date him,
but I couldn't resist.
Am I doing the right thing, Hae-hyo?
This is already so interesting.
A while back, you said only chaos awaits
when fantasy meets reality.
You remember that?
I do.
Good for you. You can tease me about it
for a million years.
I just couldn't help it.
You'll date him for a million years?
Gosh, stop teasing me.
I wasn't teasing her.
JIN-U
-Hey.
-Come to the studio with your grandpa.
Just let me borrow the camera.
You can't go ahead
and let us use the studio.
I got my boss' permission.
Gosh, seriously.
You're so difficult
even when someone's offering help.
People like you really need help.
Thanks.
You motivate me
to open my own studio sooner.
You've saved up enough?
I'm not doing it with my own money.
I just need some help
from the bank and my dad.
Look at me eating this
even though I had breakfast.
You're such a good cook.
Gosh, I'm glad you like it.
-Maybe I'll do it again.
-Good.
This pancake goes really well
with makgeolli.
-You don't have any, right?
-I'd say no even if I did.
It's too early for alcohol.
Yeong-nam and I have to go to work.
You're so self-centered.
A little bit is fine. I never said
we should drink until we drop.
We just never see eye to eye.
Look at Yeong-nam.
He only says nice things.
He's not like that with me.
Of course, you wouldn't stay quiet
when someone's complimenting me.
I'm just stating a fact.
You scold me every single day.
Why did you bring that up?
They're fighting because of what you said.
No, we're not fighting.
Why stick your nose in and get told off?
He didn't get told off.
You two are truly a match made in heaven.
-No.
Fine, you're not.
My gosh, that's so pretty.
Oh, this? It's new.
It's a knockoff,
but it was still expensive.
You can afford to buy authentic stuff.
You're rich.
Gosh, had Father never lost all the money,
you wouldn't have had to sell the house.
I tell myself the money was never ours.
That way, I feel better.
Hi.
Oh, Hye-jun! It's been a while.
What happened to your face?
I got hurt during a shoot.
You even make that band-aid look so cool.
Dad, I need the car in the evening.
Where are you going?
Don't ask such a thing.
I'm sure he has stuff to do.
Hye-jun,
is Park Do-ha handsome even in real life?
Yes.
Can you get me his autograph?
I can't ask him because we're not close.
I guess he's arrogant
because he's super famous.
No, it's not that. Anyway, have fun.
See you.
No, rumor has it that he's very rude.
He and Lee Mun-jeong broke up
because he cheated.
With multiple girls, even.
You always talk about celebrities.
Do you have nothing better to do?
What? It's fun.
It's fun to even just look
at those good-looking people.
Talking about them is more fun.
Celebrities would rather be bad-mouthed
than not be talked about at all.
No way. Are they perverts?
Who likes to be bad-mouthed?
That's just what people say to lessen
their guilt about bad-mouthing them.
You guys, seriously… I'm upset.
Why are you all quiet?
Why aren't you taking my side?
Yeong-nam, we should get going.
Shall we?
Where are you going?
-I have a shift.
-You still work there?
You said you're filming a movie.
Are they not even paying you?
I'll get paid when the filming is done.
Must you talk like this to me
right before work?
That thing on your forehead
is making me angry.
Where's your grandpa?
If you notice anything odd,
tell me right away.
I can't let him cause trouble again.
Can't you let go of his past mistake?
People don't change.
You don't have a class today.
I came to practice.
If you over-practice right off the bat,
you'll get muscle cramps.
This isn't my first time
doing something with my body.
I used to dance, you know.
Oh, I knew it. You're flexible.
And I see some muscles too.
Also, my grandson
paid for my classes.
I should be doing it for him,
but he's taking care of me instead.
Oh, look at you
bragging about your grandson.
He'll even take photos of me today.
Hi, friend.
-I'm a customer today.
-Do you have a shoot?
No, a pre-shoot meeting.
-How many and what kind?
-I'll need ten.
And for the menu… Let me see.
I'll leave it up to you.
I like meat,
so I'll pick the ones with meat.
And one club sandwich for me.
Hey, are you all right?
Park Do-ha's name is trending.
That happens often enough.
A new music video?
"Park Do-ha, Americano."
"Park Do-ha, assault."
His name is everywhere.
This won't affect the movie
you guys are filming, will it?
I'm not sure.
You should ask Min-jae.
If bad stuff happens to him now,
it can't be good for the movie.
MIN-JAE
Another hardworking day.
It's scary, things are going too well.
Anyway, we got this!
Speak of the devil, and she shall appear.
She's such an amazing manager.
I even got a role in a mini-series.
Hye-jun, you're finally--
I'll pay for the sandwiches so that
you can brag a little to your boss.
-Okay. Congratulations.
-Thanks.
DIRECTOR YOON JI-HO
Why isn't he picking up?
-Hello, Min-jae.
-Hello, I'm just calling to say hi.
Don't hesitate to contact me
if you need anything.
Min-jae, why didn't you tell me?
-Pardon me?
-Sa Hye-jun.
I heard he betrayed Tae-su
to sign with you.
No, that's not true!
Where are you? Let's talk in person.
Forget it. I made a fool of myself.
Who said that?
I heard it from Tae-su.
Wait, Director--
Director!
Gosh, this bastard!
Darn it.
LEE TAE-SU
Pick up.
I said pick up.
Pick up!
LEE TAE-SU
HOURLY TRENDING KEYWORDS
PARK DO-HA ASSAULT
ASSAULT ALLEGATIONS
PARK DO-HA PUSHES A FAN
This obnoxious punk. Gosh, seriously…
What the hell?
-Don't worry.
-You couldn't tell them not to publish it?
I could've, had you told me. But
this already happened. I can sort it out.
How?
"Attack the messenger
if you can't attack the message."
Besides, the message itself is so wrong.
I mean, how was I supposed to know
that she was my fan?
She showed up and grabbed me.
I'll take care of it,
so calm down.
So what exactly are you going to do
to take care of it?
I've only known you
for a little while, right?
So how can I trust you?
You're just like me.
Of course you wouldn't trust me.
I totally get it.
But wouldn't it be better for you
to stay out of it?
If things go south,
it won't just end with me.
It'll affect you as well.
Are you sure you can sort it all out?
"The Next Park Do-ha"?
Change the headline.
Did you see his name trending today?
I know he has a solid fandom.
And with the K-wave,
he won't go down easily.
But I don't want Hae-hyo
to be associated with him.
Okay, fine.
We'll use him this time, but no more.
Has Hae-hyo left for the ad shoot?
All done?
Yes, I got everything.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
HYE-JUN
Is work going well!
Stop smiling, will you?
Can I make a quick phone call?
Hey, it's a text. Just text back.
-If you call, he'll be flustered.
-That's what I want.
I'm having a good day at work.
I'll see you at eight.
Why aren't you calling him?
He asked me if work was going well,
but he put an exclamation mark at the end.
Most people would put
a question mark, right?
What do you think this means?
He's convinced that
I must be doing a great job at work.
Why ask me if you were going
to answer the question yourself?
Oh, sorry.
You like him that much?
Yes, I do.
Let's go.
Come on.
I'm coming.
YEONGNAM REPAIR AND BUILDING
All right.
-Fasten your seat belt.
-Fastened.
Let's go!
My blood sugar's bottomed out.
So good.
Cut.
Can you get more of it on your lips
when you're eating it?
Sure.
Have you had too much of it?
No, it's fine. It's delicious.
I like that attitude. Okay.
Let's fix your makeup.
The makeup team!
Yes!
-You must be hot.
-Yes.
Thanks.
I guess your friend isn't coming.
She always keeps her promises.
JEONG-HA
Hey, Jeong-ha.
Gosh, I'm so sorry.
Tell him I said sorry.
It's okay. Don't come if you're busy.
Don't stress yourself out.
No, I'm done.
I can be there in 20 minutes.
Okay.
I'll give you a ride.
We're here.
Thank you.
Bye.
Back then, I chose friendship
over love without question.
But now,
I want to make a different choice.
I've still got a chance.
I'm so sorry that I'm late, sir.
That looks great.
Hye-jun, you're in the frame. Move back.
-Sorry. Better?
-Great.
My gosh.
-This one, we'll just…
-Wow.
-No.
-My gosh.
-You're in the frame again.
-What about this?
-Nice.
-Amazing.
Great. That's nice.
That's good, but take a step back.
Really? Okay. Let's do this.
Hye-jun, hold it,
so the light gets reflected.
-Hye-jun.
-Sorry.
-It's too long.
-Hye-jun.
Like this.
Hye-jun, fix his clothes.
There you go.
-No.
-Looking good.
-Grandpa.
-Is it long?
That's too long.
-Yes.
-Make it short.
-Jeong-ha, fix his clothes.
-Okay.
It'd be nice if we all could drink.
But you guys have to drive. What a shame.
Let's drink next time.
There's always tomorrow.
No. When you're my age,
it wouldn't be weird
if I were to die tomorrow.
Grandpa, you just killed the mood.
You should sing.
Hey. You can't ask your elder to sing.
Wait. Why not? Sing, please.
That's enough.
Why would he sing here?
Come on, man. I was just joking.
Why are you so serious?
We're here to have fun,
not to get serious.
I was joking, too.
-Really?
-Come on.
-Seriously?
-Sorry.
Okay.
-Gosh.
You guys are so beautiful.
Sir, let's raise our glasses.
You'll make a toast, right?
Before I do that,
I would like to thank you guys first.
Today,
I learned a lot from you guys.
When I was 20,
I wasn't as smart as you.
But I gave birth to my son.
That's the best thing I've done in my life
because my son gave me Hye-jun.
After meeting Hye-jun,
I met Jin-u
and Jeong-ha.
That's why I feel elated today.
And I am very envious of you.
And…
thank you for adoring me.
Thank you so much for that, too.
All right. Cheers.
Oh, right. There's one more occasion
for us to celebrate.
Hye-jun got cast for a mini-series drama.
It's too early to tell.
I haven't met the director yet.
Min-jae said you got it.
Then, you have the role.
Hey, that's great news.
Here's my toast to my life.
Thank you.
-Thank you. All right.
-Thank you.
That hits the spot.
-Grandpa, have some.
-Okay.
You should have some, Hye-jun.
-You should eat, sir.
-You should eat.
You should eat, Grandpa.
You can check every corner.
I've been hiding this listing
for my close friend of mine.
It's 400,000 won a month?
It is cheap.
Not bad.
It's better than "not bad." It's great.
So no mortgage on the house?
Gosh, you don't trust me.
No one will ever try to con you.
Do you have the copy of register
and the POA, right?
-Of course. Take a seat.
-Okay.
The POA from the property owner.
Here's the authentication of the seal.
I should sign the contract
directly with the property owner.
If you don't trust me, don't sign it.
-I have people waiting for this listing.
-Gosh.
-I didn't say I won't sign.
-Come on.
I like smart people, you know.
You work at a bank,
so I put in a good word for you.
All right. Look at this.
Here's today's date
on the copy of the title register.
The title was transferred to the current
owner, Kwon Nam-hui. You see it, right?
And you can see that
the owner paid off all the mortgage.
So no mortgage on the house.
-Right.
-Will you sign then?
Yes.
TOP TEN TRENDING KEYWORDS
PARK DO-HA ASSAULT
USED EXCESSIVE FORCE
POSSIBLY ASSAULTED HIS FAN
PARK DO-HA PUSHES OVER A FAN
I FEEL BAD FOR DO-HA
THAT STUPID FAN IS TO BLAME
DON'T BADMOUTH DO-HA
WHY GRAB HIM WHEN HE SAID NO
DON'T ACT LIKE YOU'RE THE VICTIM
DON'T MAKE DO-HA A BAD PERSON
THAT FAN IS A CRAZY BITCH
I WOULD'VE PUNCHED HER IF I WERE HIM
YOU DON'T DESERVE TO BE HIS FAN
WHAT ABOUT PARK DO-HA?
HE'S ENDURED MENTAL ABUSE
IT'S SO HARD TO BE A CELEBRITY
HE CAME OUT FOR COFFEE
The articles are all under control now.
My gosh, you're amazing, sir.
Let's send some gifts to the journalists
who wrote
these articles today.
Why?
Do you know how a traveler takes off his
clothes in a story from Aesop's Fables?
If you get hot,
you take your clothes off
even when you're told not to.
Okay.
You didn't get it, did you?
-No.
-That's why you must learn from me.
Then, I'll help you set up
your own agency.
Okay. I'll do my best.
Go pick up Do-ha. I'm leaving now.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Lee!
Hello.
-Why won't you answer my calls?
-I've been busy.
I had to handle Do-ha's articles.
I thought you'd changed
because you're a director
at a big company, making good money now.
It's not like I came to you for a favor.
I see. You met with Mr. Yoon.
That's how you found out
that I blew the chance for Hye-jun.
Why did you do it?
You wanted me to teach you as your senior.
That's what I did.
What lesson I should learn here?
You need to get used to this
if you want to make a rookie popular.
In this industry, there's a truckful
of people who backstab you.
I gave you a sneak peek.
I know you're grateful.
I'm so grateful that I might cry.
No. You should be crying blood.
If there's anything I can do
to get in your way, I will.
Why?
Because both of you left me.
You were the one who caused it.
Oh, right.
Did you tell Hye-jun that he was cast?
You must tell him that he's not anymore.
Too bad.
That's what I was going for.
Making you two suffer.
Hey! You…
You…
Don't call yourself a human being.
That's right. Now we're talking.
You're finally learning.
Agents aren't human.
We're a different species.
So we speak a different language.
JEONG-HA
We congratulated Hye-jun
on getting cast in the drama
It would have been more fun
if you were here with us.
-It's the same room, right?
-Yes, I set it up there.
Make sure no one sees him.
Yes. I'll make sure of it.
Let's talk now.
What did you do?
There are two ways
in stopping such articles.
One is manipulating comments.
The other is publishing other articles.
It's a diversion mechanism.
Now, do you trust me?
Well,
you're not so bad.
People like us
who don't trust people easily
can only trust numbers in the end.
The numbers for likes and dislikes.
If you want people on your side,
you fix the numbers to your advantage.
You're smarter than I thought.
I was born in 1977, the year of the snake.
You can call me by my name.
Okay.
Tae-su.
We live in such a great world.
Let's live for 1,000 years.
Let's live long!
Did you guys already get started?
Don't make me sad now.
-Of course not.
-Sir.
-Not until you get here.
-I missed you.
-Come on in. Hurry inside.
-Have you been well?
-I missed you.
-I missed you, too.
All right.
Thank you. Okay.
-Get home safely.
-Okay.
-Good night.
Isn't that Jin-u's car?
Why did he give you a ride?
What's up with your outfit?
You're not young anymore.
What about it?
I look good. That's all I need.
You're late, Father.
Did you have a drink, Father?
I literally had only one drink.
How did you know?
Were you with Father?
No. We met in front of the house.
Where's Hye-jun? You went out with him.
He's young and busy, unlike me.
Hye-jun will be in a drama.
It's a mini-series drama or something.
That's great!
Really?
Be good to him.
Don't let him resent you later.
I don't deserve resentment.
I just scold him for his own good.
-Gosh, this guy.
-Goodness.
It feels surreal
that you're driving this truck.
Why do you feel that?
Your existence is just surreal.
And being together right now
doesn't feel real, either.
Can I take a photo?
I want to record this moment.
All right.
One, two, three.
I'll make you feel this is real.
How about a movie?
Sure. Let's watch a movie
nominated for the Academy Awards.
-What are you doing?
-To walk you home.
Gosh, there's no need.
He never listens to me.
Did you notice it?
It's not raining.
When it rains, I'll think of someone.
Who?
Should I answer it or not?
When you're not sure,
you should answer it.
I won't.
Go inside.
-After you go.
-No.
I'll see you go in.
I can't ever win, can I?
-Oh, hey.
-Hi.
Did you eat?
I never skip my meals.
Three meals a day. You?
I always eat them, too.
Even if I don't eat much.
I wasn't sure eating popcorn this early
-would be good.
-I'm glad you got it.
It's caramel popcorn.
I like caramel popcorn.
Do you not like it?
That's the best kind.
Why isn't it starting? What time is it?
I'll tell you.
It's 6:55 a.m.
It's a watch for blind people.
I can tell time by touch.
I've never seen one.
This is for the minute.
And this is for the hour.
Do you want to try it?
I want to live a life
that teaches me how others feel.
And this watch is one of my attempts.
Here.
It's 7 a.m.
CALLS
HYE-JUN
I really need to tell Hye-jun.
The longer I hesitate, the worse it is.
Yes.
I've decided.
I'll go back to sleep.
REMEMBER TO GET VACCINATED
FOR CERVICAL CANCER
Today is the day.
I've got three stamps.
Look at you all glowing.
Doesn't my skin look dry? I woke up early.
I watched a movie with Jeong-ha at 7 a.m.
She has to work in the morning.
Are you kidding me?
If that's dry skin, I wish
I had your dry skin all year round.
-When did it start with Jeong-ha?
-I know you have a girlfriend.
Why can't you tell me?
I really want to tell you, too.
I really want to tell you, but…
This is driving me crazy.
-Don't tell me.
-Why not?
I don't want your pain.
Darn you.
You.
Me or Jeong-ha? Choose one.
Jeong-ha.
I'm a fool for expecting loyalty from men.
-What about you?
-I'd choose Hae-na.
Hey!
Have you gone mad? She's like your sister.
-Don't tell him.
-Don't tell him I knew when he finds out.
So this is the portfolio, right?
There are two.
He can keep one of them.
Thanks.
You'll make a polite corpse.
-I will die?
-Probably. Hae-hyo will kill you.
-Hey.
-Hi.
Where are we going?
I don't want to go to a hotel.
What about a pension house?
I don't like it either.
Hae-na.
-We don't have to go if you don't want to.
-We should go. I made a promise.
I always keep my promises.
Don't change your mind.
Let's go.
That must be the one.
Right here.
-You can't even open it?
-I haven't been here a lot.
Let me do it. I've been here a lot.
-What?
-With my family.
With your family.
I LOVE YOU, HAE-NA
This is so childish.
Didn't you know I was childish?
Isn't that why you like me?
Right. I like you
because you're not on my level.
Shall we drink champagne first?
-No.
-No?
Then, what do you want to do first?
I'm very goal-oriented.
We came here to achieve a goal.
I've seen you ever since you were a kid.
I don't think this is right.
It's like I'm violating you.
You're still a kid.
Let's wait a bit longer.
Let's have fun here. We can drink this
-and watch a drama.
-You asshole!
How could you call me that?
You're not my brother!
Are we blood-related?
-Hae-na.
-Do you know
how long I have been waiting for this day?
Okay, fine.
-Let's do it. I can do it.
-What?
I don't want to anymore.
Hae-na, I'm sorry.
Let go of me.
You're not my brother,
but a loser who can't grab his chance.
Isn't it exhausting, Grandpa?
Don't overexert yourself.
I'm not.
Besides, I'm enjoying it.
Here's your portfolio.
What?
And keep this one as a memento.
I look good.
-You look dashing.
-Really?
Gosh, look at how handsome I am.
Grandpa, dinner's ready!
Hye-jun, let's hide it.
Okay.
Mom, the side dishes look divine.
Hye-jun was cast in a drama series.
His career must finally be taking off.
I'm thrilled.
-Thanks.
-You're in a drama series?
-Which network?
-I don't know yet.
You got cast,
but you don't even know that?
That's for his manager to handle.
The actor can know later on.
The apartment you rented
seems too cheap for the neighborhood.
Are you sure it's decent?
Dad, don't you know who I am?
I managed to score a good deal
thanks to all the hunting I did.
I trust you, of course.
You're never the one to disappoint.
So you're moving next weekend.
Will you call a moving service?
You should help him.
All the appliances are there anyway
and he doesn't have a lot of stuff.
I can't that day. I have to work.
Then I'll help.
Why? It'll only be exhausting.
I'll do it.
But you're busy. Don't you have to film?
We've yet to do the read-through.
Even though the house is full of men,
you're the only one offering to help me.
Mom,
that was distasteful.
You made us look bad by complimenting him.
You and your way with words.
Enjoy. I made it for you, you know.
After dinner,
tell me all about your new series
including the director and writer.
The number you've dialed is currently
unavailable. Please leave a voice message.
MIN-JAE
The number you've dialed is currently
unavailable. Please leave a--
Just you wait, Yeong-nam.
Your dad is on his way!
MIN-JAE
I'm sorry.
You should fire me.
I thought about it and…
I don't deserve to be your manager.
I'm clumsy, moody,
and nosy.
And good at self-criticism.
Will I ever be able to
be of any help to you?
The premise is wrong.
I believe people should work for their
own sake, not someone else's sake.
-I know.
-They all say they do.
Not doing as you know
is worse than ignorance.
I would've stopped you
had I known that Mr. Lee was involved.
I didn't take this seriously enough.
I'm not the one who got you
the movie, either.
I'm useless.
At least it served as a teaching moment.
Everything comes with a cost.
Thanks for saying that.
You're quite admirable, though.
How can you be so calm?
This isn't my first time,
so I know how to handle it.
What pisses me off is that--
Even though I apologized?
People make mistakes and do wrong things.
What I hate is how you dodged me.
A manager I can't get a hold of
is the worst.
Are you scolding me now?
How can you tell me to fire you?
That should come last.
It was a joke.
Or maybe you took
this industry too lightly.
Min-jae,
I don't have much time left.
Sometimes,
my laughter isn't real.
CATCH
It just isn't compelling enough.
Why is Hae-hyo
only getting these lousy offers?
Yoon Ji-ho is the director,
and everyone's grabbing at it now.
He already failed twice,
and the writer is a newbie.
This is a gamble for Hae-hyo.
He's not exactly in the position
to pick and choose.
So all you bring him
is a small supporting role?
Are you people kidding me?
Signing with a big agency
was all for nothing.
I'm the one who snagged
Director Choi's movie,
but you people still took 50 percent.
Anyway, unless you bring him
something worthy,
he won't renew his contract.
Let's go.
What a nice sight.
You look like her subordinate.
Jeez.
I'm exhausted.
It's like I'm doing all the work.
What will Hye-jun be up to
after the movie?
A mini-series.
That's great. Which show is it?
It's called Catch.
What?
This one?
CATCH
Is Hae-hyo in the series too?
He's thinking about it.
I didn't hear about Hye-jun, though.
-Are you sure?
-Of course.
The leading role hasn't been cast yet,
but Hye-jun already signed on?
I guess the supporting actors
could get cast first.
That's rarely the case.
Some even get cut after the read-through.
Is she saying he'll get cut?
Hey, I wanted to ask you something.
Has Hye-jun been cast in Catch?
Right.
Okay, got it.
What was the answer?
It's news to them.
I wonder why he said
he got the part though.
That's probably what he was told.
Hye-jun will be so disappointed.
Act like you know nothing
until he tells you first.
B: NON-FICTION, ESSAYS
"HOW SIMPLE AND FRUGAL
A THING IS HAPPINESS"
Boy, this is hard.
Hold on.
I should practice somewhere more spacious.
All right.
Lower the shoulders
and straighten the chest.
Here I go.
Sorry, I'm late. You must be hungry.
No, it's fine.
I'll be right out!
Grandpa, what are you doing?
Oh, it's nothing.
You're home early today.
I always come at this hour.
Is that so? I see.
Grandpa!
Grandpa?
Mom!
-Father?
-Grandpa!
Father?
-Call an ambulance.
-Father!
Grandpa!
Let me see.
Father might have to stay a few days,
so pack a bag for him.
All right.
Got it.
There.
And this.
I guess these are enough.
Will he need his pacemaker ID card?
SA MIN-GI
What's this?
Unbelievable.
Grandpa, I saw that.
-Did you?
-Are you all right, Father?
Oh, well…
How can you be? You just collapsed.
You're finally up.
He just woke up.
You can go home
once the IV drip is emptied.
What caused this though?
Was it his heart?
It would've been a lot worse
had it been his heart.
He's probably exhausted.
-Exhausted?
-What?
Why were you in there?
What's this?
I got him into a modeling academy.
Instead of stopping him,
you encouraged him?
Do my words mean nothing to you?
Do they?
Grandpa wanted to work
so that he could help you.
That's why I did it.
So you got him hooked on a silly dream
like yours?
This is why I can never
stop worrying about you!
I gave up on going to college
because of Gyeong-jun.
I believed that one of us had to
since the tuition
was too much for you to bear.
I never asked that of you!
Gyeong-jun got good grades,
so I figured I had to.
My dream doesn't require a degree anyway.
Isn't that realistic enough?
Why can't you see the sacrifice I made?
Are you seeking credit?
You quit because you wanted to,
so who are you blaming?
This is why I call you a menace.
You're just like your grandpa!
How's that a bad thing?
It's way better than being like you.
You darn brat!
Did you just hit me?
Damn it.
JEONG-HA
Hi, Jeong-ha.
Did you catch a cold?
No.
You sound like you have a cold.
I'm glad you don't though.
I'm bored.
Want to hang out with me?
Sure.
This place is awesome.
You know a lot of nice places.
I come here when I'm depressed.
Were you depressed?
Yes,
but I'm not when I'm with you.
I'm like your personal
anti-depressant then,
so pay up.
-For real?
-Yes.
That's great. This is a lot though.
I'm expecting the change.
I'm keeping it.
Yes, free money!
Hey.
Jeez, you're fast.
Gosh.
You should keep it.
-Really?
-Yes.
This place is really nice.
There's a piano!
As kids, weren't we all forced by our moms
to take piano lessons?
No.
You know how to play.
I taught myself, actually.
That's how I learned most things.
-So are you saying you're a genius?
-No, just poor.
Can you play this?
Something magical happens
when you fall in love with a woman.
That was cool.
This particular woman has a name.
An Jeong-ha.
Searching for the stars
Sparkling in the night sky
I see your eyes blinking
Oh, how beautiful they are
I finally take the steps
After hesitating over and over again
And I will never forget
How you held my hand
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi
RECORD OF YOUTH
I'm grateful to have you by my side
right now.
Hello, Mother.
Hey, don't be startled.
I just wanted to live alone and feel free.
Forget about my duty as the eldest son.
What have you ever done
for the family as the eldest son?
-Mom.
-Shut it!
What do people think of me here?
I'll not let you have it your way.
He wants a model-turned-actor.
I finish once I start something.
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs