RECORD OF YOUTH
THIS PROGRAM HAS BEEN SELECTED AS AN
"EXCELLENT BROADCAST CONTENT" AND IS SUPPORTED
BY THE MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS, TOURISM
AND THE KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
Aren't you going to answer it?
HYE-JUN
Then we'll have less time to talk.
I have a client.
-I'll get straight to the point, then.
-Yes, I'd like that.
By the way, your makeup is excellent.
I didn't even do much today.
And you look this good?
Then with a little more makeup,
you'll look stunning.
Of course, you're already pretty.
Thank you.
Peach eyeshadow will look lovely on you.
Today won't work, but come and
get your makeup done some other day.
Are you trying to make me your client?
Come. I'll give you
a ten-percent discount.
How long have you and Hye-jun been dating?
We're not dating.
We have photos of him leaving your place.
Is this an official interview?
Yes, it is.
Then you'd have to record
this conversation,
so I'll do it for you.
We shouldn't go back on what we said
here today, right?
Sa Hye-jun is one of my celebrity clients.
But we're the same age,
so I admit that he often treats me
like a friend.
RECORD OF YOUTH
EPISODE 15
"Actor Sa Hye-jun
and makeup artist A
are not dating.
Sa Hye-jun's makeup artist…"
GYEONG-JUN
-Hello, Gyeong-jun.
-Hello, Ms. Lee.
Couldn't you prevent this article?
I denied it,
but they went ahead and published it.
Okay, but it's your job to sort this out.
All right, I will get on it.
-I have so much to do--
-I wrote the letter.
Really?
I wrote it thinking that
I was apologizing to myself.
I wronged myself on so many occasions.
-What's he saying?
-What? Pardon?
Nothing. I'll pass it along to the lawyer.
All right.
Gosh, he's like
an overbearing mother-in-law.
"They have been working together for…"
LEE TAE-SU
What now?
Yes.
I saw the article about Hye-jun.
Why hasn't there been a rebuttal yet?
Gosh, seriously. Mind your own business.
This is my business.
I'll sign with Hye-jun.
Take good care of him
until he signs with me.
You must think I'm a joke for you
to tell me that you'll steal him from me.
You have to keep saying it aloud
to make it happen
even though
it seems practically impossible.
Hurry up and release a rebuttal.
The sooner you do it,
the better it will be for you.
I have to ask Hye-jun.
If you ask him,
he'll say he'll just go public with it.
You know very well.
Ms. Kim said she's working on a story
that's even more scandalous.
Don't think this will be easy.
CONFESSION
Is it about my boyfriend?
Yes, it is.
You were going to confess
that you're his girlfriend
but you couldn't
because Jung Ji-a beat you to it.
I just wanted to thank my subscribers.
I'm on your side, Jeong-ha.
Sa Hye-jun has changed
since he blew up, didn't he?
I mean, his status has changed.
Hye-jun isn't like that.
Why are you so protective of him?
Why are you trying to turn me
into a woman who was dumped?
When I interviewed Jung Ji-a,
I could tell that
she still wasn't over him.
She agreed to reveal her name and face
because she still loves him very much.
Those two are on the same level now.
Everyone around them will be happy
if they get back together.
I see that you're a skilled interviewer.
I am definitely offended,
and you're making me want
to say bad stuff about Hye-jun.
Next time, book an appointment first.
I can help you improve
your public image as well.
HYE-JUN
-Hey.
-What are you up to?
Going to my Pilates class.
Aren't you seeing Jeong-ha?
We couldn't meet up,
so I was wondering if you were free.
Am I her stand-in?
Do you think you can be her stand-in?
Cut it out, will you?
SA HYE-JUN DENIES DATING RUMORS
You come here too?
I guess you really are a hotshot now.
You haven't changed at all.
So this is still your indicator
for judging success.
Yes, I'm still the same.
Do you think you're any different?
I never claimed to be.
Do you remember when we first met?
You were such a show-off that I thought
you were different from me.
I bet you can relate to me now.
you had that article published in no time,
denying your relationship with Jeong-ha.
An article?
Of course.
You should say that your manager did it
without telling you.
You're a fast learner, Hye-jun.
-You didn't get changed.
-I have to go to JJamppong.
Isn't it your day off?
Didn't you see the article?
Must I bring it up?
I have nothing to say about it.
-What did Jeong-ha say?
-I can't reach her.
Did you release that without telling her?
I have to find that out,
but Min-jae isn't picking up.
I stopped by to say hello
because it's been a while.
I'm so anxious these days.
What will the management say?
They've been quiet so far.
His quick rise to stardom
has caused a lot of jealousy and rumors.
There are too many dating rumors
and too many scandalous gossip.
We signed with him because of
his upright image.
Please, handle the media better.
I'm worried that
all these scathing articles about him
would damage the company's public image.
That won't happen.
We sued them for defamation.
Hi.
Hi, my foot.
I'm not in the mood to say hi to you.
I guess you don't want to lose
the advertisements.
I see that you've turned
into a total money-grubber.
Good. You're a true manager now.
They trusted Hye-jun to be
the face of their brand,
so I didn't want to trouble them.
It's not about money.
What brings you by?
If Hye-jun loses the contract,
Do-ha should get it.
Park Do-ha, a man of sound body and mind.
Are you deliberately trying
to sabotage him?
Then why do you even want to
manage Hye-jun?
Because he's proven himself as a star.
And all the rumors about him are false.
His momentum can't be stopped.
I'm saying that I'll help him
get back up if he falls.
How very thoughtful.
I can hire you at our company too.
You can't do this alone.
Has he renewed his contract?
I guess he hasn't. See? I told you.
They all think it was all their doing.
Why do you think I ended up like this?
Trust, faith, love?
At the end of the day,
it's all bullshit if you have no money.
You keep believing that.
I'll go my own way.
Do you think
he'll recognize your hard work?
Does he know you're here?
I bet you released the rebuttal
without asking him.
Your relationship will be cracking soon.
What you're hoping for will not happen.
We're very tight.
Why did you release the article
without telling me?
A rebuttal has to be released quickly.
-The sooner the better.
-Fine.
Let's forget about what I think
for a second.
Did you give Jeong-ha the heads-up?
Jeong-ha will understand.
She's very clever.
I don't want her privacy
to be infringed upon because of me.
I know that.
But I need to do my job too.
As your manager,
my priority is to protect you.
I get what you're saying.
But to me,
protecting Jeong-ha comes first.
NEW COMMENT
WAKE UP.
TO HIM, YOU'RE JUST ONE OF THE GIRLS.
WHY MAKE A MOVE ON HIM
WHEN YOU SHOULD BE WORKING?
YOU NEED A REALITY CHECK
YOU'RE NOT GOOD ENOUGH FOR HIM
MOM
Hey, Hae-hyo.
I saw Hye-jun.
He said he couldn't reach you.
-I'm going to call him.
-Where are you now?
-Home.
-Why are you home already?
My mom's coming.
You answered my call.
Why didn't you pick up Hye-jun's?
-You're asking that now?
-You shouldn't have picked up.
Then I would've come over, all worried.
-You're a great friend.
-Did you just realize that?
Why do people apologize to each other
when they're in love?
Maybe because
they want to do better but can't.
They can try and be better. Why apologize?
I'll never apologize for that reason.
HYE-JUN
"I'll never say sorry."
He couldn't keep his word.
Back then, we thought love was simple.
Love encompasses all sorts of emotions.
The First Human is about a feud between
third-generation conglomerate heirs
over their family business
and also about romance.
-You've done a number of romance dramas.
-He sounds so natural.
-This made me curious about you
-So different from when he's home.
-and your co-star, Jin Seo-u.
-That's why he made it.
-The shoot hasn't begun yet,
-What?
-but Seo-u and I have been friends…
-He's made it big.
Yes. It's good to see you
finally admitting it.
What's going on with the lawsuits?
I wanted to ask him earlier.
Ms. Lee will tell us
when it's all sorted out.
Like Gyeong-jun said, I wouldn't
be worried if it was a big agency.
Will she be able to manage?
I'm worried too.
Father! Where are you going?
I have a meeting at the academy.
-Honey, get going.
-What do you mean?
-Father's heading out.
-So what?
Come on. Give him a ride.
Are you going to take his side?
The business is slow, I guess?
I think Yeong-nam is stressed,
although he's trying to hide it.
I'll just say it!
It's not that. He was told
he shouldn't use his shoulders.
Jang-man's been working
without him for a while.
Father is getting old, you know.
You'll regret this later on.
If my parents were still alive,
I'd be so good to them.
You still have a chance.
What if he keeps expecting me
to be his driver?
-I'm fine with that.
-I need to continue my work.
It's okay. I'm working.
I make enough
to cover our living expenses.
Hurry up. I'll be late.
Gosh.
-Here.
-Thank you.
It looks like your son
really is your manager now.
What about your work?
I'll figure that out.
Why did you want to see my father today?
So you're not actually his manager, right?
This isn't about work.
We'd like an exclusive contract with you.
An exclusive contract?
What does that entail?
You'll only work with us.
But we'll take great care of you.
He already gets work through you guys.
What's different?
Here's the contract.
You read it over.
The most important part is
that it'll be a 60-40 split.
We'll give him all the support he needs.
You no longer need to neglect your job
and follow Mr. Sa around.
What will happen
if I don't sign this contract?
Then we'll just keep doing
what we're doing now.
I'll just do that, then.
I want to keep my son as my manager.
You can't compare our management
to the work your son's doing for you.
-We're professionals.
-I feel more comfortable with my son.
Let's go. Call me if there's work.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Why would I interrupt
when my father's talking?
Hey, I'm surprised
you can say stuff like that.
Stuff like what?
You're talking like an obedient son.
I'm going to try from now on.
-Should I stop?
-It's not that.
It's just scary because it's so sudden.
You scared me the other day too.
Gosh! There you go again.
Okay, fine. I heard you.
-Be quiet, please.
-Well said. Be quiet.
-Can we listen to some music?
-Sure.
Can you put it on for me?
Jeez.
HYE-JUN
Hey, Hye-jun.
"Hey, Hye-jun"?
I was worried but you sound cheerful.
-Is this intentional?
-You sound aggressive.
I'm sorry I stood you up.
-Where are you?
-Home.
Should I come over?
That's my mom. Talk about bad timing.
Right, you said your mom was coming.
Today's just not my day, it seems.
Right.
Go get the door.
I'm coming.
What is this?
What do you think?
I'm going to stay with you for a few days.
Tell everyone food is ready.
I took the day off today.
I'm supposed to be resting,
but I keep setting the table.
You have to set the table to eat.
You've had it too easy until now.
The table is set. What's Hye-jun doing?
Can't you even come and eat?
Where is this soybean paste from?
It's not store-bought.
Dad sent it to me.
So this is how he got you?
What are you talking about? He's my dad.
I went through so much to raise you,
but you seem to care more about your dad.
What's with that suitcase?
Let me stay for a few days.
By the way, he's a real catch.
What do you mean?
I was wondering why you quit your job
to work at a salon.
Was it because of Sa Hye-jun?
-What are you talking about?
-I read the article.
You really are my daughter.
I knew a smart girl like you wouldn't
quit your job without a solid plan.
-I misunderstood your intentions.
-Mom!
Da-on is a huge fan of his.
Can you get his autograph?
I'm sure he'll do it
for his girlfriend's brother.
I work with him,
so I can ask him for an autograph.
But I won't.
If I get you one,
your imagination will run wild.
It's so nice to have lunch and dinner
with all of you.
Only because it happens rarely.
You wouldn't want to cook
if this happened every day.
Why are you always so negative?
He just doesn't want his mom overworked.
Dad, you've finally come to your senses.
I am Sa Gyeong-jun! Your eldest son.
Tell Jeong-ha to come over for dinner
this weekend.
I'll cook something nice.
Sounds good. I'll ask her.
Is it a good idea for her
to have dinner with us now?
-What do you mean?
-She--
Don't.
Okay.
Does he have something on you?
It's so unlike you
to back down right away.
I guess he's finally grown up.
There's a lot of growing up going on
in the family. That includes you, Father.
People don't change.
I was mature to begin with.
You just didn't know it.
Thank you, Father.
For what?
Thanks to you,
Yeong-nam is working as your agent.
Gosh, you're overreacting.
He has no work at the moment anyway.
But I wonder if Dad
can actually work as an agent.
Why can't I?
An agent should know
what their client is thinking.
You need to figure out what
your client needs and get it done.
I'm good at that.
-You?
I really am.
-Sure, just eat.
-Let's eat.
Hey.
What's going on?
Ms. Lee said she'd sue them,
but I haven't heard from her.
It'll take some time.
Is that all? Give me the details.
I have nothing to tell you.
Hye-jun seems amicable
and doesn't seem to hold grudges,
but he can be really stubborn at times.
Like that's going to change anything.
Are you holding a grudge against me?
No.
I said those things because--
You trampled on my pride
so I could do better.
I understand.
Then why would you say
that I trampled on your pride?
-What is that about?
-What do you think?
I'm saying I know you very well.
Can I go to my room now?
Go.
He's still holding that against me.
Of course he is. Even I still remember it.
I shouldn't expect him to get over it.
-Did you eat?
-Yes.
-With who?
-By myself.
-Don't you have anyone to eat with?
-It's not that.
Hey.
I'm trying to reach out to you.
I thought you did all those things
out of love,
but I was wrong.
You care a lot more about your life.
Whether I'm hurt or not,
you just want your life to be fabulous.
You say that because you think
your life is separate from mine.
If I live a fabulous life, so will you.
It goes both ways.
Is it wrong that I think of you
as I do for myself?
You and I are different.
We have different upbringings.
-Why would you think we're the same?
-I love you like I love myself,
so I want to make sure
you shine the brightest.
That's what I decided to do
even before you were born.
That won't work anymore.
Why are you so startled?
You always try to hit me.
It doesn't even hurt.
That's not the point.
It instills fear in me.
Do you actually feel fear?
Seriously, what is going on with the kids?
If I tell you, you'll laugh at me
and ask me
what I've been doing all this time.
It's all your fault.
I guess you'll blame everything on me now.
Yes, everything is your fault.
I don't even know where to start.
No, I know exactly what went wrong.
It was when Hae-hyo entered
a public elementary school.
Fine.
I get what's going on with him,
but what about Hae-na?
Is she dating some jerk
who went to that school?
-Jin-u!
-Hey.
-Did I keep you waiting long?
-No. You must be hungry.
I'll take you to your favorite place.
Let's go.
-It's too expensive.
-You came here often with your mom.
Yes, but my mom paid for it.
Since when did you consider
the price of meals?
Let's just leave.
You should've said so
before we came in here.
You didn't say anything.
Seeing the price on the menu
served as a reality check.
This is the only reality
I can offer you though.
I'd rather not be sad right now.
What's reality for me is sadness to you.
My mom invited you over
for a meal this weekend.
Did your mother leave?
Thanks for the invitation.
My mom's staying for a few days.
Good night.
"HAPPINESS IS SIMPLE AND FRUGAL"
NIKOS KAZANTZAKIS
MY RECENT MOST FAVORITE QUOTE,
FROM HYE-JUN
Are you cooking?
It's nothing new.
You don't have any tofu.
The convenience store has some.
Who's calling this early?
I'm on tofu duty, I guess
HYE-JUN
-Hello?
-Head outside.
-What?
-Check what's outside.
What is it?
FROM HYE-JUN
No way! It's from Sa Hye-jun!
-Mom!
-You said you two weren't dating.
He's crazy for you!
-Why would you--
-You sure are a cunning little minx.
I fell for a handsome man
who had nothing to offer
and paid for it harshly,
but not you.
You won't be left with nothing
even if you do break up.
You haven't changed at all, have you?
How vulgar.
Lend me some money.
Seeing how we've crossed all the lines
there are between a parent and a child,
there's nothing left to lose.
Let's go all the way.
SA HYE-JUN
RATINGS PLUMMET FOR THE FIRST HUMAN
IS SA HYE-JUN TO BLAME?
What? Out News?
It's the same reporter.
How does a 2.1 percent drop
qualify as a "plummet"?
Unbelievable.
Here you are. I've been looking for you.
Ms. Lee, I read an article.
-It's her, right?
-Yes.
How is Hye-jun the cause of this?
It's the plot that's boring.
-I downloaded and watched it myself.
-Can't you see it when it airs?
My family watching it
doesn't get added to the ratings,
so it's of no use.
Why do articles like this keep surfacing?
I've seen agencies block articles
for their actors on TV. Can't you do that?
I can't, so just give me
your written apology.
It has everything that it needs.
Save the compliments for others to give.
You're leaving already?
I need to head over to the set.
With ratings lowering,
you can imagine what it's like.
Have a good one then.
It must be fate.
-Good job, everyone.
-Good job.
-I thought Min-jae was coming.
-She's using the restroom.
Good job, everyone.
Only two weeks left to go
and we're in a mess.
It's because of Sa Hye-jun.
Background checks should be mandatory
before casting actors.
All the skeletons in the closet
keep coming out.
The director is too nice to say anything,
but imagine his stress.
I never thought Sa Hye-jun was the type.
He's not.
Let me apologize.
The gossip surrounding Sa Hye-jun
is due to my lacking as his agent.
We'll see you around.
Would it kill them to at least apologize?
That damn reporter.
Damn it!
ACCUSED: KIM SU-MAN
COMPLAINANT: SA HYE-JUN
Damn it.
-Sir.
-Yes?
I consulted with a lawyer
and was told to settle
since the charges could stick.
-Then go for it.
-But sir.
Can't the legal team
talk to Sa Hye-jun on my behalf?
But this isn't a company issue.
Once the bosses know, you'll get the boot.
But sir!
You're the one who told me
to go for the jugular!
Sergeant Lee,
let me have Sa Hye-jun's text messages.
Just take this and leave.
How about a deal?
-There's another article.
-What article?
That you're lowering the ratings.
-It's the same one from this morning.
-And that makes it okay?
How about…
we reveal the texts?
It'll turn the tables.
I'm not that desperate yet.
I want to take a vacation after this.
But I thought you were a workaholic.
Don't you want to review
the offers you received?
No.
JEONG-HA
THANK YOU
You must be tough mentally.
Me? I doubt it.
Nothing fazes you.
Says who?
I cry myself to sleep.
Really?
What you see isn't everything.
I can smile during the day
because I cry at night.
That's cool too. I respect you.
Do you know what it is?
THE TREE THAT BRINGS JOY
The tree that brings joy.
It feels surreal
that you're driving this truck.
And being together right now
doesn't feel real, either.
I want to record this moment.
One, two, three.
I can't believe my Jeong-ha
can wash her hair on her own now!
Just a second.
Let me apply some lotion on you.
Round, and round, and round
The warmth I felt back then.
That is enough of a reason
for me to forgive my mom.
MIN-JAE
Hey, Jeong-ha.
Min-jae, when will Hye-jun
have some free time?
I need to talk to him.
It's so hard to get a hold of you.
Right.
I'm sorry I stood you up that day.
You've apologized enough for that.
It's okay.
It's nice to finally be able
to talk to you face to face.
Same here.
I decided to listen to you
and take a break.
I kept working
because I was anxious.
Getting this far wasn't easy.
You got this far
thanks to your hard work and tenacity.
You're also level-headed
and you never inconvenienced others.
You're very passionate
when it comes to acting.
It's nice to hear you put it that way.
Thanks for noticing.
Instead of apologizing,
we're thanking each other today.
I love you.
We should break up.
Why?
Do you remember
how you told me
that you would never apologize
to the person you love?
Just think about
how often you've apologized to me.
I'm sorry.
Every time you apologize,
I can only think of
how hard it must be for you.
The Sa Hye-jun I know
always stands by his words.
I don't want to be your emotional outlet
anymore.
I want to go back
to before I fell in love with you.
Apologize to your mother for me.
What is it?
Let me drive you home.
It's fine.
That's
enough.
That's barely 30,000 viewers.
Sa Hye-jun doesn't generate
much publicity anymore.
How can he when he's
at the center of continuous scandals?
"Stop using Hye-jun for publicity."
"Love between two people isn't a crime."
"Who cares what the texts say?"
"I hope Hye-jun sues his ass."
The texts will end Sa Hye-jun's career.
Do you want to see them?
If only I could actually show them to you.
What a bummer.
CHARLIE JUNG
I KNOW YOU DON'T LOVE ME
BUT I REALIZE THAT YOU RESPECT ME
I WANTED TO APOLOGIZE TO YOU
EMAIL
Hold on.
Why are you home?
I'm not working today.
Isn't Mom home?
No, she went to work.
Why do you seem so glum?
-It's nothing.
-I see.
I bet Jeong-ha's thrilled
to have dinner with us.
She is,
but we'll have to reschedule.
Is she busy that day?
Yes. It seems that way.
SA HYE-JUN'S AGENCY DISCLOSES
CHARLIE JUNG'S TEXT MESSAGE
THE RUMORS WERE PROVED TO BE FALSE
SA HYE-JUN REJECTED
CHARLIE JUNG'S ADVANCES
I guess his agency is close
with Choi Kang from Image News.
Image News always gets the exclusives.
Do you have anything?
We need to talk about the lawsuit.
My lunch must have been too salty.
I need some water.
I don't think I got here late.
Were you surprised when I called?
You're still as rude as ever.
It really got on my nerves at first.
I found you very amicable,
so I was trying to be friendly
in my own way.
Let me give you some legal advice
because you seem to like me so much.
You should settle.
-So I've been told.
-You can talk to me.
Should I proceed with it?
I haven't decided yet.
Why are you so hostile against Hye-jun?
I hate disloyal and selfish people.
He dropped Lee Tae-su
when his agency went under
and left with
JJamppong Entertainment's CEO.
Su-man.
You've made me speechless.
-What?
-You've got it all wrong.
Do you know
what Lee Tae-su put Hye-jun through
by pocketing Hye-jun's pay?
Of course, he said he'd pay him
once his agency did well.
-What?
-I told him Mr. Lee was a fraud
but he didn't listen to me.
No way.
I've been checking your news articles.
I know you want to criticize him more,
but you might get a heavier sentence
for multiple offenses.
Your company will not protect you.
They'll kick you out after the sentencing
because you were overly enthusiastic
and harmed the company.
If you want to settle, call me.
-Hello.
Is there a lady who came alone?
I knew it. You know how to drink, Ms. Kim.
Drinks are best had during the day.
Okay.
Go ahead.
How's work?
Is it going well?
How could it go well?
The company is ignoring me.
That's awful.
I'm sure it will work out.
Or quit and become a YouTuber.
Talking about the stories you know
from your job will be a huge hit.
You know that won't happen.
You're right.
The competition is fierce among YouTubers.
If you knew that,
why did you encourage me to do it?
You're a bit touchy today.
The lawsuit
must have hurt you pretty badly.
But this is nothing in the long run.
Something feels off.
Why did you lie to me?
Sa Hye-jun didn't betray you.
I did some digging
and found out you were famous
for stealing money from your clients.
I never said he betrayed me.
I just said I lost him to her.
It's valid from my perspective.
I said I looked back on my actions
and want to bring him back,
so I can take good care of him.
You were the one who interpreted it
the way you wanted.
You can't blame this on me now.
The biggest asshole in life is someone
who pretends to be the victim
when he's the assailant.
Calm yourself.
Why are you suddenly acting
if any of this matters?
Mr. Lee, have you watched
the movie, Veteran?
I did.
"I don't have money, not self-respect."
Do you think I'm a joke?
I'm going to bring
A June Entertainment down.
Park Do-ha?
I'll keep exposing him to the public.
You pay for the drinks.
I don't have money.
She's freaking crazy.
Have you been avoiding me?
Why would I do that?
Don't you have a shoot?
It's over.
Thanks to Sa Hye-jun,
your successful drama went down in flames.
The ratings went down the gutter.
It's because of the plot.
You're still protecting him, Hae-hyo.
I thought we were a little closer
to each other. Was I wrong?
We've seen each other at our worst.
I suddenly don't feel like working out
thanks to you.
You and I should have fun.
I know a fun place.
Is this the fun place?
It's so much fun once you get used to it.
It's very private.
It's been a while.
Gosh, you should have come more often.
Didn't you miss me?
I'm leaving.
Hey, what's wrong?
Do you not like us?
I have to be somewhere.
Hey.
Hey. I didn't know you were home, Hae-na.
Don't you have classes today?
Ms. Han.
I'm lonely.
You should date someone.
Don't just study all the time.
I want to gain weight
so I can get back at my mom.
You must love your mother
as much as you love yourself.
I do?
It's unhealthy if you put on
a lot of weight over a short period.
You're harming your own body,
but you think you can hurt
your mom with that.
I thought sacrificing everything
for your children was pointless,
but I guess it wasn't.
Right.
I guess Mom and I are connected
in ways I never imagined.
I don't know what this is about.
But don't avoid her. Just talk to her.
If you keep talking to her,
you're bound to wear her down.
She's your mom.
Mom.
That won't work.
I lost.
Is this a new plan?
Are you pretending to surrender
to persuade me?
I guess this won't work, either.
Isn't there any way for me to have my way?
No.
REPUBLIC OF KOREA MARINE CORPS
ENLISTMENT DETAILS
Hye-jun.
Are you tired?
I don't have work today.
I did something really bad.
I'd like to share
some very interesting news today.
Ms. Kim, you were the first one
to deliver us the news about Sa Hye-jun.
Yes. That must be why many people assume
he's the main subject of my news articles.
I see.
This is the text message
Sa Hye-jun's agency sent.
HYE-JUN, CONGRATULATIONS
If he disclosed it sooner,
he could have avoided speculations
and hate comments.
From this, I could see how much
Sa Hye-jun respected
the late Charlie Jung.
As someone who reported about him
many times, it was quite heartwarming.
I'm glad it's finally over.
I look forward to hearing
more heartwarming stories about him.
Sure.
I didn't tell you in advance
because I knew you wouldn't agree to this.
Hye-jun. Oh, you're here, too.
Is this a strategy meeting?
What strategy meeting?
The forums are a mess
since  Hot Issue Tok Tok aired.
They're saying he disclosed it
because he wanted to avoid criticism.
I'm sure there are some nice comments.
-Yes, they are.
-Why bring up the bad news?
Nice comments don't go viral.
You should have discussed it with me.
You shouldn't have disclosed it like this.
Why are you always unhappy
with everything I do?
It keeps repeating over and over again.
If we try to fix it by releasing
a statement, it brings another problem.
This is why I wanted to wait.
I believed this was the best decision
we could make.
We haven't renewed our contract yet.
I will accept whatever decision
you make.
PARK DO-HA RECEIVES EVALUATION
FOR MILITARY SERVICE
OUT NEWS KIM SU-MAN
Gosh, Kim Su-man.
Damn it. I shouldn't
have made an enemy of her.
Why did I do that?
Why?
Tae-su!
I thought you were friends
with Kim Su-man, the reporter.
Why is there an article
about my military service?
Do-ha.
Do-ha. Don't worry about it.
I'll take care of everything.
You should focus on working out
for our next project.
Can I trust you?
Of course, you can.
Trust me.
This is Jung Ji-a.
Can I get my makeup done by you, Ms. An?
This way, please.
I have a trial this afternoon.
I see. How about makeup that
makes you look soft, but elegant?
Sounds good.
You don't have to worry
about Hye-jun and me. We're just friends.
Men and women can't be friends.
On top of that, you're his ex.
I don't think I can. I'm not that cool.
If you're bothered by it,
I'll stop seeing him.
No. I'm also his ex now.
That way, please.
Ji-a isn't here yet. She's in court.
When did you get here?
A while ago.
I'm clearing your schedule.
I won't book anything
unless it's important.
Okay. Let's talk
about our contract next week.
I'm sorry I'm late.
It was a simple trial,
but there was a curveball.
I asked to meet you here
because Ms. Kim wants to settle.
What do you want to do?
What should I do?
It's better to settle.
I talked to her,
and she's not a vicious person.
She only wrote those articles because
her initial intel was completely off.
Then we'll settle.
When her lawyer sends me their draft,
I'll show it to you
after my boss confirms it.
If you think it's reasonable,
we'll finalize it.
Thanks.
Well,
can we talk about something else?
We're 28 now.
You were 20 when we first met.
A lot has happened since then.
You will be
the most beautiful
and sparkling part of my youth.
Thank you.
I can finally let you go,
emotionally speaking.
I met with Jeong-ha.
She seems nice and is the same age as us.
I want to be her friend
regardless of your relationship with her.
Do you remember
how you told me
that you would never apologize
to the person you love?
I know how busy you've been lately.
I'm sorry
for not replying to your texts.
we can't spend much time together.
I'm sorry, Jeong-ha.
I want to tell you the full story
in person.
I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry.
-What are you apologizing for this time?
Just think about
how often you've apologized to me.
Every time you apologize,
I can only think of
how hard it must be for you.
-Aren't you busy?
-No.
The shoot is over.
Why did you come here?
I can't break up with you.
Subtitle translation by: Hye-lim Park
RECORD OF YOUTH
You were able to fulfill your dream,
but I'm just getting started.
I'm sorry
that I wasn't there for you.
I always wanted your approval.
You raised a good son.
You didn't fail.
I've put my name on the map.
Let's wrap things up.
Promise me that you'll remember
the time we spent together.
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs