RECORD OF YOUTH
THIS PROGRAM HAS BEEN SELECTED AS AN
"EXCELLENT BROADCAST CONTENT" AND IS SUPPORTED
BY THE MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS, TOURISM
AND THE KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
How about some music?
Sure.
Hae-hyo.
Do you know Jung Ji-a?
Did you date her?
No, Hye-jun did.
Oh, right. Jin-u talked about her too.
My gosh, Hye-jun has high standards.
It's Ji-a that has high standards.
He and the girl he's seeing now
are a perfect match.
Who's a perfect match?
Hye-jun and his girlfriend.
Hye-jun has a girlfriend? Who is it?
It's none of your business, Mother.
His career still hasn't taken off.
I can't believe he has a girlfriend.
He got a role in Gateway.
My gosh, it sounds like
things are going well for Hye-jun.
Poor you.
You're single, and you don't even
have any dramas lined up.
You little…
I'm coming up with a plan
for your brother.
You've already read this,
so read the other ones.
There are so many.
You thought he wasn't getting any work?
He was in a movie and played the lead
in a web drama.
It's just none of them was a big hit
even though he's been working nonstop.
We need to find that big hit.
I've been too easy on you.
Look at you saying this to my face.
I said I'll figure it out.
Let's not fight. I'm on your side.
Put me to good use
instead of trying to push me away.
I won't go anywhere
even if you push me away.
So just give up.
What happens if I get angry?
A war will break out.
Will you give up?
No.
Let's listen to something else.
I'm hungry.
Me too. Do you want to go eat something?
No. I'll gain weight if I eat now.
You shouldn't either.
You need to stay fit for the shoot.
I always stay fit.
-I can eat now.
-No, you can't.
I'm saying it's fine.
Why are you saying I can't?
You're being overbearing.
So? You don't like me?
I like you.
Let's go.
What would you like to order?
Just a moment, please.
Hae-hyo's the model,
so we should buy some.
Doughnuts are the best
when your blood sugar falls low.
I thought you weren't eating.
Don't attack me using
what I said in the past.
Point taken. What do you want to drink?
Coffee.
It'll make me stay up all night,
but I still want coffee.
No.
I want coffee.
This isn't fair. Why order me milk
when you're having what you wanted?
You're being overbearing.
So? You don't like me?
I like you.
Smoothies and doughnuts are both sweet.
It goes better with coffee.
I don't know why people drink coffee.
It's too bitter.
You're like a kid.
On your lips.
Here.
By the way, you have such big hands.
It'll cover half of your face.
Is it big?
-I guess it is.
-I can't see a thing.
Did you want to see me that much?
That was too cheesy.
I like it.
You do?
-Yes.
-Wasn't it too childish?
That's why I like it.
I want to feel like a kid when I date.
When it comes to dating,
I don't want to be too realistic.
Reality has been hitting me hard
since I was little.
Let's do that if that's what you want.
-But you don't want to?
-I probably can't be like that.
The more you love someone,
the more responsible you become.
I'm happy I'm dating such a good guy.
This is how you're training me
to do better.
You could tell?
I'm going to dye my hair black.
-Why?
-Because I'm playing a doctor.
-But you don't have the script yet.
-They told me about the character.
I'll dye your hair.
Isn't it a nuisance?
Work's keeping you busy enough.
Your girlfriend's a makeup artist.
I can certainly do that much for you.
And I've been promoted to designer.
I heard I got promoted very fast.
I'm so relaxed when I'm with you.
I feel secure.
Like how my name sounds in Korean.
An Jeong-ha makes you feel secure.
My name, Sa Hye-jun,
can mean "forgiveness."
Does that mean
I have to forgive everything?
This is amazing.
Don't forget. You have to forgive me
no matter what I do.
Deal.
Eat.
-Seeing you eat fills me up.
-Gosh, cut it out.
RECORD OF YOUTH
EPISODE 8
I'm sorry, but can you bring me
my tablet PC?
Sure, no problem.
I heard Hye-jun got a role in Gateway.
What kind of role?
Pardon me?
You didn't know? The drama will air soon.
Oh, he hasn't told you,
so it's probably a minor role
with only a few lines.
-I see.
-I heard he's got a girlfriend.
You didn't know?
Good for you.
Your kids just figure stuff out
on their own. How convenient is that?
My gosh, I have so much to do.
Hae-hyo's acting career,
military service, marriage, and kids.
Hae-na's law school, law firm,
marriage, and kids.
Will it ever end?
I'll probably have to look after them
until I turn 70.
Why are you all quiet? You always have
something to say about the kids.
Today, I have nothing to say.
The look on your face tells me
that isn't the case.
You seem upset.
-Do I look upset?
-Yes.
I see. I guess I can't hide my feelings.
Wait.
Gosh, what's with her?
What does that make me?
I didn't know I let my feelings show
even in front of Hae-hyo's mother.
But Hye-jun really is
taking care of everything on his own.
Is everything okay with your family?
Hey, don't scare me.
Goodness.
Hye-jun, congratulations.
I heard you got a role in a drama.
Seriously?
I doubt it.
-What's going on?
-Hye-jun got a role in a drama.
That's amazing.
Is he sure this time?
We'll find out once the drama airs.
Why bother asking?
It's great news. Can't you be positive?
Even last time, it fell through.
We won't know until it happens.
I actually hope it falls through
so that he can learn his lesson.
Don't forget to meet me later.
He's finally back to himself.
Gyeong-jun, what a great brother you are.
How come Hye-jun isn't saying anything?
Come on in. I made sure to get ready
just before you arrived.
-Aren't I so good?
-Be good at other things.
-You'll bring me down?
-As if that's possible.
It is.
Keep your spirits up.
You're doing a great job.
My gosh, that line…
Hey, you just made my heart skip a beat.
Goodness, people need to see this.
This needs to be seen.
HYE-JUN
…
I asked him why he's not saying anything,
and he sent three dots.
Hae-hyo is handsome.
Although Hye-jun is more handsome.
Have you found anyone who's a good cook?
-Yes, she can take the job.
-It's someone you trust, right?
You know Jin-u, right?
She's Jin-u's mother.
I see.
Is this a school parent meeting or what?
When can she start?
I'll give you her number.
You can contact her.
-Okay.
-By the way,
Hae-hyo was the one who told you
that Hye-jun is seeing someone, right?
How long has he been seeing her?
I didn't think he'd date anyone
after breaking up with his ex.
But you know, Hye-jun can't really afford
to be dating now.
Look at her throwing a hook just because
I've let my guard down a little.
These days, people say
that you should be grateful
if your kids can date without your help.
What's with her these days?
She always talks back to me.
You know a lot of things.
Thank you.
That was not a compliment.
Are you going to stand there?
Don't you find this noisy?
DAD
Hi, Dad.
Where are you?
On the bus. I'm headed to the salon.
You're headed there early today.
I'm going to the hospital.
Don't be surprised.
You got me worried.
Is everything okay with her?
She got a facelift yesterday.
She's pretty, but she keeps on
comparing herself to when she was young.
I'm on my way to pick her up.
Good for her that she's married
to a man like you.
And good for you
that you have a dad like me.
Will you ever call me first?
I miss you, Jeong-ha.
I miss you too.
But I'm on the bus now,
so I can't talk long.
Oh, okay. I'll visit you soon.
Good morning.
I'll do your makeup for your blind date
tomorrow. I'll make you look lovely.
My gosh, I'd love that.
How about salad for lunch? There is
new salad place across the street.
If anyone wants salad, let me know.
I'll put in the order for everyone.
Can you ask Su-bin too?
She has such a thick skin.
I know. I can't beat her.
APPOINTMENT LIST
DESIGNER: AN JEONG-HA
Those who bring you down
and want to destroy you.
You're fully booked today.
You seem immensely interested in me.
When are you going to quit?
I'm well aware of the fact that
I can't change things no matter what I do.
You're smart. I see that
you're always quick to gauge situations.
Why are you doing all this?
Do you know why someone
would come to hate you the most?
They just hate you.
But one good thing about it is that
it's giving me so much energy.
The wheels are turning in my head
to come up with a way to kick you out.
I'm realizing that I should just pity you.
How dare you!
Now that I know
what kind of person you are,
I'll not let you have it your way.
Hot off the press.
You won't read it?
I'm going to the library
to do some research.
Which department?
Emergency Medicine.
-What can I refer to?
-Remember ER?
Although it's an old drama.
But that's not important.
Your romantic eyes--
You're at it again? Don't be so shallow.
Being shallow isn't bad.
It's about your preference.
Okay, I'll respect your preferences.
Let's have lunch and head out together.
No, I want to go study.
I'm seeing Gyeong-jun in the evening.
Where are you going?
You're starting a new drama.
I'm seeing the reporters
to say hello and stay on their good side.
Hello.
I should have visited you sooner.
I'm sorry it took me some time.
I know the other director at A June
very well.
-Nice to meet you. She's my junior.
-Hello.
I enjoyed your article. Let's sit down.
You were stressed out because of Do-ha.
There were many mean comments
about that article.
We were also criticized
for poor management.
Will Do-ha and Jessica
both be in the mini-series, Catch?
As for Jessica, it's been finalized.
And Do-ha…
It hasn't been confirmed yet,
but you'll be the first to know.
Nice. You can publish an exclusive.
JJAMPPONG LEE MIN-JAE
Oh, sorry.
No problem.
Hello, Ms. Lee. Yes.
One of the top writers is working on it.
I'll tell you all about that too.
Thank you.
I'm in a meeting now.
I'll call you back in a bit.
Okay. All right.
Do you know about JJamppong Entertainment?
JJamppong, again?
There's such an entertainment agency?
JJamppong? What kind of name is that?
Is it a joke or what?
But she's very nice.
I was going to just introduce myself
and have a cup of tea with you.
But I have to say, I really like you.
Do you like to drink?
I know it's still early, but we can drink
until we drop if you're free.
DEPARTMENT OF EMERGENCY MEDICINE
So who's that bastard?
The bastard who wants me dead.
It's actually a woman.
She's an office worker.
She begged for mercy,
but I said flat out, "No way."
Good.
You don't have to do it
if you don't want to.
I can't say no after meeting
the director and writer.
I'll take care of all the difficult stuff.
Just do what you want to do.
Do-ha, you're very quiet.
I'm shy.
I see.
I'm a fan of your dramas.
Thank you.
His work is delicate but powerful.
Gosh.
Let's get down to the point.
You'll join us on the drama, right?
I should, since the two of you
are working on it.
Thank you. Let's do a great job.
Oh, have you finished casting
for the other roles?
Who's playing Yeong-min? I interact
with him the most, after Jessica.
We have two candidates.
Lee Yong-ju and Tae Yeong-jin.
-I see.
And for another role,
we're thinking Won Hae-hyo or Lee Ji-seop.
Hae-hyo? I like Hae-hyo.
Won Hae-hyo? Are you close?
We shot a movie together. He's easygoing.
I see. I've never met him.
I should meet him soon.
Yes, you should.
I'll need your ID
if you'd like a new debit card.
Where did it go? I'm in a huge rush.
-Please hurry.
-Okay.
Where is the option
for reissuing a debit card?
You don't know how to do it?
No, because it's not my duty.
You know I jumped in to help out.
So it's not something you normally do?
Anyway, please hurry.
It's on the far left of the main menu bar.
Oh, there it is.
Ms. Kim Ju-yun.
Please fill this out--
Gosh, what the hell.
What an incompetent clerk.
I'm not incompetent. This isn't my duty,
but I'm helping out my colleague.
Please understand.
Do you know what Mr. Sa said
in front of a customer earlier?
-What did he say?
-Is he a fact-checker or what?
He wants to show off
that he's an SNU graduate.
What's the use though?
He's so incompetent.
He even fell victim to a rental scam.
Gosh, that is ridiculous.
And he acts all smart?
-Goodness.
-I heard he lost all his money.
Anyhow…
I wonder why people always
bad-mouth others in the restroom.
And the person being bad-mouthed
always happens to hear it.
Sorry about that.
Why don't we go grab a drink later?
I can't. I have plans.
Okay. Another time, then.
Let's go.
We're sorry.
It's so easy for them to say sorry.
I want to punch them, but I can't.
I need this job.
The bastard who conned me…
I hope his family suffers
for three generations.
Yes, ma'am.
-Mr. Sa.
-Yes.
It is your duty to help out the customers
when others are busy.
Why must you always draw the line?
If there isn't a clear line,
you don't know who's responsible for what.
Then someone could be
wrongly accused of a mistake.
I heard you were born in 1992.
-Yes.
-I was so surprised.
You look older than your age.
I looked like this in middle school.
Because of you, I even read a book called
90's Kids Are Coming.
I'm trying to understand you better.
Can you please listen to your superiors
and do as you're told?
Yes, ma'am. I'll try.
You must try your best.
You must try a hundred times harder
than others.
"Others"? What do you mean--
Forget it, Trooper.
Go back to your desk.
That's it for today.
Yes, ma'am.
-What do you want to eat?
-What's good around here?
Around here? There's a galbi restaurant
and grilled clams…
-Mr. Sa?
-Yes?
Who is he?
Oh, say hello. This is my manager.
Hello, I'm Sa Hye-jun.
He's my little brother.
Seriously?
I hate this world.
People judge others
based on money and looks.
By any chance, aren't you a model?
You look familiar.
I used to model
but have switched to acting.
I knew it.
I could tell.
You're so handsome.
What brings you here?
We're having dinner together.
My gosh, I haven't had dinner yet either.
Go have dinner. I'll be off, then.
Let's go.
-Take care.
-Bye.
That heartless jerk.
You should drink too.
I said I won't drink in the evening
for a while.
Gosh, you're so strict.
You said the shoot will begin next week.
It's only a week away.
Lucky you.
Everyone likes you
the moment they meet you.
What's this nonsense?
Dad is so proud of you and calls you
the brain of the family.
Hey, it's not like I can walk around
with my report card or business card
on my face so people know
I'm smart and have a good job.
Nothing can beat a handsome face.
Are you drunk?
Try to calculate the monetary value
of the kindness you receive from others
thanks to your handsome face.
That's all you can do
when you were born with that face?
It's a serious problem.
You're drunk. Let's go home.
When I got conned,
you didn't say anything
and just bought me dinner.
I was so grateful to you.
I thought, "My little brother, Hye-jun,
is all grown up now.
He's an adult now.
He knows how to console others.
He's grown into such a cool guy."
Shut up.
I can't drink if I shut up.
Come on. Get up.
Okay, I am getting up.
Gosh, you're such a handful.
A handful? You use that word when
you're talking about things like food.
Don't eat it with your hand.
All right.
Gyeong-jun sure is the eldest child.
Look, he's taking Hye-jun out for dinner
despite his situation.
Go in.
Dad.
Dad!
Gosh, what happened?
Darn it.
-How come only he's drunk?
-Dad.
Why did you let him drink so much?
Do you only see how drunk he is and not
how I practically carried him home?
-Dad.
-Yes.
Dad…
My gosh, Gyeong-jun.
What's wrong? Who upset you?
-I'm stressed out.
-Of course.
That son of a bitch.
I want the scammer's family
to suffer for three generations!
-Damn it.
-Yes, of course.
Stop, enough.
How can I stop?
Every time I close my eyes,
I see that bastard's face.
How can I stop thinking about it?
Take him to his room.
-Mom.
-Shut it!
It's okay.
Oh, here.
I'll take that.
Thanks for carrying Gyeong-jun home.
Thanks for saying that.
I feel a bit better now.
But you hurt my feelings a little.
Why didn't you tell me
about getting the role in the drama?
It fell through last time, you know.
I was going to tell you once it airs.
But you'll be heartbroken
if it falls through.
You can turn to me at times like that.
I know that your dad
keeps hurting your feelings.
But it's not because he doesn't love you.
He didn't receive affection
from his parents, so he doesn't know how.
Try to understand him.
Don't just expect me to understand him.
Judging from the way he treats Gyeong-jun,
he obviously knows how to show affection.
Right? It is your dad's fault.
Parents must give love first.
What the heck is he doing? How petty.
If you take my side like that,
I can't stay mad.
You're so clever, Mom.
Do you have anything else to tell me?
I'm pretty sure you do.
I get really upset
when I hear about you from someone else.
Your girlfriend.
Oh, Jeong-ha?
Her name is Jeong-ha?
Yes, Jeong-ha. An Jeong-ha.
-She's sweet.
-Is she?
Yes.
That's good.
It's very important.
I'm sure I'll love her.
Do you want to meet her?
I'd love to.
Since you brought that up first,
I can't stay mad at you either.
Welcome.
I thought we were doing it at the salon.
I can't use the salon for personal stuff.
I don't like that either.
We're similar in a lot of ways.
I have something for you.
In return for your gift.
What a beautiful illustration.
What did you write?
Read it later.
Applying some oil on your hair
before dyeing it
helps the dye job
and protects the hair from damage.
That feels nice.
All right, sir. We'll get started now.
I'm coming in.
How do I look?
The color turned out very nice.
Don't do that.
Sorry.
All right, we should end this properly.
Here, some hand cream.
Do you apply hand cream here first?
Yes. What about you?
-How could you start there?
-Why start on the palm?
You're set in your ways.
Many people start on the back of the hand.
You're very opinionated.
Most people don't care.
Start on the back of the hand
and it'll feel less greasy on the palm.
I've never pondered what's good
about putting it on the palm first.
I just applied it like how others did.
The fact that everyone does it
means it's the best way.
That's something only a stability-seeker
like you would say.
The minority definitely looks classier
than the majority.
But I'd still like to be the majority.
Say that with a straight face on.
-You win.
-It's not a battle.
-I respect your preference.
-Hey. Stop that.
Hey.
Dr. Park Jeong-geun,
please come to the ER.
Hae-jin.
Did you finish tidying up?
What is it? You're scaring me.
Can I ask you out?
Can I hit you?
-Is that a no?
-Yes, it is.
Did you finish cleaning up?
That was way too fast.
I doubt that you're that good.
I'm good, too.
I may not be as good as you,
but I'll get there.
Don't trip and fall.
Father.
He did it.
He made it now.
Father, why are you crying?
-I don't know.
-I'm home.
I can't stop crying.
Call him and find out
when he's coming home.
What's wrong with him?
Because I'm happy.
Honey, Hye-jun's drama
just finished airing.
It's so weird!
I bet it is.
Why watch it? It's upsetting.
It was weird because he was just amazing.
He didn't look like he's one of us.
Did you guys meet outside?
He and I had a drink.
Then, you should have come home early
and watched the drama with us.
I don't like dramas.
I'll only watch his clips.
Father, get a grip.
Don't get too sentimental and think
that this actually means something.
He totally ruined the moment for me.
GYEONG-MI
Hey, Gyeong-mi.
Ae-suk, this was amazing!
I got butterflies.
Is that the same boy I know?
Hye-jun is going to hit it big!
Can I ask you out?
Can I hit you?
Is that a no?
Hae-hyo. Hae-hyo!
The episode was nice.
You had great chemistry with Ms. Lee.
MS. KIM I-YEONG
Hyeon-su is an incredible actress,
so I look pretty decent next to her.
Gosh. "Hyeon-su"?
When did you become such close friends?
Are you still shooting?
Yes. But I only have one scene left.
I couldn't even watch the episode.
I watched it. You were great.
We're rolling soon.
I have to go.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
Who was that?
Hye-jun. I called him
after watching the episode.
He was totally cute in the episode.
Did you watch it?
I won't admit it even if I did.
Your drama will do better than his.
Don't worry.
I'm not worried.
Yes. You shouldn't worry.
I'll do all the worrying.
You'll be working with Park Do-ha.
If his drama isn't a hit,
that itself is a problem.
-Here's water.
-Okay.
Do-ha, when will your drama air?
Early next month.
Which drama are you girls
watching these days?
Gateway.
Can I put this on now?
-I heard that's popular nowadays.
-Hae-jin.
But the TV ratings aren't that high.
His name is Sa Hye-jun,
and he's in the limelight now.
What is it? You're scaring me.
Can I ask you out?
He wants to ask her out!
I just became his fan.
Can I hit you?
-Do-ha.
-Get out.
You have no sense of gratitude.
I basically feed you girls.
Wait, is someone going to give us a meal?
We can pay money for a meal ourselves.
I don't mooch off anyone.
-You're so dense.
-Girls, get out.
We're leaving.
-Gosh.
-Just move aside.
Are you bothered?
This is ridiculous.
How can they like someone else
when I'm here?
You know what?
You're a top star.
When your drama airs,
everyone's eyes will be on you.
What is it? You're scaring me.
Can I ask you out?
"Can I ask you out?"
Was that supposed to make
my heart skip a beat? Seriously?
That stupid writer. This doesn't work
anymore in this day and age. Gosh.
"Can I ask you out?"
Sir, let's crank up the music.
Okay.
Gosh.
Goodness.
What is it? You're scaring me.
-Can I ask you out?
-He's so handsome. What's his name?
Right. What is his name?
-Hey, let's find out his name.
-Okay.
-He's so handsome.
-It's Sa Hye-jun.
-Is that a no?
-Yes, it is.
Do you know him?
Well, I know him from my last job.
He was a model, then.
He used to be a model.
-That's why he's so tall.
-I knew it.
Everyone liked him. He's nice and polite.
I see.
Don't trip and fall.
Don't stare at me like that.
It's a bit uncomfortable.
-What?
-I'm leaving.
-Gosh.
-Hey. Wait.
If you have more information,
tell us before you go!
Cut. Okay. Well done!
-Good work.
-Good job.
-Nice job.
-Thank you.
-Great job.
-Good work.
Good work.
-Good work. Thank you, sir.
-Thank you.
-Well done.
-Good work.
Hye-jun.
-What is it?
-You didn't watch the episode, right?
-My heart skipped a beat.
-Don't exaggerate it.
My mom said you were handsome.
She's happy
that you're on TV more than I am.
Please thank her for me.
Your mother has great eyes.
-I'll be nice to you, Chi-yeong.
-Why would you be nice?
Do you not have your agent?
Why are you always with Hye-jun?
Because we have a lot of scenes together.
Hye-jun.
Anyway, let's eat.
Let's discuss what our next step is
during our meal.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
I'm on my way, too.
He's adorable.
Gosh.
Drinking milk will help.
-But that's fattening.
-Gosh, get me two cartons of milk.
-Gosh, okay. Is two enough?
-Excuse me.
Can I get an autograph?
Sure.
Give me the paper.
Today's episode was really good.
What will happen to Ji-hun and Hae-jin?
Unrequited love, probably?
I hope they end up together.
What's your name?
It's Hong Yu-rin.
That way.
Did you stay up all night?
I heard your drama was over.
I filmed a commercial.
Nice. You must have made loads of money.
I don't know that yet.
You're getting pretty popular now.
Shouldn't Min-jae escort this superstar
to the salon? You're the talent.
Our agency is pretty small.
I don't have a car.
But I'll get a car pretty soon.
It's crossing the ocean.
And she has an important meeting.
Did I answer everything?
You know,
I recently started working with Do-ha.
I've been meaning to say hello to you,
and I'm finally here.
Ever since he joined us,
our sales went up.
And our brand got popular.
The company was very happy
with my decision.
I'm sad this will be
the last one with him.
What…
This is the last one. I see.
All right, then.
Brands that change their models often
might be perceived as a bit disloyal.
Yes, that's true, too.
Excuse me. I must get back in.
I have another appointment.
I see.
I was in such a good mood when I came in.
And now, I'm in a shitty mood.
Hello.
Let's be civil.
As an agent, you must say hello
despite your personal feelings.
No. Being civil means
not stabbing people in their backs.
How could you say hello to me
after what you did as if it was nothing?
What about me? What did I do?
You came to me and said
you would learn from me
and wanted me to teach you.
So I taught you the basics about people,
namely, how backstabbing they are.
I gave you a warning,
so you could succeed.
-Do you still trust people?
-I do. I just don't trust you.
I taught you well.
Why are you here?
Take a wild guess.
I'm here to sign a contract
for Hye-jun's commercial.
I told them to pay him more than Do-ha
even if it's a cent more.
If not, I told them
I wouldn't sign with them.
It looks like my talent, Hye-jun,
has hit it big.
I doubt that they will.
Whether they do it or not,
mind your own business.
Hey, Mom.
I'll drop by at your work
later this evening.
Da-on is staying with his grandma
this weekend.
No. I have plans.
Cancel it. I told you I wanted to see you.
It's been too long.
I already made plans.
You can come another day.
People are jealous of me
for having a daughter.
Poor me.
Mom, I…
I'm in front of my office.
Okay.
She doesn't know
that I quit my office job.
We're meeting the guys today.
Should I cancel it?
No. I'll go in first.
Come in after ten minutes.
Let's go in together.
No. I can't come to work with my client.
But you do that with Hae-hyo.
Our relationship is different.
-But still, I don't care.
-I care.
But I like that you don't care.
Hello.
I've been waiting for you
after seeing your name.
-"Can I ask you out?"
-"Can I hit you?"
Hey.
All of us became your fans, Hye-jun.
Thank you.
This way, please.
Hello.
Su-bin, I'm almost out of this.
Okay.
I want smokey makeup.
I want my eyes to stand out.
My single-eyelids don't stand out.
I'm doing the surgery this summer.
I have single-eyelids, too.
So people tell me to get the surgery,
but I don't plan to get the surgery done.
There's a unique charm
of having small eyes.
Having double-eyelids could make you
look attractive,
but you can't go back
to having single-eyelids.
Do you want the makeup
that achieves the same effect?
Wear this makeup
when you want to have double-eyelids.
On other days, you don't.
You have more options, then.
Well, I guess you can try that.
-What do you think?
-It looks great.
Do you like it?
No.
I'm sorry.
Do you want the smokey makeup?
Do you think I have time for that?
You're so nosy.
Just do the makeup I asked!
You talked about having options.
What is this? Look!
I'm sorry. Let me know what you want.
And I'll do it for you.
-Buy me a house.
-Pardon?
You said you'd do anything for me.
What can you do for me?
Why say something you can't do?
Who's the manager here?
I want to see the manager now!
I'm right here.
Why don't you come this way?
Do your job right.
It will be more painful if she knows
her boyfriend saw that.
Did you pick a theme for the mock trial?
Not yet. I have a few in mind,
but it's still under discussion.
HAE-HYO
What?
If you're free, drop by later.
We're celebrating for Hye-jun.
Why are you inviting me
to one of your hangouts?
Hye-jun's girlfriend is coming.
She might be bored.
She might feel out of place
with just the three of us.
I've got to go.
How considerate of him.
-Was that Hae-hyo?
-You know my brother, too?
Of course.
The four of us hung out together often.
But after I broke up with Hye-jun,
I lost contact with others too.
It sounds like they still hang out.
They are all busy, so not really.
Hye-jun is the busiest now.
He has a girlfriend.
After Gateway, he got popular.
So they only talk on the phone.
What does Hye-jun's girlfriend do?
-I'm sorry.
-It's all right.
I should put her on a blacklist.
Go get some fresh air and have
a cup of coffee with a lot of cream.
Thank you.
Don't lose Hye-jun as your client.
If you keep it up,
he will be your best client.
Okay.
-Did I do well?
-Yes.
-But I was nervous.
-I was more nervous.
I thought you liked it, so I got scared.
But it's not that bad.
-Seriously?
-No, I didn't mean that.
I surprised myself, too.
Perhaps,
I should give acting another shot.
When you said okay
to the double-eyelid makeup,
I got so scared for a second.
Gosh, she really is a smooth talker.
I get why men are switching over to her.
So what, then?
She's got a nasty personality.
Now that you taught her a lesson…
When did you get here?
Hey!
"She must hate me for a reason.
I should work harder."
I tried to figure out why.
Even when you told me you hated me
for no reason and tried to slap me,
I had hope in someone like you.
What's your point?
I can't work
with someone like you anymore.
I'm walking out.
But when I do, I'll expose everything
you accused me of doing.
I did like your makeup.
Don't be blindly loyal to your friend.
What does she mean by that?
My goodness, look at you.
Are you okay? Oh, no.
Goodness, look at him.
Are you hurt?
Gosh.
I'm just embarrassed. I'm all right.
Now that your grandson's career is
taking off, you must be happy.
Perhaps, that's why you're losing focus.
I'm in such a good mood.
So you should focus and do a better job.
If you improve a bit more,
you can be a professional model.
Okay. I'll do my best.
You're here.
Why didn't you come to the shoot?
Jang-gun was with you.
You and Jang-gun aren't the same.
Shouldn't we renew the contract
for the cosmetic commercial?
You don't forget anything
that involves money, do you?
Since it's been three years,
they'll give me a raise, right?
You got canned.
What's that look on your face?
Is that a no?
You're no longer in demand
by the public, you punk.
Oh, right.
Call my dad and tell him
not to call my mom and to live
a nice life with his mistress.
And this is the last handout for him.
Okay.
I'll go wash up and sleep.
I came here to see you
after filming all night long.
LEE TAE-SU
I never asked and I don't give a shit.
Damn it.
Could Hye-jun end up
scoring that campaign?
Still, a plant should be cut off
while it's a sprout
so that it never grows.
OUT NEWS REPORTER KIM SU-MAN
You're a long one, aren't you?
You're endlessly long.
You drove yourself to set today
and successfully wrapped up filming.
I couldn't be more grateful, My Lord.
What put you in a good mood?
I think you're going to land
that cosmetic campaign.
I asked a lot for it
because it was Park Do-ha's.
At first, I didn't think you'd get it,
but the client is extremely fond of you.
Have you read the scripts?
Yes, and I'm interested in one.
Gosh, I think it's the one I like, too.
All right, then. We'll say it on three.
One, two, three.
-The King Returns.
-Love and Guilt.
Why?
Do you not know how important
your next project is?
You've put yourself on the map,
so you need to expand next.
Love and Guilt features
a named writer and a named director.
You were offered this chance because
the A-list stars were all too busy.
Min-jae, let's not value
fame over the content.
I'm still me either way.
A romantic series
is how you score commercials
and gain global fame.
Period dramas won't get you far.
Even the title baffles me. Love and Guilt.
Why is one guilty when in love?
You would know
if you were experienced in love.
I probably know more than you.
Just so you know,
romantic series is for those
who are clueless about love.
The cold-blooded power struggle.
I like how it's brutal.
I also love the king
choosing his children out of need.
The power struggle within the family,
and how they attack each other
are also good.
Well, I'm against all of that.
You need to do what you do best
and assert yourself
as the nation's new heartthrob.
Why should I
when I plan to keep on acting?
I'm not done yet.
Being in a period drama
won't score you any commercials.
I want to fill my filmography
with projects I want to do
even if they fail.
But…
Superstar Sa, wait.
What am I supposed to do with you?
This isn't much. It's just a spa coupon.
Those who work at their desks
tend to have stiff necks and back pain.
How considerate of you, Mr. Lee.
I love going to a spa.
Do-ha's show starts next week.
Well, I honestly can't wait.
However, I've been hooked on
an actor named Sa Hye-jun
who was in Gateway.
He made it big as a model
and now he's acting.
Hye-jun…
Right, Hye-jun.
Do you know something?
I guess that's just life.
What do you mean?
Mr. Lee, you promised
I'll be the first to know, remember?
I won't publish it.
That means you will.
Hye-jun was signed with my agency.
Way back when he was a model for about…
five to six years.
Goodness. You must know him well then.
He's currently signed with an agency
run by a woman.
She stole him away.
Just thinking about Hye-jun…
Gosh, what's gotten into me?
Oh, dear.
I feel terrible, you see.
Who knew he'd…
Mr. Lee, do tell.
I swear I won't publish it.
Have you heard of a Charlie Jung?
Yeong-nam, why haven't you
offered to buy me a drink?
You must be thrilled
now that Hye-jun's on a roll.
Must I be the one to say it?
I'm even more worried now.
Things went well for him too
when he first debuted as a model.
If this doesn't pan out for him,
his life will be a mess.
The situation seems different this time.
Even Jin-ri mentioned how
the kids at school were talking about him.
My wife's saying that he's a star.
I saw him in the series
and he sure did look handsome.
-He's always been good looking.
-Of course.
-Anyway, we'll grab a drink sometime.
-No, now.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Okay, fine.
-Good.
I'm here to see An Jeong-ha
of the Management Support Team.
-Could you call her?
-Sure.
-For our future, love and work!
-For our future, love, and work!
Enjoy, guys.
We're partying all night
and Hye-jun will pay.
Got it.
Are you kidding me?
You're supposed to eat,
not film a romantic scene.
Is it because it's been a while?
You two seem awkward.
Why would we be
when we've known each other forever?
JI-A
Where are you?
With my brother and his friends.
I told you earlier.
I'd like to join you.
I'm heading home after studying all day
and I'm famished.
But Hye-jun's girlfriend is here.
So what? I'm going there
to see Hae-hyo and Jin-u.
Who was that?
Ji-a wants to join us.
-So?
-I told her not to come, but…
I can never completely say no to her.
Hae-na!
Ji-a.
Now, talk.
Once we're done here.
My brain is at full power
trying to figure it out.
I wonder who'll be hurt the most
if I join your dinner party.
You came knowing
that someone could get hurt?
I'm only making a guess
since you stopped me from joining you.
I had no ulterior motive.
And you hurt Hye-jun with that attitude.
Hye-jun and I had a good run.
Only we would know.
It's why we constantly got back together.
I get it, so just get going.
You shouldn't be here.
Do you like his girlfriend?
The person who'd be
most bothered by my presence.
It's his girlfriend.
-You're not denying it.
-That's enough.
But I'm just getting started.
-Ji-a--
-You're stopping me
so that I won't go there
and cause any damage.
Don't you get that your presence
can upset people?
That's rich coming from a guy
who harbors feelings
for his friend's girl.
Let's go.
I'll prove that my presence
won't make anyone uncomfortable.
Where did Hae-hyo go?
Beats me. He left without a word.
Something must've come up.
Then let's call it a day.
Okay, you win.
I'll pay, so take your time.
It's been a while.
Congratulations on your career.
Thanks.
Ji-a wanted to join us, so I invited her.
The more the merrier
when celebrating, right?
Sure, thanks.
Hae-na, how sweet of you to cover for me.
She didn't invite me. I invited myself.
As if I care.
Have fun, then.
Where's Jeong-ha?
She left in a hurry to see her mom.
You quit your job?
How can you do this to me?
What's your passcode?
I'll wait for you at home.
Who are you to glare at me?
What have you been up to?
Why did you quit?
Did you find a better one?
If you had, you would've told me.
Didn't you take out
a huge loan to get this place?
How do you expect to pay it back?
How can you be so reckless?
Let me take a breath first.
I knew this would happen.
Why did I bother to raise you well?
It's just like the old saying.
Like father, like daughter.
Why are you crying?
I have it worse, you know.
As if you know how I feel.
Mom.
Why are you poor
when you throw yourself at life?
-What?
-You devoted your life to raise me?
Why don't I recall that?
What I do remember though
is how I was forced to grow up fast.
Life can be ironic, don't you think?
The man you call
unrealistic and incompetent?
You spend your days looking for a chance
to insult Dad, but he's rich now.
That man you live with though?
Not even once have I thought
that he's better than Dad.
How dare you.
We've been married for over ten years
and have a child between us.
Look at you insulting me for being poor.
I'll get lost then,
so live well with your rich dad.
JEONG-HA: ARE YOU ASLEEP?
Do you like it?
Yours will be here soon, you know.
Are you kidding me?
I'm curious, that's all.
As you know, I love cars.
Why don't you get in?
That should be mine.
Here you go.
-Thank you.
Want a ride?
Sure.
Okay, step on it.
Wait, hold on!
Easy does it.
Wow.
You're the second to get a ride,
but you'll always be the first to me.
Jeez, that was corny.
You're the one who encouraged me to do it.
I like how you listen.
I'd love to drive a car like this too.
Do you have a license?
I got mine in college
and my driving is superb.
Then take the wheel.
No way. I'm not insured.
Mine will cover you.
What did you pray for?
Nothing. What about you?
I prayed on your behalf.
Me? Regarding what?
Finally, I have your attention.
You always had it, you know.
You seem worried about something.
-Do I?
-Yes.
You thought I wouldn't notice?
No.
I know how busy you've been lately.
I'm sorry…
for not replying to your texts.
It's raining.
So it is.
We must be rain-cloud magnets.
Yes, it rained
on the first day we met too.
I used to hate rainy days.
Do you still hate them?
No. I don't even remember why I used to.
I bet you hate unpredictable people.
I feel like I'm becoming
just as unpredictable though.
I bet you desire a stable life.
I don't even know if such a life exists.
Maybe I came up with something
that doesn't exist
just because I desire it.
What will happen to us?
What do you hope for?
I love you.
What was that just now?
The old man told the children
to wait inside
until it was no longer raining.
Do you remember the first day we met?
We were in the rain
from the very beginning.
Grown-ups have to go outside
even in the rain.
When I'm with you though,
even the rain is enjoyable.
Subtitle translation by Hye-lim Park
RECORD OF YOUTH
Don't you know that Hye-jun is a star now?
Does Hye-jun know?
I want a good relationship for us.
I've been chosen for an advertisement.
Congratulations, Father.
I cannot let Hye-jun beat me.
You said you care about me.
Then what can you do for me?
How could you disappoint me
when I did all I could to support you?
I always tell myself
that I must be strong.
I don't want to rely on someone.
Someone of this era
who people can relate to
and find comfort in.
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs