RECORD OF YOUTH
THIS PROGRAM HAS BEEN SELECTED AS AN
"EXCELLENT BROADCAST CONTENT" AND IS SUPPORTED
BY THE MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS, TOURISM
AND THE KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
JI-A
Hey.
I met with a reporter today.
You'll see an article about it.
What do you mean?
Ji-a came to see me.
I'm not following.
This moody, selfish girl
chose to make a little sacrifice for you.
Hae-hyo is here. Let me talk to him first.
Ji-a is one thing,
but shouldn't you have told me
before she met the reporter?
-That's why I'm here.
-You came too late.
Are you mad at me?
I wanted to help you.
I cooperated because I thought
it'd be helpful for you.
-Is that so wrong?
-With some help, you must refuse it.
That's the case with Ji-a's help.
You've changed.
-How?
-The Sa Hye-jun I used to know
would have been grateful to the people
who are trying to help him.
Don't you see that I'm upset
because I'm grateful?
I don't want to have to make lame excuses.
The truth will come out with time,
so I just need to hold this out.
I'm offering to make those lame excuses
on your behalf.
You'd step in and help
if I were in this situation.
The old you would have.
Why do you keep saying that I've changed?
Look at yourself.
You never used to be like this.
You always respected my opinion
and consulted me first.
You no longer have time for that.
You're always busy.
You're with Jeong-ha when you're free.
You don't have time for us.
And Jin-u is dating Hae-na.
What is this mess?
Jin-u and Hae-na…
When did you find out?
So,
you knew?
Those jerks…
You guys hid it from me?
You guys fooled me?
No. Just until Jin-u could tell you
himself…
What's with him?
I'm the one who should be angry now.
I guess guys fight just like girls do.
Don't guys tussle?
You two are such gentlemen.
In movies, I always see guys
punching each other.
Anyway, you should thank Ji-a
when you see her later.
I'm so grateful that she stepped in.
What did Hae-hyo and Ji-a talk about?
RECORD OF YOUTH
This isn't like you.
Your parents won't be happy about this.
Do you still like Hye-jun's girlfriend?
Learn to hide your emotions,
or Hye-jun will figure it out soon.
If he finds out, he'll be so hurt.
You know exactly where to poke.
You'll be a great lawyer.
I want to protect Hye-jun.
When we were together,
I did all sorts of things
to test him as well as my love.
He's the real deal.
That's my conclusion.
And now that he's taken,
I want him even more.
I'm glad to hear there's something
you can't have your way with.
I'm thrilled.
If I can't have him,
it means you have no hope whatsoever.
I'm sure you want things to work out
between me and Hye-jun.
Isn't that right?
I guess you are.
But Jeong-ha won't date just about anyone
even if she and Hye-jun break up.
And I do?
You're so good at insulting others.
Just call the reporter at Out News
and schedule a meeting for me.
Hey, we need another switch
and electrical outlet over here.
You already told us.
Just go back upstairs.
-Hey, are you here to monitor us?
-Fine. I'm going back upstairs.
Mr. Sa.
-You don't need to give us dinner.
-Were you going to stay for dinner?
-Go up and get some rest.
-Okay.
Looking good.
Come in.
-Hi.
-Yes.
Are you done?
I knew it. He didn't come back upstairs.
What do you mean?
I told him to rest up,
but he must've stepped out.
Why does he need to rest?
Is he not feeling well?
He won't let me tell you guys.
He saw a doctor for his shoulder,
and he was told he'll need
another surgery if he's not careful.
Can you talk to him?
He already had surgery,
but it didn't fully heal.
Can he keep working?
Of course not! But he's being stubborn.
He's too stubborn for his own good.
He takes after his mother,
so he's bullheaded.
I think he's embarrassed to face Hye-jun.
He was against Hye-jun's career choice.
Goodness.
Where have you been?
I was running errands.
Where are you going?
I think I got a job.
I have a meeting at the academy.
-Get going, then.
-What are you up to?
What do you think?
I have to fix up Hye-jun's room.
Can't you give me a ride?
I have to walk all the way down there
to take the bus.
I'm old, so I tire very easily.
You look a lot more energetic than I do.
So? Aren't you going to give me a ride?
I won't. Why should I?
I'd have nothing more to wish for
if you could just talk more nicely.
Then I'd be too perfect.
You're baffled
that you just said that, right?
It's because I started watching
a lot more TV thanks to Hye-jun.
Women love it
when men say stuff like this on TV.
That's because they're good looking.
It won't work if you do it.
Whose fault is it that I look like this?
You gave me nothing good.
-Can I put on some music?
-No, you can't.
Just go alone.
Why do you want me to come with you?
Because it'll bother me.
You'd be so bored
if you had to wait alone outside.
-Is this it?
-Yes.
Come on.
Hello.
You're here.
Did you hire a manager?
No, this is my son.
Oh, I see.
He doesn't resemble you at all.
Take a seat.
Let's sit down.
To be honest, it's still too early
for you to hire a manager.
Unless we work even harder
and bring you more work.
Why did you want to meet?
You got an offer for a TV commercial.
For a health supplement.
Really?
The pay must be pretty good.
Yes, it's for a TV commercial.
It's different from printed ads.
-Would you like something to drink?
-Sure, what do you have?
Well, sir.
Do you mind going down to the first floor
and picking up some beverages?
Why make my son do it?
I don't need to drink anything.
It's nothing difficult.
-What should I get?
-Hey, don't bother.
My gosh.
You must love your son very dearly.
I'll get the staff to do it.
Why make such a fuss?
I can just go pick it up.
Are you complaining that I'm caring?
I'm not complaining.
You're the one making a fuss.
You need to work on this.
Must you talk to me like this
in front of my instructor?
What is she going to think of me now?
And what about our family?
She will think we're a hot mess.
No, I won't. I'll go.
Hold on, ma'am.
Why did I ask you to tag along?
How embarrassing!
Should I leave, then?
No, stay until I'm done.
Goodness.
I'm so embarrassed.
THE FAIRNESS OF SA HYE-JUN'S
BEST ACTOR AWARD QUESTIONED
ISN'T SA HYE-JUN STILL A ROOKIE?
I DON'T GET HOW SOMEONE LIKE HIM
WON THE AWARD
Ae-suk!
-What's wrong?
-I get so angry every time I read these.
People at the broadcasting station
aren't idiots.
They gave him the award
because he deserved it.
Of course!
Hye-jun was the only qualified nominee.
People are still talking about that?
I was reading the malicious comments.
What? Those punks.
I must tell the members.
The Giving Tree, Hye-jun All the Way,
and Sa Hye-jun Gallery.
I'll get the fans together
to raise the funds to sue them.
Is it really necessary to sue them?
Yes. People support that these days.
That's the trend.
Then how come Ms. Lee isn't suing them?
Exactly. We're going to do it
because we're frustrated.
How long is Hye-jun's contract?
-I don't know.
-Find out.
He needs a bigger, better agency.
This agency is no good.
JJamppong? Is it a Chinese restaurant?
What's that?
Oh, I have to drop off
the side dishes at Hae-hyo's place,
so I made some for your family as well.
Great. I was wondering
what I should make for them
when Hye-jun's room is all done.
Is Yeong-nam working too?
-Yes, I think so.
-Ae-suk, Yeong-nam is…
It's nothing.
What is it?
Let's talk later.
I have to go to Hae-hyo's place.
Every time I come here,
I don't want to leave.
Thanks.
I'm off.
-The number you have dialed
-Won Hae-na.
is not available.
-So, is this your plan?
-Please leave a message after the beep.
How much longer
do you think you can avoid seeing
your mother?
MY DAUGHTER
Did you ignore my calls
when you were home?
-I'm sorry.
-Heading out to see Jin-u?
-Yes.
-Before you head out,
can you spare me
about ten minutes of your time?
If you can't, we'll talk later.
I can.
I've done some thinking.
-Are you going to get angry?
-No.
I'm not that close-minded.
You have to be faithful to one man
once you get married,
so I support you dating
as much as you can before that.
-Really?
-Of course,
I'd want to see you dating someone
who I approve of,
but it's okay. I understand
why you're charmed by Jin-u.
Thanks, Mom.
Just don't get pregnant.
And you can't marry him.
Have some fun and come home.
You don't approve at all.
Everything you have belongs to me.
I can claim ownership over you.
Your body is the only thing
you have sole control over.
I never asked you for anything,
so why claim ownership?
I obeyed my parents.
I have to live like that
just because you did?
Yes.
Go meet up with Jin-u.
Have fun with him.
And learn how painful it is
to have a relationship
that has no future.
It'll help you grow.
Mom, you're much scarier than I thought.
I kept giving you guidelines,
and you stayed within them.
That's why we got along so far.
You ruined our relationship.
If it's ruined already
and we can't put it back together,
we should reset it.
-No.
-I don't want to either.
Then I'll have to impose you
with some restrictions.
What kind of restrictions are put in place
when international conflicts occur?
Do you want the credit card or the car?
You're so smart.
Which one will affect you more?
Both, equally.
Don't try to fool me.
I think the credit card
will affect you a lot more.
I'll go easy on you for now.
I'm taking your car away.
Give me your car keys.
All cleared.
Okay, go have fun with your boyfriend.
I'm happy you're dating.
And welcome to the real world.
I didn't think you'd be recording this.
If you want to help,
make it worth your while.
Sure, I want to.
You already know
which law firm you'll be joining, right?
How did you know?
My cousin works
at one of the big law firms.
The elders in our family
always compared us.
Did you date Hye-jun for a long time?
Why is she being so rude?
We were together
all through our early to mid-20s.
I know everything about him
during those years.
Okay, we're ready.
Your love is over,
but you're staying loyal to him.
But is it actually over?
It's none of your business.
I can't stand her.
Should I look at the camera?
Jin-u!
Hae-na!
Didn't your mom find out?
My mom said we can date.
Your mom is amazing.
I was worried for nothing.
We had such a narrow outlook.
My mom is so creative.
For the first time ever,
I realized I would never beat her.
Why beat your mom?
That was never my intention.
Otherwise, I would have never
kept our relationship a secret.
You're a bigger coward than I am.
Yes, I am a coward.
Marriage is reality
whereas dating is like a fantasy.
Going from fantasy to reality…
I don't want to do that.
I see.
I can trust you more now.
Because I now know
you're not recklessly emotional.
It's because I love you.
What? Did that make your heart skip?
-No!
-It clearly did.
What? I'm sure he has a lot
to deal with now. Why is he calling?
Hey, Sa Hye-jun.
How's it going?
Not good. How did you know?
Let's meet. Come to our usual spot.
I'm sorry I've been neglecting you guys.
JJAMPPONG ENTERTAINMENT
Come in.
I'm stepping out for a while.
Call me when you're done.
Okay.
Have a seat.
The office is smaller than I expected.
-You should move to a bigger space.
-This is the right size for us.
Do you want some tea?
I don't want you
to come back into my life.
I always do the opposite of what you want.
And that's how I tested your love.
It took me a while to realize
that was your way of testing me.
And I concluded I couldn't put up
with being tested all the time.
Let's relax around each other now.
Now, I know
that we can't get back together.
And I've also accepted the fact
that we can't even be friends.
Thanks.
I was very happy to see you doing so well.
But I'm the only one who can destroy you.
I cannot allow others to harm you.
So?
Well, I proved
that Sa Hye-jun likes women.
I was happy I could do that for you.
I'm no longer indebted to you.
I didn't know you thought
you were indebted to me.
I have a heart too.
You seem to think
that I'm a horrible person.
I did many things
to make you think that about me,
but I regret it now.
Back then, I thought
I was being considerate of you.
Your skin turns red
at the slightest touch.
You have combination skin
that is also very sensitive.
The lack of sleep is making it worse.
It's your wedding anniversary.
You're doing a photo shoot,
so I understand why you're nervous.
I'll apply some calming cream first.
I love this one-client setup.
I feel like a princess.
Please visit us often.
I hope you don't become too famous
so this can be my secret.
Thank you. I'll take that as a compliment.
HAE-HYO
1.1 MILLION FOLLOWERS
You look very comfortable.
Is this your office?
No, it's not.
But you pay all the expenses
with the money that I earn.
That prick is trying to take credit
for everything again.
-It's just so odd.
-What?
Hae-hyo's follower count. It's too high.
It's none of your business.
I tend to pry
when I'm fixated on something.
If he'd hired one of those companies
like you said, then I'd understand.
Okay, let's say he did.
But why is that any of your business?
He's too perfect.
That comfortable, well-off vibe he exudes
bothers me.
As you know,
my self-esteem has hit rock bottom.
I'll feel much better
if he turns out to be someone
who resorts to such tricks to get ahead.
"Rich people are not all that different."
In that sense, I guess popularity is fair.
It's not something you can buy.
My gut tells me that he did it.
Oh, you're still here.
Gosh, Won Hae-na…
I'll put the side dishes in the fridge.
Please let me know what to make next.
I must tell her to quit.
Jin-u's mother is a good cook.
It's seasoned perfectly.
And it tastes light and clean.
That's why I'm putting up with a lot.
Just so you can eat good food.
Thank you so very much.
Keep on putting up with her, then.
Where's the list?
I have to tell her to quit.
What's in season now? I don't have
much of an appetite these days.
Well…
How about something spicy?
Deodeok seasoned with gochujang.
Don't use gochujang.
Grill it with some sweet rice flour.
Why don't you make it here?
It's best when it's fresh.
-What about braised semi-dried pollock?
-I'd love that!
What? You can't tell her to quit
because of these side dishes?
I make really good braised monkfish.
My gosh!
Now, I'm craving braised monkfish.
I'll make some for you.
Delicious food
is the best remedy for stress.
Why would I be stressed?
You're not?
No, I'm not.
You're too quick to make assumptions.
Bad press is better than no press.
No one talks about Hae-hyo,
so I thought you'd be upset.
No, it's the opposite.
Also, stop comparing Hae-hyo with Hye-jun.
Hae-hyo can do something else
if this doesn't work out.
He has many options.
"Option"? What is that?
I mean, he has many choices.
I see. You could've worded it like that
in the first place.
I didn't understand what you meant.
I should use that word.
Anyway, take care.
I must tell her.
Don't come back.
I've said it.
It's her fault for not hearing me
and coming back.
I guess you're not that busy.
I told her, and she wants to meet you.
That actress I mentioned.
Thanks. Who is it?
-I'll give you her number.
-My gosh.
This big brother always does
something for you.
But look at you.
Even now, I made time to come here.
And what? "I guess you're not that busy"?
I'm not sorry anymore.
I want to tease you again.
-"Big brother"? When's your birthday?
-September 27. When's yours?
November 4.
Hi, big bro.
Hey, don't do that.
Jeez.
-Let's go eat.
-I have to go home.
Why do you always say that
when you see me?
Why today of all days?
I have to get ready for my live broadcast.
Are you going to be a YouTuber today?
You don't even have many subscribers.
It's because I'm not focusing on it,
and I don't plan to.
I'm just going to treat it as my diary
and use it to communicate with others.
What will you talk about today?
Watch it later if you're curious.
Did you see Hye-jun?
I did, but I'm not happy.
He's neglecting his friends
because of his girlfriend.
Way to go, Hye-jun.
When did you see him?
I've just been texting him.
I know he's busy and tired,
so I don't want to ask him to meet up.
And I don't want to ask him
about the rumors.
Why can't you?
You said your relationship is solid.
I'm just waiting for him to tell me first.
I was never good at waiting,
but I've changed.
I guess you love him.
That's what love does to you.
You begin to like things you couldn't do.
Why are you single
when you know so much about love?
You're so naive.
Let's go. I'll give you a ride.
It's Hye-jun's job, but I'll do it.
I'd never make him do it.
I'd just tell him to go home and rest.
Hurry up.
Okay.
-Cheers!
It's so refreshing.
It's been so long since I last drank.
You've been working too hard.
Are you a workaholic now?
You never take a break.
Working relaxes me.
I want to work a lot while I'm in my 20s.
Right.
After we serve in the military
and turn 30,
things will be different.
Gosh, the military. When should I enlist?
Hey, you have to postpone it
as much as you can.
Work while you can.
Your next show… Yes, The First Human!
That's one grand title.
You'll see Hae-hyo often
because you're both in it.
I was excited to work with him,
but he snapped at me earlier.
I'm sure you did too.
Right, I did.
It's nice having childhood friends.
Why did you snap at him?
Because of Ji-a's interview.
But what if
Jeong-ha sees that interview?
Why are you following me?
I don't want to talk to you.
I'm going to keep trying to talk to you.
Did you see this?
It's an exclusive interview with Ji-a.
EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW
WITH SA HYE-JUN'S EX-GIRLFRIEND
I guess Hye-jun really is popular.
An exclusive at this hour?
I know. What were you up to?
I'll watch Jeong-ha's live broadcast.
LIVE BROADCAST NOTIFICATION
The broadcast is called "confession."
What is she confessing?
I don't know.
LIVE BROADCAST
It's a live broadcast.
It sounds grand since I titled
the broadcast, "confession."
"Is it about your boyfriend?"
Is she going to talk about Hye-jun?
Is it about my boyfriend?
Yes, it is.
HYE-JUN
Let me pause for a second.
I'll be back shortly.
Hey, Hye-jun.
I'm sorry, Jeong-ha.
Why are you apologizing to me?
I want to tell you the full story
in person.
There's an article about me.
I should've given you a heads-up
before it was published.
I only found out after the interview.
What is the article about?
And who did the interview?
Where is everyone?
THEY LEFT TO WATCH THE INTERVIEW
WITH SA-HYE JUN'S EX
I see.
WHO'S YOUR BOYFRIEND?
WEREN'T YOU GOING TO TELL US?
Right. I wanted to tell you guys
that you are my boyfriends.
To show my appreciation, I'd like
to give away a voucher for my studio.
Let's go. You should call Hae-hyo.
-Now?
-Yes. Let's make up today.
Both of us shouldn't drag this out.
-Be careful.
-Yes.
Can you take a photo with us?
If you promise not to post it online.
We won't.
-That's a promise.
-Yes.
One, two, three.
-Thank you.
HIS FACE IS TINY AND HAS PERFECT SKIN
HE SEEMED TO LIKE TO DRINK
HE WAS WITH HIS BOYFRIEND
EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW
WITH SA HYE-JUN'S EX-GIRLFRIEND
WE DATED IN COLLEGE
HE IS NOT GAY
He doesn't know
that I'm doing this interview.
If he knew, he would have stopped me.
He hates to inconvenience others
for his sake.
He was a good person and a good boyfriend.
I wanted to tell people that he wouldn't
do anything that deserves any criticism.
I'm so grateful to her.
His ex is helpful,
and has a new girlfriend. Lucky him.
You're still single, right?
Yes, I am.
Don't sound so proud.
You have a job now.
Why are you still single?
He never dated even in school.
Dad, you're upsetting me these days.
You don't love me as much as you used to.
I bet Hye-jun gave you money.
Why won't you answer me?
Why not?
SA HYE-JUN HAS TRANSFERRED MONEY
TO HAN AE-SUK
Do you remember?
When I was in middle school,
I promised if I made a lot of money,
I would give you a comfortable life.
I didn't forget my promise.
When I grow up, I'll earn a lot of money,
so you can live comfortably.
I'll do the same.
I'll give you all the support you need
so you can do what you want.
I thought you were cooking.
Are you crying?
What's this?
We'll be able to pay off the debt.
And we'll have some left.
I could never make this much money
even if I worked all my life.
He earned this much money in a year.
It took more than a year.
Think about everything
he had to go through for this.
That breaks my heart.
He didn't forget his promise to me.
When he told me
he was going to help me live comfortably
once he grew up,
I said I would give him
all the support he needed
to do whatever he wanted.
But I couldn't keep my promise.
I don't want to take this money.
Father, are you going to sleep now?
Yes, I am.
Do you have Hye-jun's agent's number?
I have her business card. Why?
Do you know what Gyeong-jun just said?
Do you really think nothing happened
between them?
I mean, this rumor
must have started from somewhere.
Instead of blindly siding with him,
we must see if it's reasonable to doubt.
You're his brother.
How could you say that?
Think about how others would think.
His agency isn't dealing properly, too.
We should pressure his agency.
Don't do that.
What do you mean, Father?
Don't pressure his agency.
Just stick to
what you've been doing so far.
It will only get on his nerves.
Out of all people, you should be
the last person to do so.
-Hello?
-Hi.
This is Hye-jun's father.
Hello, sir.
I called because I had some questions.
Sure. Go ahead.
When does Hye-jun's contract
with the agency mature?
He's not home yet,
so I'm asking you directly.
I see. I didn't think
to check the contract.
It has already matured.
It was a one-year contract.
We have to renew the contract now.
But when we drew up the contract,
there was a clause that
we could end the contract
if one of us isn't happy.
Did Hye-jun say he was unhappy
with his contract?
Did he?
What did Jeong-ha say?
What do you think?
She probably feels awful.
Shouldn't you see her instead of Hae-hyo?
You know what?
The less my affection is,
the less humiliated I feel.
What?
The way they're spreading rumors about me
is embarrassing.
It makes me feel naked.
Back then,
whatever happened to me,
my family didn't know about it
before I told them.
Right.
But now, they know it
even before I tell them.
They worry about me.
I don't know why that's hurting
my self-esteem.
Is that why you got mad at Hae-hyo?
But I don't feel that embarrassed
in front of him.
He gets hate comments, too.
We're in the same boat,
so it doesn't bother me.
Tell me you're embarrassed in front of me.
That means you love me, right?
Crazy jerk. Get away from me.
Don't be so harsh on me.
Hae-hyo might beat me up later.
I see Hae-hyo over there.
You're dead meat.
-What's up?
-You sure took your time.
Did you know that I knew? Or didn't you?
-I knew.
-How can you think about dating my sister?
I didn't think much, you know.
-Right. You never think, do you?
-Yes.
Didn't you think to tell me?
No way. So you could beat me up?
So you were expecting it.
Let me punch you first.
Okay. Which side? Right or left?
Damn it.
Hey, Hye-jun. Save me.
He's going to kill me!
Where's Hye-jun?
He's not here?
He's here somewhere.
He said he needed to make up
with you in person.
Really?
Is he sorry about throwing a tantrum?
I can smell alcohol on you.
I had a few drinks.
I just opened a cold one. Do you want one?
Yes. I'll get it.
How did you get here?
I took a cab. I drank with Jin-u.
The guys were not happy with me.
They feel neglected because I've been
paying attention only to you.
That's what Hae-hyo said earlier.
You saw him?
Yes, he stopped by my studio.
I'm really grateful to him.
He'll set me up with a famous actress.
I want to prepare myself thoroughly,
so I can be her makeup artist.
Hae-hyo might win you over.
That won't happen.
You're always my top priority.
-I love you.
-I double-love you.
I have a business trip next week.
I'm doing Kim So-rang's makeup
for her movie.
I was able to get a celebrity client
all on my own.
Congratulations.
Did you watch Ji-a's interview?
I did.
It didn't feel good.
I'm telling you before you ask me.
Thank you for saving us some time.
-She's pretty.
-Not as pretty as you.
So she is pretty, then.
-I'm sorry.
-I like that you apologized quickly.
Well,
when something like this happens,
why do you not discuss it with me?
Why did you make me worry all by myself?
You're very calm when you get angry.
That's a good thing. It's scarier.
I want to show and tell you
only the good things.
-I want--
-Am I your kid?
That's what parents tell their children.
I can put up with those hateful comments
because they aren't true.
But
I don't want my family or you to find out.
The fact that the people I love
have seen those comments
hurts my self-esteem.
The people you love
want to share your burden with you.
You only disappoint them
by hiding it from them.
I love you
more than you think.
SA HYE-JUN CONFIRMED
TO STAR IN THE FIRST HUMAN
A NEW PROJECT ALREADY?
HE'S GREEDY FOR MONEY
IS HE REALLY NOT GAY? THE DEAD CAN'T SPEAK
WHO KNOWS?
THE INTERVIEW MIGHT BE STAGED
People just believe
whatever they want to believe.
The interview didn't help at all.
Why did Hye-jun's father want to see you?
I don't know. Is Hye-jun up?
I hope our meeting
wasn't too early for you.
It's fine. I just left
a few minutes earlier than usual.
You didn't have breakfast, right?
-Have some of this.
-Thank you.
I hope it's to your liking.
I like everything.
You're already here.
Yes.
He wanted to talk to me.
About what?
You can talk to me.
I was just curious about how she is
handling those vicious comments.
There's nothing to worry about.
Did you file a lawsuit?
We kept finding more comments.
As we can't gather all of them at once,
we'll file the first lawsuit for now.
I see. That's what's happening.
People don't know anything.
Did they say something?
Well, you know, I just read some comments.
You're here, Ms. Lee.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-Ms. Lee.
-Yes.
Can you drop me off at work on your way?
Gyeong-jun.
She's my agent, not yours.
You should leave now.
You're so rigid. I'll get going.
-See you around.
-Have a good day.
Thanks.
-Dad.
-Yes?
Can I talk to you?
Dad,
I know that you're concerned,
but I can handle this by myself.
Of course. I know that you can handle it.
I was just worried.
Min-jae is my agent.
She believed in me when I had nothing,
and she works hard to keep me motivated.
I'm not arguing with it.
Let me be the person who talks to her.
I don't want to hurt her.
Treat me like that, too.
Okay.
Gosh. He sounds like the CEO of an agency.
Why can't I argue with him?
Why not?
Why can't I?
Why is that?
Gosh.
Ma'am.
Goodness, it's been a while, Hae-hyo.
You're so busy that
I don't get to see you when I come.
I heard you're in a series with Hye-jun.
Yes. He has the leading role,
and I have the supporting role.
It doesn't matter who has the lead.
Only the roles matter.
Looking at Hye-jun,
fame really does happen overnight.
He woke up one day to find himself famous.
That can happen to you, too.
Thank you.
Where is my mom?
She went out. She's meeting someone.
But she didn't seem excited
about the meeting.
Stop.
I don't want to eat with you.
Why must we talk over a meal?
You know, I never forget
to give credit where credit's due.
Ms. Kim, thanks to you,
I met Mr. Yoon and got a big return.
I ought to show my appreciation.
If you truly mean that,
don't pick and choose.
You must be honest with every situation.
Park Do-ha was the one
who got Hae-hyo in Catch.
I am very offended.
Why did you lie to me?
I won't be making
any more introductions to you.
It was only a friendly prank
to get close to you,
so I can't believe
you took me for my word.
Life is full of deceptions.
People only realize it
when they're the victims.
Hae-hyo has an extremely high number
of followers on social media.
What is he getting at?
What does him
being popular on social media have
anything to do with this?
You know how that's possible.
I've bought them with money before too.
Quite simple, isn't it?
It only takes a few clicks.
As if I'd admit to it.
How should I know if it's simple or not?
I agreed to meet you
only because I'm a decent human being
even though I didn't want to.
-Our relationship ends here.
-No can do.
I'll be good, I-yeong.
What did you call me?
You're too young and pretty
to be called "ma'am."
Who'd guess that you're Hae-hyo's mom?
You think I'm some pushover, don't you?
If you thought you could
laugh things over with me,
I urge you to reconsider. Re-evaluate.
Got it.
I'll re-evaluate my situation
and do my best to get on your good side.
After the interview,
you're needed in Gangnam.
What do you want to eat?
Something light.
A sandwich and melon smoothie then.
Today, I'm here with Sa Hye-jun,
one of the hottest actors
that's been trending.
Can you greet the viewers
of Memory Talk Talk?
Hello, I'm actor Sa Hye-jun.
This is your first interview following
your Best Actor Award last year.
Right.
Aren't you here to promote
your new series The First Human?
I am.
The First Human deals with
the power struggle and romance
of young adults born
into prestigious families.
You're known for your dreamy gazes.
I'm curious about how you'll portray
the romance between you
and your partner Jin Seo-u.
How will it be?
It's too early to say,
but I'm curious
about our chemistry as well
since we used to model together.
Don't come any closer.
We…
broke up.
Did you forget that?
I knew it.
You can't live without me.
Cut. We'll take a short break.
It sure is awkward
to do scenes like this with you.
"You can't live without me."
-Stop it.
-Stop what?
You haven't changed at all.
Likewise.
-You're glistening a bit.
-I had to dance, remember?
My regular makeup artist
took her maternity leave.
Someone new took over,
but she's not considerate enough.
Then can I introduce you
to a makeup artist
who is skilled with her hands
and warm at heart?
Are you vouching for your girlfriend?
-How did you know?
-A hunch.
-Give me her number then.
-Sure.
-I guess you'll need your phone.
-I have it memorized.
Well, hello, lover boy.
Are you filming tomorrow?
-I'll be at it with Hae-hyo.
-Hae-hyo?
Oh, right.
Won't it get physical between you two?
I'll be beating him up.
I'd love to come by and watch.
-You should.
-Can I?
But won't you lose in a fight?
What? Why do you always say that?
Aren't you exhausted?
Even on a tight schedule,
your face keeps glowing.
Maybe it's the red ginseng.
You were born this way, Mr. Workaholic.
He's heading overseas
for his fan meet-up event tomorrow.
-So?
-You called him a workaholic,
so I thought I'd recite his schedule.
I'm filming later at night too.
I thought I'd recite my schedule too.
It feels good to say it.
Can you stop eating? You'll gain weight.
-How about slicked back hair?
-Yes, let's.
-We need to get going.
-Sure.
Gyeoksejigam is the word.
What does that mean?
Being astonished
at how much things have changed.
It's used in situations where
you feel like decades have passed
because the change is too drastic.
Yes, that's the one.
-You weren't sure?
-I knew the gist of it.
He sure has made it big.
The sight of him is blinding now.
Filming will begin in ten minutes!
Got it.
-He needs to get going.
-I'm almost done.
Hye-jun.
Hey, Hae-hyo.
-You made your big brother come to you.
-You're the younger one.
Jeong-ha came with me today.
She's the only help I have.
Hi.
Hi, Jeong-ha.
-Oh, hey.
-I've been doing well in your place.
I see. Is that so?
Well, let's get going.
Jeong-ha, could we talk?
Were you shocked
to see Yeong-jin in your place?
Hye-jun didn't ask me
for today's shooting,
so I figured.
Too many eyes are on Hye-jun now
for you to do
both his and Hae-hyo's makeup.
Of course.
I was going to call you to set things up,
but you had Hae-hyo to care for too,
so I didn't.
I thought I'd tell you today.
Good thinking.
He has countless events
and people to meet.
On top of that, being in this TV series
requires a makeup artist on standby.
It's why I had her promoted.
You'll be best as an observer right now.
Got it.
Managing his schedule
sure is tough enough.
REPORTER KIM SU-MAN
It's the reporter.
Just a second.
-Yes, Ms. Kim.
-Ms. Lee.
Mr. Sa's dating his makeup artist, right?
What are you talking about? No way.
Haven't you done enough damage?
First the article on Charlie Jung,
and then his ex-girlfriend's interview.
Why can't you leave him alone?
Once again,
you're barking up the wrong tree.
So I'm wrong?
Spread wrongful rumors again
and I'll take action.
Don't you dare write this article.
You do your job
and I'll do mine.
What's going on?
What do we do?
She's going to expose your relationship.
This is bad for Hye-jun.
His image will take a huge blow.
First his ex, now his current girlfriend?
This is bad. It's a terrible sign.
I'm going to sue her ass if she does it!
It's nice to work together.
-Right, Jeong-ha?
-Yes.
Just don't use me as a cover.
Can't you let us?
Okay, fine.
-Hey.
-What are you doing?
It'll only be believable
if she's by my side.
Is that so?
Yes, it is.
Besides, her standing with me
doesn't make her mine.
You two always claim ownership over things
that aren't even yours.
It's Seo-u. Take it.
-Hey.
-Hi, brothers.
It's too bad we don't
have any scenes together.
Are you filming today?
No, I'm here to practice.
Isn't it weird to be romantic with him?
Why would it be
when we're dating? Didn't you know that?
-Hey.
-What's with the sour-face?
That's just how I'll be thinking
while filming this series.
I can't afford this one to tank.
-We should grab a bite sometime.
-Sure.
Bye, Hae-hyo. Be nice to my boyfriend.
Bye!
What's with her?
She's being true to her character.
The show should be a hit.
We film the next scene in five.
-Sure.
-Got it.
Can you take a photo of us?
-Why?
-To savor the moment.
Don't you have a job out of town tomorrow?
Let me drive you there.
It's okay. I can take the bus.
Hye-jun's busy tomorrow morning,
and he'll head abroad
for a fan meet-up event.
-I didn't ask.
-I'm just saying.
ALARM 5:00 A.M.
HYE-JUN
You, who I have by my side,
are always the best.
"Out of sight, out of mind."
Not being within eyesight
makes someone grow distant.
I had faith
that our relationship was solid.
But faith
is much more fragile than love.
-Hi.
-Over here.
-Are you the assistant director?
-Yes, I am.
I'm here as Kim Song-yeon's makeup team.
-You're Su-cheol's friend, right?
-Yes.
She's in that van.
-Thank you.
-Thanks.
That wasn't what happened.
Come on. Let's start over.
Unbelievable.
It's almost midnight, damn it.
Could you lift your chin a bit?
Sure. Why can't they just be done with it?
I'm really sorry to ask,
but can you face straight ahead?
Don't try to be perfect
and be a little less dense.
The makeup around your lips,
nose, and cheeks have gotten flaky.
Are you patronizing me?
It may not seem like a big deal,
but it'll show on the screen.
Fine, just make it quick.
Are you done?
Be careful what you wish for.
So much for Mr. Workaholic.
Wake me up at the airport.
We're here.
But why do you hate rainy days?
It makes me feel like I'm all alone.
I'll call you when it rains.
You're not alone.
HYE-JUN
CALLING
You can come in.
Subtitle translation by: Hye-lim Park
RECORD OF YOUTH
She has an interview with Hae-ji
for a makeup job today.
Are you sleeping?
Now we have scandals round-the-clock.
What do you think people want to know?
-It's who he used to date.
-He seemed to be really competent.
Stay away from my family.
Did you know that you can pay
to increase the number of followers?
I wanted to prove
that I could make it on my own.
That's the one thing I asked you
to let me have!
What's this?
I want to make it up to you
for having been a lousy father.
Why did you call Hae-hyo first and not me?
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs