RECORD OF YOUTH
THIS PROGRAM HAS BEEN SELECTED AS AN
"EXCELLENT BROADCAST CONTENT" AND IS SUPPORTED
BY THE MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS, TOURISM
AND THE KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
Only one of you can survive.
No, more like…
"I can only survive if I kill you."
Let's do this. You know what to do.
You guys are pros. All right.
Give me more intense eyes.
Nice.
Hye-jun, can you try to relax a little?
-Oh, sure.
-Just be natural.
-Can you blot Hye-jun's face?
-Sure.
-Thank you.
-No problem.
-Do I look okay?
-You have an amazing friend.
We were going to only interview Hae-hyo.
-Let's resume the shoot.
-All right, let's do this.
Let's do this!
All right. Look at the camera, please.
Great. Nice.
Hey.
Ji-hun has been discharged.
We're meeting up later. Come with me.
Later? What time?
Let's get changed. You should wear this.
Can't I just wear this?
You're meeting with the director.
You look like a punk in that outfit.
He'd never look like a punk
no matter what he wears.
Right? He exaggerates sometimes.
Can I take Hye-jun to the meeting?
Just get changed, okay?
Yes, get changed. I'm off.
See you at eight.
I don't think I can make it.
-Why not? Do you have plans?
-No, I just don't want to go.
-But why?
-I don't want to tell you.
Why are you acting like a teenage boy
these days?
Why don't you want to tell me?
You never told me last time.
I know you're trying to help me out.
-Then be good to me.
-But the thing is…
Today, it makes me feel…
I mean, I can't really explain it,
but something's flaring up deep inside.
Right, it's been a while
since we last fought.
You didn't do anything wrong though.
It's just me.
Today, I just can't take it.
My self-esteem has hit rock bottom.
Because I suggested you tag along?
Or because of the shoot?
Yes, both. And my dad.
RECORD OF YOUTH
EPISODE 3
You're back.
It really isn't fun at all.
I can't even hit the ball,
but I have to do it for business' sake.
Didn't she say that she enjoys golf
more than anything else?
Am I here alone? Say something.
You once said you enjoy golf
more than anything else.
Right, I do enjoy it.
But you can still get sick of it
if you keep doing it.
Isn't it nice to do what you enjoy
until you get sick of it?
I'd just be grateful if I were you.
But our situations are different.
Just because
Hae-hyo and Hye-jun are friends,
it doesn't mean we're friends.
"Friends"? Of course, we're not.
I'm younger than you.
I mean, this isn't the US.
Well, you didn't have to
draw the line like that.
Come with me.
This one.
And this one.
This one too.
She always does this. I can't hate her.
This one is no good, right?
I'll take it. I can get it altered.
I'm not throwing them out.
I just don't love them anymore.
I wouldn't care even if you were.
I like how things like this
doesn't bother you.
I mean, it'd bother me.
Why would it bother me?
These are better than the clothes
that I buy.
Right, I like that mindset.
You must be upset because of Hye-jun.
If he joins the military,
his career will be over.
Why is she bringing him up
all of a sudden?
Too bad he lost to Hae-hyo, of all people.
I think Hae-hyo feels bad.
I'm not worried about him.
He'll figure out what's best for him.
Right, I know you have to say that.
I understand.
No, you'll never understand
because our situations are different.
I'm a very empathic person.
Thank you for these clothes.
What? You don't think I am?
Come on. I'm so good to you!
You call this a good job?
You said it'd be different
once I put on the dress.
You call this bridal makeup?
We discussed all the details
and decided everything together.
You said you wanted to look
natural and elegant, so I--
Why are you talking back to me?
I'm getting married today.
I'm sorry. I'll redo your makeup.
Should I emphasize the eyes more?
MESSAGE
SU-BIN
I hope these can bring
some vicarious pleasure.
You should beat Jin-ju.
You should beat her at least once.
If you lose even with my help,
you’re a fool.
I am a fool indeed.
Hello.
I'm Lee Min-jae, Sa Hye-jun's manager.
-Oh, hello.
-This is for you.
Hello.
I'm Lee Min-jae, Sa Hye-jun's manager.
Please contact us
when you have another movie coming up.
He'll do a better job next time.
He's pretty good,
but he's not that well-known yet.
What's going on?
Has coming all the way here
become your new hobby or something?
I've been thinking a lot
since we came back from Milan.
-Why are you all serious?
-I'll be your manager.
-Min-jae.
-Postpone your enlistment.
Taking a two-year hiatus now
will kill your career.
I've already decided.
Do you know why you didn’t get the role?
The director liked you at first,
but Hae-hyo has more followers than you.
So they went with him.
You lost because of popularity,
not because of your acting.
But that's part of your competence.
Trust me just this once.
I'm over 40 now, and I've finally
found something I truly enjoy doing.
I'm sorry, Min-jae.
Try giving your all
at least once in your life.
Get home safely.
Hye-jun, I even got
my business cards made.
"JJamppong Entertainment"? Seriously?
Yes, it sums up
what my life has been like.
It's like a representation of me.
There is no better word.
Who else is at JJamppong?
You're the only artist.
Forget it, then. You weren't
in your right mind when you did this.
-No, I can't do that.
-Then don't.
It's your life, so stick to your plan.
But leave me out of this.
Hye-jun, wait.
Hye-jun!
You're making a mistake!
Think again for your future's sake!
That fool! Goodness!
I know you told me to beat her,
but I lost.
AN JEONG-HA
I thought you might be curious.
I was hesitant but wanted to tell you.
My grandpa said that sometimes,
losing is winning.
SA HYE-JUN
Which means, you won.
What are you up to now?
Hey, you.
Don't come so close.
What if people see us?
Who cares?
Are you getting funny ideas?
What funny ideas?
Also, that's not a nice habit.
What's with that finger? Are you trying
to criticize me or something?
No, I'm pointing at you
because I'm talking to you.
I can't do that?
You can.
Do you come here often?
It's one of the places I visit
when I'm sad.
You're sad?
I'm feeling down.
Me too.
Thanks.
-For not asking why I'm feeling down.
-Why are you feeling down?
Do you want to drink something?
From outside, everyone looks so happy.
I said we should drink something inside.
I said everyone "looks" happy.
I never said they're actually happy.
Buying coffee is such a waste of money.
It's too expensive.
I said I'd treat you.
It's my money, not yours.
Either way, I just hate wasting money.
You seem very comfortable
talking about money.
Most people aren't.
Money is like poop.
It's a difficult topic to bring up,
but you're screwed if there's a problem.
It sounds like you're speaking
from experience. Am I wrong?
RECEIPT
Gosh, again?
Hello, Mr. Kim.
This is An Jeong-ha from the support team.
We're missing the receipt from
your transaction at Jangmo BBQ,
on October 8. A total of 97,000 won.
You must submit a receipt for anything
over 30,000 won. I've told you.
No, I can't. The deadline is today.
Find the receipt, please.
People are so irresponsible
when it's not their money.
-Jeong-ha.
-Sir.
About Mr. Kim's receipt…
Just write it off for him.
Gosh, please don't be like this.
Just do as you're told, will you?
Back in my day,
I always obeyed my superiors' orders.
-How dare you glare at me…
-When they say, "Back in my day,"
it means they want you
to just shut up and listen.
Back in my day,
I didn't get paid
for the shows that I did.
Kids these days are money-greedy.
Back in my day, I could never think
of leaving work on time.
How could you people
leave right on the dot?
-Show some devotion.
-We're so good at this.
We shouldn't do this to
people when we're older.
Agreed.
But I'm craving a latte now.
Me too, actually.
Shall we sit inside?
You don't want to waste money?
I'll just compromise my principles.
You have foam on your lips.
So do you.
Hi, Grandpa.
What? What is wrong with this?
I hung up because I didn't want you
to pay an expensive phone bill.
Why call me back?
I get 30 minutes of free video calling.
You don't want to see my face?
I do, of course. Why aren't you home yet?
I'll be home soon.
By the way, have you looked into it?
Yes, I'm still looking into it.
Gosh, you're so impatient.
My day is shorter than yours.
Stop rushing me, please.
This is my friend, Jeong-ha.
-Hello, sir.
-Hi.
My, what a pretty lady.
You can't say stuff like that these days.
No, it's fine. I like it
when someone tells me I'm pretty.
I've never seen a woman
who doesn't like to be told she's pretty.
Even your grandma…
Gosh, this means you'll go on
for at least 30 minutes.
Okay, I'll hang up now.
-Bye!
-Bye, take care--
Oh, he's gone.
I guess you take after your grandpa.
He's very handsome.
He's also tall for someone his age.
-Do you want to see him?
-Yes.
Let me see.
Isn't this too close?
Right, sorry.
He could've been an actor.
Why didn't he get into acting?
He couldn't. He was conned several times.
He trusts people too easily.
Being trusting is a good thing.
Those who con others are the bad ones.
You're pretty good at lecturing others.
Sorry. By the way,
what did he ask you to look into?
He wants to get a job.
Do you think it's possible?
You won't find anything
if you think it's impossible.
Good point.
-Hey, you made it.
-Hi.
-Hello.
-It's been a while.
How have you been?
-Hye-jun didn't tag along today?
-That's rude.
You always bring him whenever we meet up.
I guess we can relax and talk today, then.
About what?
I recommended you to my dad
as the face of our beauty brand.
My dad is on board.
Hi, you draft evader.
Don't be like that. I'll enlist soon.
Just like how age matters,
the one who enlists first
deserves more respect.
Pour me some drinks.
Is that so? All right, sir.
-Let me pour you one.
-Sure thing.
You seem to be really enjoying it.
I can't stop eating.
You've been suppressing yourself too much.
That's true.
I'm happy now.
Me too.
-Stop copying me.
-You told me to copy you.
We got together too late.
You were too young.
You were too busy dating other girls.
Gosh, you're at it again?
But you're my first.
This is also my first time
dating someone knowing we'll break up.
Sure.
Whatever it is,
the first time is always exciting.
Also, don't you think
it makes us become more passionate?
No.
You wanted this.
Don't beg me in tears
to change my mind because I won't.
I will never beg anyone in tears, ever.
-I'm leaving.
-Okay.
This is the script for the movie
that Hae-hyo will be shooting.
I think it'll be a huge hit.
It's so engaging.
I see.
I never asked.
The wardrobe for the character…
And I also need to help him
practice his lines.
Gosh, I have so much to do.
You know, kids these days
can take care of things on their own.
Do you think Hae-hyo got this role
solely on his own?
These days, parents need
to help their children all their lives.
Then there's no hope for this world.
How can parents possibly
help their kids with everything?
Are you saying I'm wrong?
I shouldn't even live if I can't speak out
when someone says that my child
will turn out like me.
I'm just saying
some might think differently.
Wrong opinions should be corrected.
Let me put it in simple terms.
Had Hye-jun been my son,
he would've gotten this role.
Life is like a race. You never know
who's going to win until it's over.
We don't know whether that role
will do him good or harm.
I guess time will tell.
Are you putting a curse on him?
Are you saying it may do him harm?
No. You said my opinion was incorrect,
and I'm just telling you
that is not the case.
Look at you getting all smart with me.
I've just been keeping things to myself.
Because you wouldn't understand
even if I told you.
SIS
Someone's calling you!
Oh, no!
Ms. Han!
My gosh…
Gosh, this is crocodile skin.
It can't get wet.
But crocodiles live in water.
Why can't it get wet?
Gosh, just go bring some tissues.
It's okay. Forget it!
-I'm home.
-Hey, you're back.
Hello, ma'am.
"Ma'am"?
Oh, hey. It's been a while.
Do you know her?
She's Hye-jun's mother.
You remember Hye-jun, right?
Oh, Hye-jun!
She's Hye-jun's mother?
Throw this in the recycling bin
on your way out.
Sure. It looks totally fine though.
Who wears clothes until they're worn out?
Can I take this?
What for?
That's none of my business.
Sure, suit yourself.
-Mom.
-Oh, hi.
Why are you out here?
I'll buy you those basketball shoes
you wanted.
Nice! You're becoming more generous
now that you've started working.
-Does it make you happy?
-It does.
I work for Hae-hyo's family now.
-Are you shocked?
-No, I just lost my grip.
I'm going to keep the job. I'm really
happy that I can earn money now.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
I've had the job for three months,
and I think I can keep doing it.
I initially thought I might quit,
so I couldn't tell you.
I've finally found a job
that is perfect for me.
I love to clean and organize things,
you know.
But I can't be totally at ease
when I think about you.
I'll quit if the fact that I work
for your friend's family
as their housekeeper
makes you feel insecure.
I don't want to keep the job
if it upsets my son.
Mom, so you're saying
I'm more important to you than work?
Yes, of course.
But this is my life,
and you have your own.
You don't need to feel insecure
because of my life.
What should I do?
Give me some time to think about it.
Have you been waiting long?
Sorry, I got held up at work.
Oh, boy.
So you're done thinking?
What would you like me to do?
I thought about it and realized
that your life is your own,
so why should I be the one deciding?
My life gives me enough to worry about.
Hey, you're too young to say
things like that.
I'm already 16. I have a lot on my mind.
I'm starting high school next year,
but we're poor.
Anyway, it's your life,
so you can do whatever you want.
Sa Hye-jun, you rock.
I also love how thoughtful you are.
Thinking is what makes us human.
My son is the best.
When I grow up, I'll earn a lot of money
so you can live comfortably.
I'll do the same.
I'll give you all the support you need
so you can do what you want.
Liar.
I can't believe I duped my own son.
That was ten years ago,
but we're still struggling financially.
I wouldn't be in this mess now
if my dad were rich.
I'm a bad daughter.
Am I putting all the blame
on Mom and Dad now?
I miss her.
I miss Mom.
If she were alive,
I'd be so good to her.
What is wrong with me?
Why am I talking to myself?
Why am I becoming more and more
like my mother as I get older?
My, you're such a deft handyman.
You fixed that up in no time.
This is why you've accomplished this much
even without your parents' help at all.
Father, that's a bit of a stretch.
Couldn't you have
taken care of this sooner?
Do I have nothing to do?
Unlike you, I have a job.
Well, I was just saying…
I mean, in conclusion,
I just wanted to thank you.
Oh, hey. Ae-suk is back.
Hey, you're back.
Couldn't you come home sooner?
Look at the time!
Was I out playing?
Don't even talk to me.
Hey, what's with you?
How could you yell at her
for coming home late?
She must be exhausted
from working so late.
You're so understanding.
Why can't you be like that with me?
I'm always like this,
but your twisted mind just doesn't see it.
-Are you blaming me now?
-Thanks for fixing the door.
Did something happen?
Just tell me! How else would I know
what's going on?
What's the problem?
Once I start talking, you'll be screwed.
All right.
Do you want me gone? Or shall I stay here?
Okay, fine.
I'll figure it out on my own.
Where are you going?
Okay.
I should be patient.
Be patient.
It's raining.
Yes, it is.
I hate it when it rains.
Wait here.
I checked the forecast,
but it said it wouldn't rain.
But it's raining.
And now, you have an umbrella.
-What about you?
-I can take the bus from here.
It's not raining in my district.
How fascinating. The weather in Seoul
is different depending on the location.
Are you going to stand there?
You're getting rained on.
If not me, you'd get rained on.
That's why I bought this umbrella.
You're a smooth talker, aren't you?
Did you have an active dating life?
No, I didn't.
I tend to have
long and serious relationships.
I've only been in two relationships
with the same girl.
You're so eager to tell me everything,
but I didn't ask.
Have you ever been on a date?
Of course, I have.
A strong denial is an affirmation.
I had a lot of short relationships.
I tend to get bored very easily.
It wasn't your fear of getting hurt?
I can't deny that.
Gosh. I can't believe
we're talking about this.
I'm comfortable around you, too.
Me?
You tell me what's on your mind,
so I let my guard down.
We even talked about money.
And money can be a sensitive subject.
But why do you hate rainy days?
It makes me feel like I'm all alone.
I'll call you when it rains.
You're not alone.
You just gave me goosebumps.
That was so cheesy.
I can't listen to you anymore.
Hey. Hey!
You didn't put away the umbrella.
I can always stay rational.
You get cold when you get wet.
But don't good actors think about
emotions first?
That's why your acting is…
I can't let that slide.
I'm sorry.
Gosh, I know nothing about acting.
I was…
It will help no matter how small it is.
Should I cover your face?
No, I'll do it.
-You do it, then.
-Okay.
That's my bus.
Get home safely.
Go. I have to see you go first.
Okay. I will.
Hi, Mom.
No, I haven't gotten the money yet.
I will wire it when I can.
It's raining. I'm at the bus stop.
I know I need an umbrella.
I'm alone,
but it feels like I'm not alone.
This feels great.
DEPOSITED FROM FASHION PLAY
9,670,000 WON
Hey.
I just checked the wire transfer.
I think you sent the wrong amount.
It's too much.
Thank Mr. Jung.
You did a good job with the show.
He told me to give you a bonus.
When I get my makeup done by you,
it puts me in a good mood.
Thank you. I started out
later than other makeup artists.
So compliments make me happy.
That's nonsense.
I started modeling at the age of 65.
Does it mean you're new to this job?
I've been doing this for 13 years.
I'm 78 years old now.
Why do you sound so surprised?
I want to work for ten more years.
I'm sure you can work until you hit 100.
There's always a demand for senior models.
This is a commercial for red ginseng.
The director and I decided to go
with a powerful and trustworthy image.
By the way, have you looked into it?
Yes, I'm still looking into it.
He could've been an actor.
Why didn't he get into acting?
I was just about to call you.
All right.
You came out at the perfect timing.
Yes, I did.
Your mother made gimbap.
Gosh. She rarely makes gimbap
because it takes a long time.
She's being nice to me
because I got drafted.
What am I going to do when you're gone?
I'll miss you a lot.
Just wait 18 months.
Your 18 months
feel like 18 years to me.
No! You're moping. I don't like that.
Did you forget our motto?
"Despite the discrimination and scolding,
we'll smile."
Yes. A smile brings good luck.
I reheated the soup. It's good.
You've got skills, Grandpa.
Anything you do turns out well.
My gosh. You're the best.
You've done enough for me.
You should date.
You should date. I want to work now.
I think I might have some good news.
Did you already get me a job?
Where is it at?
I'm not sure yet.
I'll have to talk about it in person.
Who are you meeting?
VICTORY
Have you been well?
What? What brings you here?
I want to get my makeup done for my drama.
I see. Wait here.
Jin-ju will be here soon.
There she is.
I want you to do it.
No, I can't.
You're here.
-Hi.
-You didn't make an appointment.
No, I didn't.
I want Jeong-ha to do my makeup.
She said she couldn't do it,
but why is that?
It's because of our salon policy.
She's still an assistant.
Is that more important
than satisfying your client?
Of course, our clients come first.
Ms. An, you can do his makeup.
I'm not at that level yet.
I can raise your level.
And we can change the policy.
-Let's wash your hair first.
-This way, please.
How could you do this to me?
Shouldn't you reflect on yourself
and figure out
why the client didn't choose you?
My skin feels so silky now.
It felt so dry before.
I can tell you're good
from how you do the base makeup.
I can always spot who's good.
I knew it even before you did my makeup.
Please don't move.
-What are you doing?
-You told me not to move.
You can breathe.
Are you feeling better now?
What do you mean?
You were acting distant.
You totally iced me out.
I didn't know you knew such phrases.
Do you really think
the Internet knows me better?
I didn't even look into you that much
because I'm not interested in you.
That sounds like a challenge.
Once you get to know the real me,
you'll hopelessly be in love with me.
Is that so? How scary.
I will never get to know the real you
in this life.
Do you only want to know Hye-jun?
No. I already know enough about him.
I bet you like him even more now.
I know how great he is.
I liked him a lot even before we met.
I was his fan.
Right. You probably like him even more
now that you've met him.
Right. I do like him more.
So I'm trying
not to develop feelings for him.
Just follow your heart.
Why would you do that?
Being someone's fan is beautiful
when they don't exist in your world.
When your fantasy and reality crash,
it becomes a mess.
It'd be fun to see that mess.
Hello.
Where's Jeong-ha?
She's over there.
Did you like your makeup today?
You were kind enough to let me choose
my own makeup artist. Thank you.
I should thank you.
Well done, Ms. An.
What?
What are you doing here?
I should ask you the same thing.
Why do you think I'm here?
You guys seem like best friends.
-How long have you been friends?
-We went to the same elementary school.
Then, you must live in Hannam-dong.
Yes.
Both of your families are well-off.
So many celebrities these days
come from rich families.
Before, they used to
come from poor families.
Not everyone from Hannam-dong is rich.
You don't have to be so modest.
Oh, right.
What kind of tea would you like?
-Do you have iced Americano?
-Of course.
-I can get it for him.
-No.
A lot of my clients like me
because I know when to butt out.
The guys missed you the other day.
What did you do?
I should get going too.
I'll see you later.
-Are you here to see her?
-Yes. Is that the makeup for the drama?
Yes. I'll be done
with the shoot next week.
WRITER KIM JI-HYEON
Hey, Ji-hyeon.
Thank you.
I would like to do it since you asked.
But my agency must sign off
to be on a variety show.
I'm going to be
in Mr. Choi Se-hun's movie.
No, I don't know if it will be a hit.
We'll have to see how it goes.
Okay. Thank you.
I befriended her
when I was on a variety show before.
She's the main writer now.
Back then, she was an assistant.
A few male idol singers will be on it.
I guess she's doing a travel show.
Hey, what are you doing here? We're late.
I called. Why are you still here?
-Sorry.
-You're here too, Hye-jun.
-Are you on a project or something?
-No.
Then, why are you here?
Let's go. I'll call you
when I'm done with the shoot.
Okay.
What is this awesome job opportunity?
You're so impatient.
Wait, no. It's not this one.
My gosh. Why does this keep popping up?
There. This is the one.
Gosh.
Isn't this too close?
So what?
His lifelong dream was
becoming a celebrity.
This is the best way for him
to achieve his dream at his age.
I'm not trying to help him
fulfill his dream.
He's looking for a part-time job.
He's 71 now.
A lot of senior models in their 80s
are still active.
Having that kind of physical features
at his age is a talent itself.
No. Not this one.
You didn't even ask your grandfather.
You shouldn't be the one
to turn down this opportunity.
-You're funny.
-No one has told me that before.
I'll take it as a compliment.
You're very calm when you're angry.
I understand
that you might not like my idea,
but I don't think
you can deem my idea ridiculous.
I've seen a lot of senior models before.
But I've never thought
my grandpa could be one.
Maybe you didn't see it
because he's your grandpa.
Why would you say that?
Well…
People change.
He might be a different person
than you remember him to be.
That's not much of a compelling argument.
Then…
How about this?
You say you want
the best for your grandfather,
but truthfully,
you don't think he has what it takes.
-Don't cross the line.
-The line is meant to be crossed.
Still, this is wrong.
You're already half on board.
No, I'm not.
Where are you going?
I have things to sort out.
What time do you finish work?
Who is it?
What a sight.
What…
Hold on.
Just a second.
Have a seat.
Are you here to pick me up
after kicking me down?
I came to give you a snack.
Your favorite red bean bread.
Serve it.
Bossy much?
What is this?
I was paid for that gig on stage.
-It was more than I expected.
-So?
You paid for my plane ticket to Italy
and covered my expenses.
You're enlisting soon, so take it.
I wasn't expecting to be reimbursed.
That'd be wrong.
May I give you some advice?
No, don't. I'm sick and tired of those.
-You're not ambitious enough.
-Why bother to ask when I said no?
You actually chose a decent path.
Being an A-list star
is the best way to hit the jackpot.
The fame comes with money
to acquire real estate.
You receive money
just by showing your face.
There isn't much
to being successful in life.
Doing what you want,
eating delicious food,
getting married, and having kids.
It's all about enjoying your today.
Unless you're born into wealth,
you'll live poor most of your life.
Your situation never gets better, but…
But most don't realize it
until they're over 30.
In our 20s, we fantasize about
living our dreams.
But the smart ones figure it out early
that earning money
is better than wild dreams.
However, you're still lost
in that wild dream of yours.
Why must you star in Director Choi's film?
He's talented, I agree.
However, he could be the wrong one,
not you.
Don't give up until
you exhaust all the possibilities.
I can get back on track
once I'm discharged.
But who'll remember you
when people barely know you even now?
STAY AND IT'LL BE TOO LATE
OUR YOUTH WON'T BE OVER ANY TIME SOON
I couldn't explain it.
But deep down in my heart,
I felt something rising up.
I finally figured out what it was.
You and I shine in our own way.
You have an amazing friend.
We were going to only interview Hae-hyo.
Can I take Hye-jun to the meeting?
-Are you on a project or something?
-No.
Then, why are you here?
I can get back on track
once I'm discharged.
But who'll remember you
when people barely know you even now?
I fooled myself that not comparing myself
and competing against him was virtuous.
Now, I have no regrets.
Are you done?
What? So you don’t even call
before you come now?
I need to do something.
Right here?
Can you cut my hair with the hair clipper?
Do you want to go back
when you were seven years old?
I’m joining the military.
-When?
-In ten days.
Why are you cutting your hair off today?
Because I keep wanting to stay.
You sound like you're leaving for good.
The period of service
is shorter now, right?
That's easy for you to say.
Of course it is.
Still, why cut it ten days
before your enlistment date?
Having a buzz cut will only
remind you of what's to come.
-You're right.
-I know I am.
You make more of an argument than earlier.
Well, I'm a fast learner.
You're also good at praising yourself.
No, I'm only stating a fact.
Anyway, you should go.
Su-bin's still here.
Are you really Hae-hyo's fan?
-Yes, I am.
-I hate liars, you know.
Three, two, one.
Fine, I'm your fan, all right?
What the hell? Did he just leave?
Damn it.
Mom, don't we have maple syrup?
We probably do.
I can't find it.
Did you perhaps borrow
my small diamond stud earrings?
-No.
-Where did they go then?
They must be here somewhere.
So where's the maple syrup?
Search the kitchen! Why do you ask?
I want pancakes, that's why!
Gosh, where are my earrings?
Jeez.
Nice. That's what I'm talking about.
This is really pretty.
Hae-na and I must have the same taste.
I can't say that for our sizes though.
-Give them to Jin-ri.
-This isn't her style.
I should give them to my niece.
There are some pants too,
so keep them if you like.
Hae-hyo's mom and I
don't share the same taste.
-I'll get them to my sister-in-law.
-Sure thing.
HAE-HYO'S MOM
-Hello?
-Have you seen my diamond stud earrings?
-They're probably in their spot.
-They're not.
When did you place them?
-I can't remember.
-Maple syrup!
Where's the maple syrup?
On the third shelf
of the fridge on the right.
Thanks, Ms. Han.
You only care about yourself, don't you?
Gosh, where did I put them?
How about you check
the powder room or the bathroom?
Got it.
Goodness.
She calls you all the time
after misplacing her things.
Just quit already.
There are plenty of other places
for you to work at.
I learned how to be a housekeeper
at her place,
and the skills I learned there
put food on my table.
I'm grateful for that.
But you hate her in some ways.
It's not that I hate her.
I keep comparing myself to her.
Comparing your family to hers
will only make life depressing.
I don't even dream
of comparing myself to her directly.
But I can't help comparing our kids.
When we were young, we were taught
to be grateful for just to have been born.
Those days are long gone now,
so fill my glass.
Got it.
You're charming when tipsy, you know.
It's like seeing a different side of you.
Ae-suk, you're here too.
-Hi.
-You're back.
Would you like a glass too?
Of course.
All right.
By the way, how did Hye-jun do
on that movie audition?
Gosh, I almost forgot!
Can you be any denser?
They would have told us had he made it.
Unbelievable.
Why didn't you tell them that
Hye-jun's enlisting
now that he failed the audition?
You're not the only one
who loves our kids.
Do you think I enjoy going off at Hye-jun?
I see you know
that you go off at him though.
I've been in his shoes.
I know because I've been there.
JOY FROM DAY TO DAY
Mom.
What is it?
-Don't you have any friends?
-I don't.
Then hang out with Auntie
instead of following me around everywhere.
I'm not following you around.
This is me being your manager.
You're only hurting my reputation.
I seem like a mama's boy
which women loathe.
Got it. For strategic reasons,
I'll take a step back.
-So you easily accept this one.
-I hate mama's boys too.
It'll make you seem less desirable.
This is exactly why I can't hate you.
You hated me?
You should never feel that way about me
even if it happens involuntarily.
It makes me sad.
I should get myself a girlfriend fast.
-I'm off to the salon.
-Is that where your girlfriend is?
You weren't paying attention, were you?
I need to go to the salon too.
I'll call Jin-ju.
I don't go to her anymore.
Then who do you go to?
An Jeong-ha.
Isn't she still only an assistant?
No, she's been promoted.
Still, she lacks experience.
Although, she's amiable
and somewhat talented.
So it seems.
Wait. Are you going somewhere?
I'm going out with some friends.
So tell me. Is this better…
or this?
-This one.
-It's as if you read my mind.
I like this one more as well.
-Grandpa.
-Yes?
Do you think you can be a model?
-A model?
-That's right.
Of course. Why wouldn't I be able to?
Why are you laughing?
Go ahead and show me then.
All right.
I never really noticed it,
but you still carry yourself tall. Nice!
Of course.
If I were your age,
I'd sign myself up to be a model too.
…can be categorized here.
UNCHILGISAM FILM STUDIO
PRODUCER KIM
-Hello, Mr. Kim.
-You were fast to pick up.
My phone was right by my side.
I was hoping to check
Mr. Sa Hye-jun's schedule.
What for?
I'm here for the beginner's class.
I'm afraid the classes
are only offered to seniors.
I know. It's for my grandfather.
I see.
Then, please fill out this form.
I have a package for you.
What a combination this is.
Grapefruit and honey!
You're stalling for some reason.
Fine, I'll cut right to the chase.
What's this package you have for me?
NORMAL PERSON
DIRECTED BY CHOI SE-HUN
Out of five scenes,
you'll be silent in two,
but will have lines in three.
The character is memorable.
Despite it being a small role,
the producer asked for you.
-I'll get going then.
-You're leaving?
Why should I stay?
Shouldn't you try to convince me
or something?
Get lost.
I detect multiple coats.
Really?
The building's 20 years old.
Can I just add another coat
to these walls?
Then the space will be even smaller.
Tearing it all down requires more money.
A bargain was requested,
so let's go with another layer.
Well, it's all the same to us.
At least ask though.
If they want a bargain,
we'll add another layer.
It is already too small
for a coffee shop, right?
It'll look a lot better if we tear down
the walls and the ceiling
to go with slabs instead.
I'll check with the client then.
-Sure.
The floor needs to be leveled again too.
Water pipes, electrical wires,
and painting.
-We'll need more hands on deck.
-Chang-min and Ho-cheol will be enough.
What's this?
I should stop by the butcher's.
Head home first.
To treat Gyeong-jun?
No, Hye-jun.
He should eat up before enlisting.
I should get some pork belly
for my kids too.
-Hello.
-Welcome.
You're home.
Hi.
What do you need to tell me?
Is it that obvious?
The film studio contacted me.
-But you failed the audition.
-It's a different role.
I'll only be in five scenes,
but I want to do it.
You'll delay your enlistment for that?
How would that change anything though?
Why must it lead to something else?
It's just that…
I don't want to see you get hurt anymore.
Giving up takes courage too.
I'm home.
Hey.
-Here.
-What's that?
Let's have bulgogi for dinner.
Hey. Aren't you even going to greet me?
You saw me too.
You ungrateful brat.
Let's hope the military
teaches you manners.
Dad.
Yes?
I agreed to be in a movie.
You darn imbecile!
Dad throwing the meat proves
that this is crazy.
I thought you had come to your senses,
-but you're back at it.
-Honey!
-Get over here.
-You can't live my life for me.
What? Let go of me, darn it!
Don't just say you wish me luck,
but let me do what I want.
How is that you couldn't go a few days
without being tempted again?
Let go of me!
There, I let go.
Let go of what?
You. I'm done with you.
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi
RECORD OF YOUTH
-I'll do it
-Nice!
You are helping me achieve my dream.
Stay out of it.
This is my fight.
Everything will be good for you now.
Start what?
Don't even talk about that.
When did you become my fan?
Fangirling over you was therapeutic.
You sound hyper than usual.
I talk a lot when I'm drunk.
I was just doing my job because it's fun.
-I believe you.
-I believe you, too.
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs