RECORD OF YOUTH
THIS PROGRAM HAS BEEN SELECTED AS AN
"EXCELLENT BROADCAST CONTENT" AND IS SUPPORTED
BY THE MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS, TOURISM
AND THE KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
The parking lot.
I got held up at the gym.
Did you ask the director
when we're shooting again?
It's next month.
Don't be such a workaholic.
I like working.
I'm going to make up for my lost time.
I'll be right up.
Hello?
Yes, hello. This is Sergeant Lee Jin-yeong
of the Criminal Investigation Division
at Gangnam Police Station.
Is this Mr. Sa Hye-jun?
Yes, speaking.
I called to ask you to come by the station
to give us a statement
regarding the death of Mr. Charlie Jung.
I didn't quite catch you just now.
Which station are you calling from?
The police are busy at work
behind the police-line
at a residence in Nonhyeon-dong,
Gangnam-gu.
This morning, Jung Jin-su,
Korea's genius fashion designer,
who was also known as Charlie Jung,
was found dead in this house.
-Hey.
-Did you see the news about Mr. Jung?
Not yet.
I'm on my way to the station
to give my statement.
He called a few days ago,
but I didn't answer.
Really?
You must be in shock.
I sure was.
I'll be heading to his funeral later.
What about you?
RECORD OF YOUTH
EPISODE 11
Ae-suk,
-how do I look?
-Pretty.
You didn't mean that
even in the slightest.
Why don't you get something, too?
I don't shop at department stores.
Well, your situation has changed.
You're Sa Hye-jun's mom.
Sa Hye-jun?
Are you Sa Hye-jun's mother?
-Yes.
-My gosh!
Yes, hello.
Let me help you find
something perfect for you.
Well, I'm not here to shop today.
That'll be my friend.
You made it sound like we're the same age.
I'm younger, you see.
We're not real sisters,
but her family and mine
are extremely close.
-Can I get you some tea?
-Do you have club soda?
We do.
Are you really not going to buy anything?
What would people think
once they find out you're Hye-jun's mom?
Do my clothes look too shabby?
Of course not,
but don't you want to splurge?
Hye-jun earning a lot of money
has nothing to do with me.
How so when you're his mom?
I'm sure he has something
planned for the family.
Has he said anything yet?
Mom.
Yes, what is it? Can I get you something?
How much do we have in debt?
Tell him you want to move.
I don't even know how much he earns.
Move next door to Hae-hyo's.
Hye-jun can afford it now,
so let Yeong-nam pay back his own debt.
Hye-jun shouldn't have to.
Exactly, so why should I be interested
in his earnings?
I never want to talk about money with him.
But you've earned that right.
Not Yeong-nam though.
The director's office, the supply closet,
and a spacious hall are the requirements.
It'll be done in no time.
You can't contain your smile, can you?
What did I tell you? I said Hye-jun
would make it big this time.
I had no idea
it'd be to this extent though.
Your troubles are over now.
He's there for you to rely on.
Meanwhile, my son asked me for 100,000 won
when leaving this morning.
Even though he has a job, it's not enough.
Guys, it's us.
-Hey, guys.
-Come on in.
Have a seat.
Come in.
Yeong-nam, congratulations.
Will you be moving soon?
Why wouldn't he
when Hye-jun's a superstar now?
You should treat us to dinner today.
Can you believe him?
He already did a few days ago.
That's then, and this is now.
The more you spend,
the more money you'll earn.
Clueless brats.
Hye-jun's the one earning the money,
not me.
Hasn't he given you
any money to spend yet?
How can he not when he earns so much now?
Okay, I'll treat you guys.
Take your pick.
The budget's 5,000 won each.
Let's go for a course meal of 50,000 won.
-Sounds great.
-All right!
-And beef!
-No, forget it.
No, you're buying.
#BEST ACTOR AWARD #FOREVER #GOODBYE #2019
Stop pretending to be close to Hye-jun.
HYE-JUN NEVER TALKS ABOUT YOU
ARE YOU REALLY CLOSE?
"Pretend to be close"?
Off to the funeral?
-Yes, Mr. Charlie Jung's.
-I saw it on the news.
You didn't walk for him that much though,
did you?
He preferred models like Hye-jun.
-He must not be going.
-We're going together.
What is his manager thinking?
There are comments online
regarding his relationship with Mr. Jung.
Going there could lead to a scandal.
They're targeting him
now that he's famous,
so why should he get swayed?
He's not like that.
You must be a saint.
How can you not be bothered by this?
He's a friend, but also your competitor.
Thinking about your career
keeps me up at night these days.
You should have won Rookie of the Year.
I can't even look your dad in the face.
This will keep you up some more.
-What do you mean?
-I'll also be in the TV series
that he will be in.
-Says who?
-Like always, says me.
You only thought you had a say in it.
It was always me who set the deal.
Do you know what I had to do
because you wanted to be in Catch?
You're here to apologize,
so what's with the silence?
No matter how hard I think about it,
I can't recall what I said.
There were many things,
but this one I still remember.
You said I was exploiting
pure and innocent souls.
Are you sure
it's an apology you want though?
I did my homework on you,
you're not one
to be fazed by such comments.
What I want is friendship.
The apology was an excuse
to set up a meeting.
Admitting that scored you points.
-What is it that you want from me?
-Your connections, possible investors,
and to get on your good side.
It's for you
that I gave him the time of day.
I got cast in Catch
because Park Do-ha asked the director.
Lee Tae-su had no say in it.
Wait. Are you saying he played me?
Do you know how many investors
I introduced him to?
You should've told me first.
Your takeaway from this
should be the fact that I'm willing to do
the things I hate for your sake.
I was the one who stepped in
when the director and the producer
were wondering who to cast
for Normal Person.
And the numbers of followers
on social media you're so proud of?
Oops.
It seems like I walked in
on a serious conversation.
I'll leave you to it then.
School's on a break. Where are you off to?
Study.
What about my followers?
Never mind. I don't want to talk about it.
-You have a blind date next week.
-What?
I won't do it.
I'm on edge these days
and your brother is enough of a headache.
Everything you have was handed to you
and not obtained.
It's about time you faced reality.
Thanks a lot for this.
The date was to happen anyway
since you're single.
Anyway, just do as Mom says.
CALL HISTORY
I haven't seen him in over a year.
Then…
Why do you think he called you recently?
Haven't you checked the texts yet?
MIN-JAE
May I take this call?
Sure thing.
Hey, Min-jae.
What's going on?
Weren't you coming right up?
I'm at the police station.
Mr. Charlie Jung passed away
and I'm giving my statement.
And you went there alone?
How can you go there
without discussing it with me first?
All I thought about
was getting here quick.
Are you aware
that most of your hate comments online
are of you and him?
It's not true though.
When will it be over?
I just got here.
Later, Hae-hyo and I
will go to his funeral--
What about our meeting?
Let me finish, will you?
The funeral can't take place
until the investigation is wrapped up.
I'll be right over.
GANGNAM POLICE STATION
-Where's your car?
-Get in first!
Deal with that later.
It's in the back.
She's scaring me.
Are you insane?
Why are you so mad at me?
Aren't you aware of your current status?
Another Hollywood agency contacted me.
Director Mark James' agency too.
He says he's visiting
and he wants to meet you.
A world-renowned movie director
is coming to Korea to meet you!
Is that more important
than someone's death?
A person just passed away.
I shouldn't be calculative.
Is that the kind of person
you want me to be?
Yes, I do!
Don't you realize
that there are people
who want to see you fail?
You're fully aware of the rumors
about you and him,
so why give them more to chew on?
There are people like that,
but there are also people who support me.
Min-jae,
I believe in the good of this world.
It's how I became a star.
Just think of my journey so far.
This is a miracle beyond explanation.
I understand how you feel
and I'm grateful for the concern,
but please be considerate of my wishes
to pay my respects to him.
Always the good guy, huh?
Meanwhile, your heart is too gentle.
It won't be enough to protect
your new superstar.
-Don't you think so?
-Get away from me.
What if a reporter saw you?
I can't even imagine.
FASHION DESIGNER CHARLIE JUNG
FOUND DEAD AT HIS RESIDENCE
POSSIBLY FROM SUICIDE
Hello, Mr. Lee.
Just look at you. You're looking
better than ever these days.
What's your secret?
Being in front of the camera
must be treating you well.
I'm not a regular yet though.
My seniors won't give up their spots.
But you've been on a roll.
I read your new exclusive.
I'm still living
from paycheck to paycheck though.
I wish I could afford
to buy a studio apartment of my own.
Won't that happen soon?
You can start a YouTube channel.
Our company provides management
for online celebrities too.
As if I could be one.
It's a pie in the sky.
This is exactly what I love about you.
Your honesty.
It must be why luck finds me.
I saw Sa Hye-jun at the police station.
He was asked for a statement.
So that's why you wanted to see me.
You know Sa Hye-jun better than anyone.
You were his manager
when he worked as a model, right?
What is it that you want to know?
Were Charlie Jung and him
in a relationship?
You sure know what to ask.
How do you want me to answer this?
Add some drama, please.
I want to be a writer, you see.
My plan's been canceled.
I'll come to you instead.
Sorry for making you come here.
You're the busier one, so it's only fair.
What should we have?
-Is this where you teach?
-Yes.
We'll eat after I hear you out.
What's so important?
I'm always grateful toward you, you know.
That I approve.
As you know, I opened my own salon,
but I don't have many clients.
Oh, dear.
You seem thrilled.
Since you lack clients,
I'm like your savior, right?
It's why I'm cutting you loose.
Me? Why?
Sticking to clients
that I'm already close to
might end up ruining me.
Men's makeup is too simple and boring.
Meanwhile with women,
there's more to do
and the change is dramatic.
For men, it's more about
the hair than the makeup.
Exactly.
I know you guys have been hiring me
to help out a friend,
but I want to quit.
You want to cut me all together?
No, but I'll reduce my service
to only certain events instead of
always being on standby.
If you guys agree, that is.
I'm telling you first though.
Hye-jun doesn't know yet.
Well,
I'm glad I was first to know.
I also appreciate
how you're letting me go
before I have to ask for it.
-Thanks.
-How did you know?
You guys have helped me out enough.
I kept working with you
because of my situation,
but this will only make me
dependent on you.
How is that a bad thing?
It is.
Over time, you won't be able
to live without the other person.
Sounds good to me.
Maybe in a horror movie.
Hello.
-Hello.
My name is An Jeong-ha, the makeup artist.
I will be your tutor for the day.
Did you take the aptitude test
at the Career Center?
-Yes.
Are you here because you have
an aptitude to become a makeup artist?
-Yes.
-We did.
I was bored.
I asked you to submit some questions
before our lecture today,
and the question I got the most was,
"Why did you want to become
a makeup artist?"
It was when I was in second grade.
When I washed my hair
before going to school,
my mom always applied lotion on my face.
Her touch felt warm and comforting
when she applied the lotion on my face.
So I wanted to share that feeling
with other people.
-What's wrong with her?
-What is that?
-How?
-Goodness.
-She's pretty.
-She really is.
Makeup artists not only
make people beautiful,
but they can also heal
the wounded hearts of people.
TO PARK SU-YEON
THANK YOU FROM SA HYE-JUN
Hello?
Yes, sir.
Okay.
The vice president is here.
He stopped by to see you.
Why me?
This is Mr. Sa Gyeong-jun.
He's Sa Hye-jun's brother.
It's nice to meet you. I didn't know
we had such a valuable employee.
We're trying to hire your brother
to model for our bank.
I'm sure he has an account with us, right?
Of course. Before he got famous,
he came by to have a meal
with his brother.
Mr. Sa here also got me
an autograph from him.
Then, he must be a VIP member of our bank.
He's in a lot of ads these days.
How come I never had a meal with him?
Did you hear the branch manager?
When will you bring
your brother for a meal?
I never agreed to that.
But you didn't say no, either.
Go inside. I need to use the restroom.
You're the star of our bank.
You can do it.
Cheer up!
What's wrong with her?
I can't live like this.
Hello?
Yes. We're making pdf files, too.
When we sue, we'll attach yours, too.
It's a war on hateful comments.
This also proves you're a star now.
Park Do-ha's fans are posting
a lot of hateful comments
because you won the award, not him.
It started after Gateway was over, right?
Yes. It's so odd.
I can't figure out the source.
It's negative viral marketing.
I bet they hired an agency for it.
Exactly, my point. Why would someone
hire an agency to mar his reputation?
His competition for ads?
I bet all that knowledge
makes you hungry fast.
Can I go and eat jjamppong?
You can never have too much jjamppong.
Go ahead.
Hye-jun, what's next on your schedule?
Isn't that your job, not mine?
Sorry.
You can go home. I can drive myself home.
-Bye, Ms. Lee.
-Bye.
Did you check your account?
I sent you your cut.
-I did.
-What will you do with it?
Are you just going to save it?
Don't you think you should
move out of your house now?
You don't even have your own room.
Move out to Gangnam.
Let's have a family meeting.
Let's talk about how we're stressed
because of Hye-jun's popularity.
What stress?
I agree.
I knew it.
You would have to agree with him.
MY FAMILY
Let's see.
Sure.
I want to know how I'm stressing you out.
Is Hye-jun upset?
Are you walking on eggshells
around him now?
Success sure changes you.
No, I don't do such a thing.
You can't put them there.
You have to put them here.
Goodness.
-Yeong-nam, why did you carry that?
-Gosh.
-Oh, my.
-Goodness. Are you okay, Yeong-nam?
Does he look okay to you?
Let's go to the hospital.
No. I don't need to.
You didn't have to come.
To make sure you got treated.
Mr. Sa Yeong-nam.
Is it serious?
From the MRI scan, you don't need surgery.
-But his pain is severe.
-He never got it treated.
He's never careful.
You must be careful.
Or your tendon will get weak
and might rupture.
Then, you'll need surgery.
I do manual work for a living.
There's only so much I can do.
If this ruptures,
you wouldn't be able to work.
I'll prescribe shots
and physical therapy for now.
-We'll observe the progress.
-Okay.
-Bye.
Get home safely.
Do you need help?
Did you wait for me?
Weren't you bored?
This place is pretty fun.
Do you want to look around?
That looks fun.
SUPERSTAR SA
I don't think I can meet you today.
I have a family meeting.
I'm going home right away.
I haven't seen Hye-jun in a while.
He's a superstar.
Yes, he is. I'm so happy he's doing well.
But you rarely get to see him.
If not seeing each other a lot is
going to break our relationship,
it's better to end it soon.
In that sense, we're doing very well.
Are you guys that steady?
Yes, we are.
I'll go home now.
You say that whenever I'm with you.
I'm anxious these days.
What if my shop goes under?
I really don't have any customers.
I need to check on my business approaches.
Do you want to meet a female celebrity?
I have two answers.
"Yes, I want to meet her."
"I had too much from Hae-hyo.
Let's not do that."
I can't guarantee she'll hire you.
She might have
her own makeup artist anyway.
-Are you having fun?
-No.
Should we stop, then?
No.
-Should we get something to eat?
-Sure.
It looks delicious.
I lied to my mom.
I told her I would be studying.
That's all right.
She wants me to go on a date.
What do you want me to do?
Well, I want to tell you
not to go on that date.
But then,
I'd have to take responsibility.
What responsibility?
Does taking responsibility mean
we have to get married?
No, that's not it.
In marriage, responsibility is mutual.
If I try to do that unilaterally,
I would be violating your right.
You sound smart now.
-What a turnoff.
-What?
I turned it on again. I did it.
There it is.
I'm not a turnoff anymore.
It's all good as long as
we can make each other laugh.
-You know, Jin-u.
-Yes?
I want to get married.
I can't stop thinking about
how it would be like to marry you.
It makes me wonder if it would be
a happy ending or end with a breakup.
I'm curious about that.
I'm going home right away.
Can I stop by for a second?
Yes. I can make time.
THE GIVING TREE, HYE-JUN ALL THE WAY
"JJamppong Entertainment sucks."
THEY SUCK AT MARKETING, TOO
"I wish he would leave that agency now.
I hate them."
I hate you guys, too.
The feelings are mutual.
What do you mean I suck?
HYE-JUN IS DOING ALL THE WORK
What are you talking about?
I do my money's worth, too.
REPORTER KIM SU-MAN
Hello, Ms. Kim.
You know, I always cut to the chase.
I heard Hye-jun and Charlie Jung
used to date.
Who told you that? That's not true at all.
You need a lot of money
to survive in that industry.
And I know his family isn't well-off.
If they were involved,
he would've hit it big ages ago.
Why go through all that trouble?
I've known him since he was a model.
You're not the only one
who's known him that long.
Okay.
What?
That felt shitty.
Today is a shitty day.
Who else would've known him that long?
Lee Tae-su?
That can't be.
He should know better than anyone.
Gosh, he won't do that.
Or he might.
Whatever.
I'll think about it when I have to.
And stop reading the comments.
Aren't you a bit too early?
You're going to Japan tomorrow
for a fan meet-up event.
You told me to have fun here.
You said this place is safe.
You know, I am incredibly hurt
and humiliated.
I have a wounded heart.
The fact that I didn't win
the Best Actor Award
is torturing me.
But you won the Popularity Award.
I only won it
because my fans voted for me like crazy.
Seriously.
I don't want to lose to Sa Hye-jun.
It looks like he'll be done for soon.
Whose side are you on?
I saw you looking at Hye-jun
the other day in the green room.
You seemed to have lingering feelings.
I guess he didn't make it this far
by pure luck.
He's so quick-witted.
What is it?
Now that he's doing well,
do you want to be his agent?
That's my house.
You didn't have to drive
all the way to the alley.
You're so stubborn.
Right there. This is fine.
So are you. I wanted
to drop you off at your house.
But your stubbornness won today.
Thanks.
What are you doing?
You startled me.
What is that?
Cleansing foam.
You might get zits if you don't wash up.
Do you like me that much?
Do you find my skin precious, too?
No.
I find it very precious.
-You have a family meeting.
-Did you come straight home?
-It took longer than it should.
-I did come straight home.
I missed you.
Me, too.
Who is that?
I'll hate that person.
Gosh, stop it.
-Hey.
-Which unit is yours?
-You left your book. I'll bring it up.
-It's okay. You can give it back later.
It'll only take a second.
Do you want to come out, then?
I'm sorry. I can't come out right now.
Okay.
MAKEUP ARTIST
What's the agenda?
My older brother is stressed out
because I'm a famous star now.
I can totally relate.
You too?
I have a lot to say, too.
-Go ahead.
-I can't do it when you ask me.
Why? I can't remember it.
Are you already getting old?
Have you been drinking a lot?
That's not it.
It's because when we meet,
I'm just happy to see you.
I'll write it down when I'm upset.
Were you upset?
Yes, I was. I was very upset.
No.
I won't be your makeup artist.
Why not? Because you were upset?
I want to do women's makeup more.
I talked to Hae-hyo, too.
You put him first when it comes to work.
I always welcome your jealousy.
I will support all the decisions you make.
Thank you.
You did the same for me, too.
I'm sorry
we can't spend much time together.
I didn't have time, either. I'm busy, too.
As you know, I'm the CEO
of An’s Make-UP Studio.
I believe I helped you with that studio.
This can be the makeup room.
And the waiting area should be here.
And the washroom can be over there.
I also need a space
where I can get ready and rest.
Over here would work.
How come you have
such a good sense of space?
My dad's a carpenter. All good now, right?
No, I still have to pick a name.
What would be good?
I've thought about this,
but I like “An Jeong-Ha Studio" the best.
It's embarrassing to use my name.
But you said you wanted your own brand.
There's no name that
can better express you than "An Jeong-ha."
Still, I don't like it.
Congratulations on the opening
of An's Make-UP Studio.
I'll take good care of this.
And thanks for the fridge.
I'm sorry I couldn't help you out more.
You were out of town because of the shoot.
You must be tired.
Thank you so much for helping.
Do you like it?
No, I love it.
My dad sent me this.
It suits the space.
Is this also your dad's painting?
No, it's from Hae-hyo.
He helped me out a lot.
I should buy him a meal
for helping you in my place.
Can I walk you
to where you're getting picked up?
-No, you can't.
-Why not?
Because then I'd want
to walk you back here.
Bye.
I'll text you before bed.
You have to. I want to hear
about your family meeting.
You should go now.
And don't tell my family.
Why hide it?
You've worked hard your entire life
to feed your family.
And you got hurt on the job.
Everyone does it.
Why make a big deal out of it?
This is actually good.
You should just retire.
Hye-jun makes good money now.
Why should you work?
I'd rather die than mooch off Hye-jun.
-Yeong-nam.
-You know how much I resented my father.
I don't want to be like him.
They won't be grateful
if I buy them food here and there.
I should just save up
and give them a big chunk of cash.
Right?
-Grandpa.
-What is it?
Well…
Tell Hye-jun that we should move.
He always listens to you.
Move where?
Not too far.
Near Hae-hyo's place in Hannam-dong.
That neighborhood is very expensive.
-I've already done the math,
-Okay.
and we can do it.
Hey, what?
What are you doing here?
Why do you have to wash up
as soon as you get home?
You're picking on me about that now?
Let's have the meeting.
Grandpa, remember. Okay?
Before the meeting, I want to know
why you're stressed out because of me.
Then I'll start with small things.
I often have to pay
when I'm eating with my co-workers.
They expect me to pay
because I'm your brother.
I get that you make good money now,
but I don't actually benefit from it.
And you, Dad?
I have no complaints.
Come on, Dad. You told me
that your acquaintances
always ask you
if Hye-jun gives you an allowance
and if we're moving anytime soon.
People say that to me too,
but why is that stressful?
You've always been classy,
so you're an exception.
And stop working at Hae-hyo's.
You always think
you can tell me what to do.
Did I ever tell you to quit your job
at the bank?
I just don't want you to work so hard.
Everyone works hard.
Anyway, why did you suggest this meeting?
Well, the branch manager wants me
to schedule a dinner with Hye-jun.
You told me to suggest we should move
to somewhere near Hae-hyo's place.
Whether Hye-jun buys a house or not
is none of our business.
And why bring that up at a family meeting?
It's his money,
so he'll decide how to spend it.
We're a family,
and we're all negatively affected by it.
Enough nonsense. This meeting is over.
I'll pay back your debt.
The family's debt.
Why would you pay off Mom and Dad's debt?
Why would you do something like that?
That's exactly why
our family is in this mess now.
If you have that money, let's just move.
Gyeong-jun's right.
If you have money to pay off our debt,
just buy a place in Gangnam and move out.
As you know, I even supported
Gyeong-jun moving out.
I'm really sorry
you never had your own room.
There's the basement.
I'll turn that space into my room.
Here's my plan.
I'll pay off the debt,
buy this house,
and make my own room.
Hey.
That's not a good investment.
When you're investing--
Are you lecturing him?
You were even scammed once.
Do you object?
No, I don't.
It's a good plan.
You made the right choice.
The branch manager would like to have
dinner with you. When is good for you?
Our son offered to pay off our debt.
Why do I have mixed feelings about it?
Don't you feel the same way?
Yes, I do.
By the way, wasn't Gyeong-jun so mean?
You heard what he said, right?
"Why should you pay off
your parents' debt?"
He totally drew the line.
But that's not what he actually thinks.
Gosh, you and Gyeong-jun.
Gosh, I'm sorry. Did that hurt a lot?
I told you to go see a doctor.
I did.
-And?
-The doctor said I'm fine.
They always say it's fine,
but you're in so much pain.
You'll have to build Hye-jun's room.
Can you do it?
I should just die if I can't even do that.
Don't say that as a joke.
Don't you know that words have power?
Why say that at your age?
Are you worried that I might drop dead?
Stop being such a crybaby.
Turn off the lights, please.
Call Jang-man and come up
with a quote for Hye-jun's room.
We should build his room
as soon as we can.
The conclusion of the meeting.
I'm getting my own room.
Congratulations.
Do I look okay?
You always look great.
I'm nervous about meeting Mark James,
the director.
Just enjoy it.
Your life will only get better from here.
HOT ISSUE TOK TOK
Su-man, who told you about Charlie Jung?
It's so detailed.
I was lucky.
I happened to see Sa Hye-jun
at the police station myself.
So they actually dated?
Out of all of your work,
Island Town is my favorite.
So, what do you like about it?
I like how you blended the basic questions
of what it means to be a human
and how we shall live in a subject matter
in a way that made it,
so that the subject wasn't too obvious.
Well…
It's clear that my instincts were correct.
I've never really cared for movies
that get too caught up in their own theme,
if you know what I mean.
So, when I watched the movie,
I feel like I had received a love letter
that was written just for me.
Look, I think we should work together
on my next project,
right from story development.
I could send you a draft of the synopsis
as soon as it's ready.
Thank you so much.
-Yeah
-Thank you for your time
and it was really good meeting you.
I look forward to working with you.
It's going to be a great show.
The death of the late designer,
Charlie Jung,
has been concluded as suicide.
But since then, everyone's been talking
about his secret love life.
Ms. Kim?
Yes, there are rumors
that he dated a number of male models.
From rookies to top models,
he became obsessed with them
once he set his eyes on them,
according to the rumors.
Right. I heard A, the actor who
recently rose to stardom, is one of them.
He's the most popular actor at the moment.
Apparently, he was very close
to Charlie Jung before he became famous.
He walked the runway
for all of Charlie Jung's collections,
and he was Charlie Jung's favorite.
Anyone can tell that A
-is Sa Hye-jun.
-I really want to know who A is.
Let's move on. The second story is…
My gosh!
-What are these tulips for?
-I just wanted to get them.
Seeing flowers always lifts your spirits.
Are you consoling me?
That's right.
You must be stressed out.
I know, of course.
No, it's not that. I bought them
because they looked so pretty.
Honestly,
you can't afford to console me right now.
Who knew the tables would turn so quickly?
I think they were talking about Hye-jun
earlier on a TV show.
It'll be stressful
when people find out that it's him.
Stressful things happen all the time.
I'm sure he'll handle it.
You seem totally uninterested
in the entertainment industry.
If this happened to Hae-hyo,
I'd sort it all out for him.
What is it? Maybe I can sort it out too.
Hye-jun apparently likes men.
Why does gender even matter
when you love someone?
My gosh, you're very open-minded.
But the thing is, not many people
are as open-minded as you are.
Hye-jun has a girlfriend.
I just said that
because it's complete nonsense.
What's wrong with that show?
Which show was it?
Mr. Sa.
Yes?
Well…
Never mind.
Go ahead. It's about Hye-jun, right?
You must have heard. My goodness.
But is he really gay?
What do you mean?
I thought you knew.
That's what they said on the show.
That's what everyone
is talking about online right now.
If he's gay, I don't even know what I am.
You don't even know what you are?
-My gosh!
-Ma'am, please!
He's always had girlfriends.
Unlike me, who's never dated.
You've never dated?
I knew it!
I can't even keep my life private here.
I don't want information
about your personal life either.
What's going on?
I just received the interview questions
from Beijing TV.
-I'll text you them.
-Okay.
Go through them.
The interview will be in English.
You don't need translations, right?
I really envy you.
You're fluent in English and Japanese.
He studied hard to make that happen.
Hold on. Why have the reporters
been calling so much?
Did something happen?
I have many missed calls too.
Yes, Reporter Choi.
Hey, Jin-u.
Really? I didn't watch that show.
What did they say?
A YouTuber is talking about me?
What about it?
No. It's not true.
You can't write articles on that.
Why is that rumor going around?
When?
In the evening?
Okay, I'll look into it.
Okay, I'll watch it.
CHARLIE JUNG'S SUICIDE
IS SA HYE-JUN TO BLAME?
-Min-jae.
-Yes, I heard what's going on.
Calm yourself and move on
to your next schedule.
I'll think about
how we should handle this situation.
Look.
CHARLIE JUNG'S SUICIDE
IS SA HYE-JUN TO BLAME?
All right, a little more.
Just a little more. Yes, 100,000!
Over 100,000 people
are watching this live broadcast.
LIVE CHAT
Guys, I'm sure you all know
that Charlie Jung was gay.
He worked as a fashion designer
for a number of decades.
How many models did he work with
over those years?
And Sa Hye-jun is one of them.
I bet he bent over backward
to win Sa Hye-jun's heart.
YOU'LL GET ARRESTED IF THIS IS NOT TRUE
Why would I get arrested?
I never said they dated.
Come on. We can all speculate that much
based on the circumstances.
There were never any rumors about him
dating anyone.
But Sa Hye-jun is so handsome.
Isn't it odd?
Unless he likes men.
What a lunatic!
Hey, what is wrong with this world?
I can't believe
people are spreading this false rumor.
We should sue him.
"Sa Hye-jun was infamous for this
even when he was a model.
I bet he sponsored Sa Hye-jun."
Stop it. Why are you reading it out loud?
We need to know what we're dealing with.
I can't stand it. This is disgusting.
Is something wrong with Hye-jun?
You don't need to know.
What's going on? Show me.
It's better not to know.
It'll only upset you.
Gyeong-jun, what do you suggest we do?
You're the brain of the family.
Hye-jun needs a new agency.
A big agency would do a great job
of protecting him.
But I like Ms. Lee.
She seemed very nice.
There's nothing worse
than being incompetent and nice.
Hye-jun.
-Why is everyone still up?
-We were worried.
Can't your agency sue all those people?
You all saw that?
Yes, we did.
How could they say something so crazy?
I can't believe
they're spreading rumors like that.
Don't worry. We're working on it.
I want to rest.
All right, get some rest.
We were excited about him
becoming famous. What is this now?
Dad.
There's no way something actually happened
between them, right?
Do you want a beating?
Dad, you seem to be
growing cold toward me these days.
I'm hurt.
The death of the late designer,
Charlie Jung,
has been concluded as suicide.
However, many people still have questions
about his sudden death.
What will happen to Hye-jun now?
It's not true,
so it'll get all sorted out.
You're here, too.
I wanted to know
what was going on with Hye-jun.
I can't sleep these days.
Is that why you're giving me a hard time?
Whose fault is it
that I can't fall asleep?
Do you have to be
in that drama with Hye-jun?
You guys are shooting the same drama?
Good! You can ride his coattails.
Gosh, you brat.
Are you happy that your brother
has to ride coattails?
I need to use the bathroom.
Mom, can't you just trust me?
JIN-U
Why is Jin-u calling Hae-na
at this late hour?
Maybe he needs something.
Answer it.
What took you so long?
You said you were curious
what it'd be like if we got married.
Why are you all quiet? Are you mad at me?
Mom!
Stop.
Let's talk tomorrow.
What did you hear?
I will never
put my hands on my children.
Hae-hyo.
Jin-u, this bastard. I'll kill him!
Reporter Yoon,
I'll stop by your office tomorrow.
Right, I'll explain everything.
Write it after hearing what I have to say.
It'll be exclusive.
Yes.
Okay.
LEE TAE-SU
What does he want now?
Hello?
You must be stressed.
I'll tell you how you can sort it out
as an experienced manager.
When can we meet?
Ms. Lee.
You should never
bite off more than you can chew.
Hye-jun is
too much of a star for you to embrace.
That sounds so wrong.
Why should I embrace him? He's not a kid.
That was a figure of speech.
You don't get it?
I don't. Just get straight to the point.
About Hye-jun and Charlie Jung…
Did you put a weird spin on it
when you were talking to Reporter Kim?
Reporter Kim?
I don't even know her that well.
But she said she knows you very well.
That's not what's important right now.
You can't sort this out for Hye-jun.
And the more famous he becomes,
the bigger the problems will be.
Why don't you
just let him sign with me?
Close your mouth.
What did I even expect from you?
I should've known better.
He's dating a makeup artist, right?
Think about it. I'll give you a pointer.
You can go public with that.
Then people won't think he's gay.
-After that--
-Enough.
I won't let you have your way.
The moment YouTubers mention celebrities,
their view counts soar.
Higher view counts mean more money.
They won't even care even if you sue them.
They'll make more money
while they let the lawsuit drag on.
Using someone else's name
is the easiest way to make money.
And the names of celebrities
are always up for grabs to the public.
This is only the beginning for Hye-jun.
Think wisely.
I'll stay behind after everyone leaves
and finish up.
You don't have to do that.
Hye-jun paid me a lot for the job.
Goodness.
I want him to have his own room soon.
What is it? Just say it.
Hye-jun has a girlfriend.
Tell him to go public with it.
That way, people will stop
talking such nonsense.
I can't drag someone's daughter into this
for my son's sake.
Goodness.
Take a look.
I like it.
Thanks.
What's Hye-jun up to now?
He's on his schedule.
Didn't you talk to him?
I just didn't know what to say.
The Giving Tree will sue them.
I'll sue all those malicious comments too.
Do you think things will quiet down
if people find out that Hye-jun
has a girlfriend?
Min-jae, I'll do anything
to help Hye-jun.
No way.
I said the same thing,
-but Jeong-ha--
-There must be a way.
I want to protect Jeong-ha's privacy.
It'll make her life very difficult
the moment we do this.
I know. I told her that.
We won't do it.
Where are you meeting Hae-hyo?
He'll be here shortly.
Hello.
Reporter Kim Su-man, right?
Yes. Are you Jung Ji-a?
Yes. I'm Jung Ji-a,
Sa Hye-jun's ex-girlfriend.
Hae-hyo told me about you.
Hi.
-Hi, Min-jae.
-Hey, you're not busy today?
No. I'm free these days,
so I'm taking Pilates lessons.
It sounds grand since I titled
the broadcast, "confession."
But it's not really.
IS IT ABOUT YOUR BOYFRIEND?
I'M CURIOUS
Is it about my boyfriend?
Yes, it is.
JI-A
-Hey.
-I met with a reporter today.
You'll see an article about it.
What do you mean?
Ji-a came to see me.
Subtitle translation by: Liya Choi
RECORD OF YOUTH
What if Jeong-ha sees the interview?
Well, hello, lover boy.
I want him even more.
Why did you make me worry all by myself?
The fact that the people I love
have seen those comments
hurts my self-esteem.
He needs a bigger, better agency.
When does Hye-jun's contract
with the agency mature?
She's going to expose your relationship.
His image will take a huge blow.
I had faith that I could endure it.
But faith is much more fragile than love.
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs