Dad, let's eat.
Okay.
What's all this?
We're eating meat
first thing in the morning?
Yes.
Do you usually eat like this?
Or did you make this specially for me?
A bit of both.
Bingo. You get ten out of ten
for that answer.
Let's eat.
Just a second.
HYE-JUN
-Hey.
-Did I call too early?
I'm just having breakfast with Dad.
-Your dad came over?
-Yes.
That's why
you haven't checked the messages.
I thought something was up.
-You were worried?
-It's all good now.
Enjoy your breakfast
and have a good day at work.
All right, you too.
You got a boyfriend?
Yes.
I have many questions,
but I won't ask.
Thanks, Dad.
I'll tell you lots of stuff
when the time's right.
Sounds good.
Now, I'll tell you the real reason
I came to see you.
Don't be too nervous.
Just be natural, Grandpa.
Why are you thanking me?
It's your first ad shoot.
Of course, I remember it.
Yes, I should be able to go home today.
Okay, got it. Good luck.
All right.
JI-A
Hello?
You haven't changed your number.
What's up?
Gosh, I'm going nuts.
The exam is coming up,
and I'm so stressed out.
You always do well.
It'll be fine.
Where are you?
It sounds like you're outside.
I'm at a shoot.
I want to go somewhere.
I used to tag along
whenever you had a show. Remember?
It's all in the past.
I saved some money to give you
when you get married.
If you don't accept this,
I'll get really mad at you.
I've started painting again.
I'm glad to hear that.
To tell you the truth,
it's been a few years.
But I was too embarrassed to tell you.
I'll have an exhibition soon.
Do you know why I started painting again?
I don't know.
To show you.
I'll work hard
and live my life to the fullest.
I know that I ruined your childhood,
but I want to be remembered as someone
who cherished his life
and did his best.
RECORD OF YOUTH
It's for the Industry-Academy
Cooperation's mentoring program,
so this would be good.
I just want to wear plain white.
This is plain too. It's sky blue.
Just listen to me.
Nothing bad will come out of it.
Are you sure about that?
What will you do about Hae-hyo?
What did you say about the new drama?
I watched a little bit of it,
and Park Do-ha totally outshines him.
You said he'll be a star.
Or is it just that I don't see it yet?
Don't be so hard on me.
The script is centered
around the main characters.
Considering that,
I'd say he's doing pretty well.
"Pretty well"?
I didn't let you have your way
to hear crap like that.
Your masterpiece, Won Hae-hyo,
needs an interim check.
Hae-na is doing so well.
If I had my way,
he'd be doing his MBA in the US now.
And what use is that?
It's not like he'll be a professor
or work as a salary man.
Getting firsthand experience
is much better.
He can live a great life with his
modeling and acting experiences alone.
What does he think?
Hey, let's talk.
I have to go out.
It won't take long.
I think you're due for an interim check.
WON HAE-HYO MAKES AN IMPRESSION
WHERE HAS HE BEEN ALL THIS TIME?
WON HAE-HYO
WON HAE-HYO'S ACTING SKILLS
COME INTO QUESTION
I analyzed all the articles
about the dramas and movies you've done.
I didn't know you were interested
in what I do.
I'm interested in your life
because it's connected to mine.
When do you plan to enlist?
Based on my analysis,
I think you should enlist now.
-I'm thinking about it.
-I'm glad to hear that you actually do.
-Dad.
-It means you've lost my trust.
Are you your mom's puppet?
You say that you're independent,
but you're just following her guidelines.
That's because
I don't want to fight with Mom.
I'm doing all I can.
What is it that you want to be?
A star or an actor?
-An actor.
-Then why agree to be in Catch?
You're only supporting Park Do-ha.
Your actions never match your words.
How did you end up like this?
I let you and your mother
do as you please.
Now, it's about time you showed me
some results that prove
your choice was right.
Otherwise, just quit.
"Results"?
"Interim check"?
He's being ridiculous.
He always steps in and tries
to take credit for end results.
What is it, Mom?
Your dad isn't completely wrong.
What did I tell you?
I told you I didn't like Catch
when I first read the script.
Why bring it up now?
We should talk about it
so you don't repeat the same mistake.
Gosh, I'm so upset.
Are you more upset than I am?
I want you to be more aggressive.
You're too naive.
Maybe it's because we're well-off.
You have no backbone.
Doesn't seeing Hye-jun
make you want to work harder?
Of course,
I know that he's not a big deal now.
But there's a thing called momentum.
It looks like he's on the rise.
What about me? Am I going downhill?
No, you're stagnant.
Your graph is drawing a straight line.
I thought you were supporting my choice.
What did you say when I supported you?
You told me to stay out of it
and said you can take care of everything.
And I did take care of everything.
Do you really think so?
Catch didn't do as well
as I thought it would,
but I'll get a lead role next time.
I'm not done yet.
Both you and Dad…
Don't you think this is too much?
Both your dad and I know
that this is a critical time for you.
You have to decide whether
you'll enlist now or postpone it.
I'll postpone it.
I can't enlist until I prove myself.
Ma'am.
I'd like to talk to you about something.
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
I heard you were leaving.
I was hurt a little.
I thought I treated you well.
You did.
Thank you for being so good to me.
Will Hae-hyo and Hye-jun leave with you?
I'm not sure.
I won't stop anyone from leaving.
I won't hire your replacement right away.
Let me know when you're sorted.
May I talk to Jin-ju for a moment
before we open?
Do you need to talk to her
to sort things out?
You should eat, too.
So what's this about?
I don't feel comfortable eating with you.
Same here.
That's why I'm trying to overcome it.
Jin-ju.
-What?
-I'll call you that from now on.
I'm leaving the salon.
I'm no longer your junior,
so I'll just address you casually.
Jeez.
You really get on my nerves.
I don't want to stay acquainted with you.
I don't like you either,
but I'm going to try to like you.
Addressing you differently
might make you a bit more likable,
so that's what I'll do.
I can't stand this. I'm leaving.
But one good thing about it is that
it's giving me so much energy.
The wheels are turning in my head
to come up with a way to kick you out.
I'm realizing that I should just pity you.
How dare you!
-Are you blackmailing me?
-Now that I know…
You have three options,
and you can take your pick.
First, I send this video to everyone.
Second, I gather everyone
and play this in front of them.
Third, you apologize to me.
If you apologize, I'll delete this.
How can I trust you?
Right? How can you trust me?
I may change my word
after you apologize to me.
DO-HA
Hey, Do-ha.
Did something good happen?
No, I feel so down that
I'm consciously trying to lift my spirits.
Both of my parents nagged me like crazy.
I want to hear some nagging.
No one dares to nag me anymore.
-What are you doing?
-Pilates.
-Where are you?
-I'm still in London.
Did you not see my post?
I posted a photo while watching
Son Heung-min's game.
I haven't seen it yet.
Oh, right.
You have almost one million followers.
Why do you have so many? It's fishy.
I mean, what have you even done?
Can't you be any nicer?
I'm nice, aren't I?
You know me pretty well now.
What are you doing after Pilates?
Going to the salon.
You still go there?
I told you to switch to the salon I go to.
I don't want to. You have the habit
of forcing others to do what you like.
That's true.
Do you like Jeong-ha?
Is that why you can't switch?
I've dated a makeup artist,
and from my experience--
You're so chatty today.
-Don't you have any friends?
-No.
Oh, Hye-jun is starting
a new drama, right?
I hope he fails.
-You're out of line.
-Let's be honest, okay?
Our drama didn't do so well.
I'd be upset if he was successful.
Tae-su is here.
I have to head out early for a shoot.
Okay.
Why take a photo of that?
This is my vibe
on social media these days.
Stuff like this makes you look cool.
Because I'm so fabulous,
the props have to be simple.
Don't post too often.
Things can go bad in a flash.
You have to keep posting photos
to gain more followers.
You can just pay
to increase your follower count.
What do you mean?
There are companies that do that.
Send them money,
and they'll do it for you.
I used that service
when I ran the model agency.
Models tend to lose their jobs
when they're not popular enough.
Well, enough about the old days.
Did you do that for Hae-hyo?
Hey, he is a completely different story.
I never managed his social media.
Director, after Yi Geon is kicked out
of the palace,
we skip about five years.
It'd be nice to change up the atmosphere.
It's difficult to do that
because this is a historical drama.
Director, have some patbingsu.
-Who got this?
-Hye-jun's girlfriend, I think.
She's very pretty.
What?
There she is.
Why are you here?
What? I'm here to give you moral support.
You must be the director.
Hello, Director.
I'm a friend of Hye-jun's.
It's too hot, isn't it?
We're used to it.
I'm in law school.
I'll be joining a law firm soon,
so I'll give you a discount.
That's how you greet someone?
It's not good to ever need a lawyer.
You two really must be just friends.
You don't seem excited at all
to see each other.
This is nice.
I can breathe now that I'm not in Seoul.
Don't do this again.
I feel guilty
that I'm taking a walk with you.
Hey, even a married man
wouldn't act like you.
I know you.
You always sneak back in
as if nothing's happened.
I really missed this.
You know so much about me,
and you're brutally honest with me.
It hurts, but I like it.
I must be a pervert.
This is why I can't forget you.
You'll find another man like that.
I'm not the Jung Ji-a you used to know.
I can speak up in front of my parents now.
And I'll be financially independent
when I join a law firm.
I've changed too.
Okay, even I can't stand
how clingy I am right now.
-Let's just be friends.
-Can you do it?
Why do you think I can't?
Why did we break up?
Don't forget I dumped you both times.
Look at this.
You're attacking me now
because I've hurt your pride.
Try to be more stable emotionally.
Don't say what you know about me.
It makes my heart skip.
I can't be friends with you.
It'll take about three hours
to arrive in Seoul, so take a nap.
Gosh, who is it?
I wanted you to get some sleep.
I won't sleep just because you tell me to.
You've had shoots back to back.
You must be tired.
Who'd look out for you if I didn't?
When will you be back in Seoul?
I'm on my way back now.
JEONG-HA
Hey, Jeong-ha.
I felt bad I had to hang up like that
because of my dad.
Did he leave?
Yes.
Gosh, hearing your voice
is making me miss you more.
Then we'll meet up.
I still have a few more hours.
Besides, where can we meet?
Many people recognize you now.
I'll come over to your place.
Oh, I never thought of that.
I'll send you my door code.
Wait for me at my place.
Jeong-ha, Hae-hyo is here.
Okay.
I have to go.
My client is here, Won Hae-hyo.
All right.
Bye.
I won't drive you all the way there.
Okay.
Make sure you don't get a photo taken
while holding each other.
-Min-jae.
-I'm talking to you now
as the CEO of JJamppong Entertainment.
I don't want to see you on tabloids.
Many eyes are on you now.
I don't think I'm that famous yet,
but I'll be careful.
-Those articles will stress Jeong-ha.
-Gosh, I can't stand you.
Go home and rest. I can go home on my own.
Okay.
Are you tired?
I'm upset.
Why? You didn't have a good lunch?
Can't you take me seriously?
Don't be all intimidated.
I feel bad now.
My dear client, I will do my very best
so you will love the makeup.
Am I just a client to you?
I feel like you'll get mad at me
no matter what I say.
Still, I'd rather you be angry at me
than be upset with something else.
That's better.
I could sense some affection.
Was that what you were after?
Here comes the skin toner
with a ton of affection.
Which actor are you closest to?
Sa Hye-jun.
You didn't even hesitate for a second.
Wouldn't this hurt Do-ha's feelings?
During his interview,
he named you as his closest friend.
Everyone knows Hye-jun's been
my best friend since elementary school.
Similar backgrounds and hobbies,
I presume?
No, not really.
Hye-jun's family isn't well-off.
By the way,
do you have any questions about me?
I actually know your mother well.
I've heard a lot about you.
I see.
I'll write you a good article.
Let's take more photos.
Wouldn't the rooftop be nice?
We should take some photos outside.
I guess the interview is done.
Well done.
Can I open your fridge?
THE PC IS SHUTTING DOWN
Good work, everyone.
-Good work.
-Thank you.
-Good job today.
-Well done.
Great job today.
-Good work.
-Let's go home.
When will I get Hye-jun's autograph?
Must I ask you like this?
I'm asking because
I'm sick of waiting around.
I rarely see him these days
because he's so busy.
Lucky you. I've seen him in so many ads.
I see him on TV and also in theaters.
Gosh, what does it have to do with me?
What are you talking about?
You're his brother.
-His one and only brother.
-Goodness.
But he's useless.
He can't even get me his autograph.
Ma'am, please. I'll get you one.
Even if you do, I'm already upset.
What will you do about that?
-I'll buy you a meal.
-Thank you.
There's a new seafood soup place
across the street.
-We should go there.
-Okay, let's do that.
Yes, ma'am!
What? "We"?
By any chance,
do you know a man named Charlie Jung?
He's a very famous designer.
Has Hye-jun told you about him?
-No, never.
-I see.
These bastards need a lesson.
Here, look.
Gosh.
He and Charlie Jung dated?
Does it even make sense?
He's provoking me.
Why show me if he knows it makes no sense?
There's this too. Look here.
It says he's a clubbing addict
and that he only goes to gay clubs.
Gosh.
What are you trying to pull?
He never goes clubbing.
-Why are you angry?
-Why are you showing me this?
-What do you mean?
-You must have a reason.
You act like you're concerned,
but you're actually saying,
"There's no smoke without fire."
It's not like you to be so emotional.
I know, right? What's wrong with me?
I was a drill instructor
when I was in the military.
They called me Trooper
because I kept on going.
But don't get me wrong.
I never used violence.
But now, I actually want to use violence.
Mr. Trooper,
I won't be joining you for dinner.
You do that.
How would you know
what your brother is up to?
Why give me shit for telling you?
I started my morning in a bad mood,
and I'm still upset.
I want to end the day happily.
You should go eat something nice
with your manager.
Something with protein for the main dish
and a dessert,
then you'll feel better.
Aren't you interested
in doing that with me?
Sorry, I have to go home.
What's there that you have to rush home?
Hey, you do need to repay me. Do it today.
Today, I really can't. Cut me some slack.
But I'll repay you twice
to make up for today.
Are we good now?
Is Hye-jun waiting for you at your place?
Yes.
Does that mean
he even knows your door code?
I hope you can end your day
on a happy note.
You can make it so.
Try to smile even if it's hard.
I'm off.
Can I come with you?
I miss Hye-jun too.
I'm really sorry.
It'd be nice
for all of us to eat together,
but he's at my place. I don't feel--
Forget it. You're mean.
I'll make it up to you later.
I'll drive you.
I'm sure you want to see him quickly.
Thanks.
-I'm almost done.
-Take your time.
HAE-HYO
It's Hae-hyo.
Answer it.
-Hey, Hae-hyo.
-I want to drink.
I'm still working.
Even you are rejecting me?
-Why are you stressed out?
-I'm just annoyed.
Why does everyone compare me with Hye-jun?
That's nothing new.
It's always been that way.
Both of you used to model
and are actors now.
And you two are close.
Really? But it didn't bother me back then.
Why does it annoy me so much now?
Because you were ahead of him then
and it's the other way now.
You're a true friend.
Was he also bothered by
how people compared him with me?
No, he didn't have the time
because he was busy making ends meet.
-You're home.
-Yes.
You must be hungry.
Wash your hands. Let's eat.
Be careful.
I missed you.
Me too. Aren't you hungry?
I am.
Go wash your hands.
Let's eat.
A piece of meat.
Two chili pepper slices.
One clove of garlic.
It's basic but it has a clean flavor.
All right.
Put the rice cake
on top of the meat.
And wrap it up like this and eat it.
Gosh, this is good.
-That looks too greasy.
-I like greasy food.
I'm going to quit the beauty salon.
I picked a spot for my own salon.
It's in Mullae-dong. It's an up-and-coming
district with cheap rent.
And I decided not to sell this house.
My dad is going to help me.
Do you approve?
Yes.
I'm glad you're not selling the house
and letting your dad help.
I wanted your approval the most
for that decision.
I like helping other people,
but I'm not good at letting
other people help me.
It's a type of deficiency, too.
Deficiency beats overabundance.
You keep improving.
Let your dad help you.
I like everything you did
to cook this meal for me,
except for one thing.
I'll go and buy it now.
-Hello, sir.
-Sir!
That outfit looks great on you.
That's mine.
It's from a fashion show in New York.
It looks too normal
for an outfit at a fashion show.
Son of a bitch?
What?
Let's stop. I'm embarrassed.
-Give it back.
-No.
-Give it back now.
I want to keep watching it.
-Don't watch it.
-Give me.
-No.
-Give it back.
-Oh, no.
-Give it to me now.
You're quite fast.
-Of course.
-No.
MOM
-It's my mom.
-It's your mom.
What do we do?
HYE-JUN
He must be filming right now.
I wanted to see him.
Your mom might be disappointed.
It's been a while since you came to Seoul,
but you didn't see her first.
I'm sure she'll understand me.
I told my mom about you.
She wants to meet you.
I have never met my boyfriend's mom.
You introduce your girlfriend
to your family when you date someone,
don't you?
No, not really.
I don't feel good about it either way.
I'm happy that you're jealous.
How's it going these days?
I can't imagine how it must feel.
How does it feel?
I'm anxious.
I look myself up online
multiple times a day.
Good for you that your name
pops up on the search engine.
Didn't you hear that I'm anxious?
I don't want to address that part.
I'm anxious, too.
What if my salon fails?
You're anxious
because things are going well,
but I'm anxious because I might fail.
There are different levels of anxiety.
You're always on a higher level.
Okay. I'll try to always look
on the bright side of everything.
I like it that you understand me.
I think I should walk you back home.
Your mother is waiting for you.
She's probably asleep.
My family goes to sleep at 10 p.m.
SA HYE-JUN
SA HYE-JUN THE RISING STAR
OF ADVERTISEMENTS
NORMAL PERSON BREAKS EVEN
DIRECTOR CHOI SE-HUN THANKS SA HYE-JUN
With success
comes anxiety.
And sometimes, what success brings
can be more valuable.
Grandpa.
I have to go to work now.
I'll get it for you. Leave it with me.
Gosh. I need it today.
You woke him up!
Hey. Sleep some more. Okay?
Go back to sleep.
Hey, go.
-Go!
-Hye-jun!
Come on.
Hye-jun.
Wake up. Have breakfast
and go back to sleep.
You're the best, Mom.
Hey, have breakfast first.
Wake up.
Wake up. Come on out.
"Park Su-yeon". Write her name, too.
-Do you know someone named Charlie Jung?
-Yes.
I modeled for his brand a lot.
He adored me.
What do you mean by "adore"?
He saw that I have talent.
He gave me a lot of chances
to be in his shows.
I see.
Okay, so that's that.
Do you go clubbing?
I never have time to go clubbing.
You startled me. Then, why were there
such comments online?
Did you go clubbing when you were a model?
Do you believe that? Don't you know him?
Mom, hit him one more time.
I didn't say I believed it.
It's all made up.
They are jealous of his success.
You're his brother.
How can you believe such comments?
I didn't believe it.
I was worried when I heard about it.
You have to be careful.
Why would you say that?
He didn't do anything wrong.
Dad, you, too?
I can't even say anything in this house.
I was just curious.
Why would you ask a question that
would upset him? He must be tired.
It's gone.
My era has passed.
The power dynamic in this house
is changing.
-Aren't you going to work?
-I am.
HAN AE-SUK
Hello?
It's me.
I know. What is this about?
I don't think I can work tomorrow.
Can I work the day after tomorrow
or on the weekend?
What's wrong?
Hye-jun just came back to Seoul after
staying in the rural area for a shoot.
It looks like he lost some weight.
I want to feed him a good meal
before he has to go back.
Okay. I'll see you in two days.
Mom. Do you have anything for my hangover?
I drank last night. I'm hungover.
Hye-jun must be
very busy shooting a drama.
Lucky you. You're enjoying yourself.
Jin-u even carried you home last night.
Your father has been pushing me.
Mom, stop stealing from me.
Steal what?
-My self-esteem.
-Gosh.
I should steal some more.
If someone can take your self-esteem,
it's better that I steal it.
-Good morning.
-Morning.
Order some food. Eat before you go.
Okay.
Let's eat out.
-Hye-jun is in Seoul. Should we call him?
-No, let him be. He must be tired.
Is he sleeping?
Yes. He's completely passed out.
No matter how exhausted he is,
he still has energy to see his girlfriend.
That's what makes him young.
-How jealous.
-Right.
I'm jealous of Jeong-ha.
although I haven't met her yet.
Is there anything you want to eat?
I'm going grocery shopping.
I'll buy some herbal tonics, too.
I'm glad there are
so many things to do for him.
Hello. I'm here for a delivery.
-Who ordered it?
-I did.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy your food.
It's my treat to celebrate my resignation.
I'll put it in the lounge. Have some food.
-Thank you. It looks delicious.
-Enjoy.
This is good. Thank you.
The person I want to thank the most
before quitting is Jin-ju.
I did train her to be tough.
I'm sorry.
Was it because you were training her?
Of course.
How can I steal male clients from her?
You knew about that.
Why would they come to me
when Jin-ju is prettier?
That's true.
-Have some.
-Thank you.
"If Park Jin-ju
apologizes to An Jeong-ha
in front of people…"
"I, Park Jin-ju,
tried to kick An Jeong-ha
out of the salon."
"…for spreading a rumor
that I stole her male clients
to kick An Jeong-ha out--"
Don't write that in such detail.
It's embarrassing.
Jin-ju, so you do feel embarrassed?
This is insulting. I won't write it.
I won't do it, either.
Let's forget about it.
Damn it.
Can you just write about the video?
-"For nitpicking--"
-Don't write that, either.
If we cannot leave together,
I will not go.
-Hye-jun!
-You are my people, too!
That's you!
I will not neglect…
Oh, Hye-jun.
Stop it.
You're not Yi Geon.
No! You're not Geon.
Bring back Geon.
Hye-jun, please bring him back!
Stop it.
Okay.
Here's my Geon!
Geon. Bring him back here!
MIN-JAE
It's Min-jae.
-Hey, Min-jae.
-Hye-jun.
I told them you'd host
the end of the year awards.
You've been
nominated as the Best Male Actor.
-Really?
-Yes, really.
Congratulations. I have to go home now.
What is it?
I've been nominated for Best Male Actor.
And I'm the host.
You're amazing!
You really became a star!
This doesn't feel real.
It will be real
when the awards ceremony starts.
-Sir, this way.
-This way?
Yes.
Ms. Han, you can sit next to Mr. Sa.
I want to sit with her. You go in.
Sure.
Gosh.
Where's Hye-jun?
He's reading the script.
He should be done by now.
I see. There's a script.
Everything on TV comes with a script.
How do you know that?
You can look it up online.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
What's all the fuss?
It's only the Rookie of the Year.
He accused me of stealing his self-esteem.
So today, I'll boost it.
I want you to give him compliments today.
You'll make him soft.
I raised him to be gentle and bright.
People like that.
He needs to be liked to be successful.
You don't like Mr. Kim
because he's all twisted inside.
Don't compare Hae-hyo to him.
Mr. Kim and your older brother have
a similar personality.
Had we raised Hae-hyo wrong,
he could have turned out like him.
Why bring him up? It's pissing me off.
-Can't we go out?
-No.
We should celebrate as a family
when something good has happened.
That's our family rule.
You look handsome. You look hot!
-You look great!
-Over here.
-This way.
-Over here!
Does my hair look too much?
No, it looks fine.
Ms. An, you must forget all about me
when you work on Hae-hyo.
Isn't that only right?
I was the one to discover Ms. An
and her talent as a makeup artist.
That's not true. I introduced you to her.
I lost her to you because of money.
There you go again.
Why don't you date each other?
I don't want to fall victim
to your bickering.
Min-su is presenting the Best Actor Award.
Will he leave right away?
I should talk to Min-jae about it.
If you win, it will be from Min-su.
Lucky you.
I doubt that I'll win.
Hae-hyo.
There you are.
You're going to win Rookie of the Year.
There are strong candidates.
But I'm sure you'll win.
Catch had the highest ratings
compared to your competitor's.
Then Hye-jun will win
the Best Actor Award.
His drama had the highest ratings
among them.
Come on. He said something nice to you.
Return the favor.
Do-ha did a great job in that drama.
You saw it yourself.
Let them talk.
It's bad manners to butt in.
Hello. I said hello to you.
I was taught a good manager
always says hello.
Right. You must be so happy
to see Hye-jun's career take off.
You know, there's something called
the beginner's luck,
so I can't say
whether he'll keep doing well.
But he was with you
when he was just a beginner.
I need to talk to Hye-jun.
What's going on?
I thought he'd come right on time.
But he's already here.
He's in the dressing room.
Hurry.
-Hi.
-Hye-jun!
It's been so long.
I heard you're hosting.
I came by to say hello.
Even now, you're still a man with manners.
I've known you since you were this tall.
I bet he's still the same height.
My manager. She'd like your autograph.
Come on.
This isn't like her at all.
I'm a huge fan, you see.
I watched all of your TV shows and movies.
-Thank you.
-I'm Lee Min-jae.
Please make sure to include my name.
Sure.
Are you winning an award today?
-I don't know.
-They won't tell us.
Why won't they tell him
when he's the host?
Must they be so close-minded?
I see. So this is how she's really like.
Actually, she's worse than this.
-Here you go.
-Thank you!
Can we get together afterward?
Hae-hyo wants to see you too.
I hear he's been nominated
for Rookie of the Year.
What will you do for me if you both win?
Your wish will be our command.
Count me in as well.
-That's enough.
-Got it.
It was nice meeting you.
Thank you. I'll keep this with me forever.
It was a pleasure.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
-I'll see you, then.
-Sure.
-Thank you.
-Sure thing.
-Have a good day.
-Sure.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
She sure is hectic.
Tae-su.
See if I'm winning an award today.
If not, I'm going home.
There's a 90 percent chance you'll win.
It doesn't matter
if Hye-jun's a rising star.
They won't give him Best Actor.
He hasn't even won Rookie of the Year.
The 2019 OVN Drama Awards.
The Best Male Actor
for the miniseries category goes to…
OVN DRAMA AWARDS
MINISERIES, BEST MALE ACTOR
I see. It's him.
Sa Hye-jun, The King Returns.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Who knew this day would come?
Up until just a year ago,
I was an unknown aspiring actor
who had multiple part-time jobs.
My grandfather encouraged
and supported me all through those years.
Thank you, Grandpa.
And Mom, I love you.
The same goes to my fan club,
Hye-jun All the Way.
I will not forget everyone
who has stuck by me
since my modeling days.
Last but not least,
all the members of Hye-jun All the Way.
Thank you.
SA HYE-JUN
The wine bottle has been popped open,
so let's enjoy a glass.
Should I try calling Hae-hyo again?
But he's not answering.
Leave him be.
Just skip to the Best Actor like Hye-jun.
Who cares about winning
Rookie of the Year anyway?
You're absolutely right.
I'll follow in his footsteps.
Let's hurry out there for a photo.
Min-su can stand in the center.
You two dummies can stand on either side.
Are you sure about this?
-What does that make you then?
-Me?
A dummy who has two dummies as friends.
I'm shy around people, but like him.
Thanks, Min-su.
I'd love to be in this photo too.
Come on, then.
Min-jae?
-Join us.
-Just press this.
-Got it.
-Thanks. Nice!
I'd love to join you guys too.
Count before you shoot.
One, two, three.
We should hurry. Your parents are waiting.
Didn't they go ahead?
My mom insisted on seeing you.
I think I should hurry home.
You should. Hae-na's worried about you.
Did she call you?
Is it odd for us to be in contact?
No. Did I say it was?
It's fine either way. Let's go.
They're over here.
I'm sorry for the wait.
Hye-jun, you were amazing today.
I'm in your fan club too
and we're all thrilled
that you mentioned us.
How can you be so calm on stage?
Aren't you hungry?
I am now, that I'm less nervous.
I already booked a restaurant,
so let's head there.
-Chi-yeong will lead the way.
-Over here.
Well, it's this way.
Min-jae, have you seen Jeong-ha?
I'm so out of it today.
Let's go.
Pay me back twofold.
Will you say no again?
My gosh. Yes, thank you so much.
Of course. We'll meet up soon.
10 MISSED CALLS
JEONG-HA: 1, JI-A: 2, CHARLIE: 1
JEONG-HA
INCOMING CALL
DO-HA
-What is it?
-Hey.
Come on over, will you?
Join me for drinks.
We were both shitted on today.
I'm with a friend.
Are you with Sa Hye-jun?
Have you no pride?
You sound wasted.
Don't pretend to be high and mighty.
I know that you of all people
don't want him to be successful,
so cut the crap!
He said I'm high and mighty.
Meanwhile, my mom tells me
I have no backbone and I'm stagnant.
Before I left home today, she said
Rookie of the Year is nothing
compared to Hye-jun being nominated
for Best Actor.
But I failed to even win
that crappy award.
Jeez, I'm hungry.
Way to cut off my serious ranting.
So what would you like?
You were hungry too.
Slow down, will you?
What's wrong?
You should see a doctor.
I throw up when I'm stressed.
-I have stomach issues.
-You should have passed on dinner then.
As if I could say no to you.
I wanted Rookie of the Year badly.
Other awards you can win multiple times,
but not Rookie of the Year.
I hate being compared to Hye-jun.
SA HYE-JUN WORTHY OF BEST ACTOR AWARD
A GAY DESIGNER WAS HIS SUGAR DADDY
WHEN HE WAS A MODEL
SA HYE-JUN DATED CHARLIE JUNG
AND WAS HIS SUGAR BABY
This will be a tough choice.
I'll just get one of them.
Actually, I'll get them both.
TAKES ONE TO KNOW ONE
SA HYE-JUN DATED CHARLIE JUNG
He does this on all the articles.
He must be like a stalker.
I BET YOU WERE DUMPED BY CHARLIE JUNG
Well done.
Hye-jun, you did great today.
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
-Father, how about some water?
-Oh, yes.
-Goodness.
-Me too.
-You're home.
-Hey.
Didn't you go out with friends?
When did you get here?
It would've been nice to have you there.
Do you know what Hye-jun said?
He thanked his grandpa.
He also said he loved his mom.
I watched the live show.
You left out Dad though.
Addressing me is the same
as addressing him.
-He didn't mention you either.
-But I wasn't there.
Tell us right now.
Are you grateful or not?
Why didn't you say it on stage?
Must you be so childish?
He's getting up because he's guilty.
Must you be like this on a good day?
I know Dad.
I'm pretty sure he's upset.
-Why are you getting up?
-To rest in my room.
Dinner must've been salty today.
-Unbelievable.
-But he didn't.
Hye-jun didn't leave you out
because he hates you.
So he hates me now?
Was I that mean to him?
Of course not.
Are you happy
to hear him say he loves you?
How could he have not mentioned
his gratitude toward me?
Hearing him say he loves me
put me on cloud nine.
Talk about a surge of emotions.
He loves me even though
I barely did anything for him.
Fighting through all the hardships
of our marriage finally paid off.
Nothing in this life is better
than seeing our son succeed.
YOU HAVE A TEXT FROM CHARLIE JUNG
MONTHLY SCHEDULE
Over here, please.
Right.
That goes over there.
-Let me take that.
-Look at all these gifts.
I'll take that.
A signature?
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
He made it big. My Hye-jun is a star!
He'll be on a path to glory now.
Let's not get too hasty.
I'm not getting hasty, it's a fact.
Let's see where
our Superstar Sa currently is.
-Where are you?
-The parking lot.
I got held up at the gym.
Did you ask the director
when we're shooting again?
It's next month.
Don't be such a workaholic.
I like working.
I'm going to make up for my lost time.
I'll be right up.
Hello?
Yes, hello. This is Sergeant Lee Jin-yeong
of the Criminal Investigation Division
at Gangnam Police Station.
Is this Mr. Sa Hye-jun?
Yes, speaking.
I called to ask you to come by the station
to give us a statement
regarding the death of Mr. Charlie Jung.
Well-known fashion designer Charlie Jung
was found dead this morning.
The police are investigating
the cause of his death
on the premise of it
likely being a suicide.
DRAMA AWARDS
#BEST ACTOR AWARD #GOODBYE #2019
And so…
the year 2020 begins.
Subtitle translation by Hye-lim Park
RECORD OF YOUTH
I've thought about this,
but I like "An Jeong-Ha Studio" the best.
Whether Hye-jun buys a house or not
is none of our business.
I'll pay back your debt.
No. It's not true.
You can't write articles on that.
Hye-jun apparently likes men.
We should sue him.
The people you love
want to share your burden with you.
Don't you realize there are people
who want to see you fail?
There are people like that,
but there are also people who support me.
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs