RECORD OF YOUTH
THIS PROGRAM HAS BEEN SELECTED AS AN
"EXCELLENT BROADCAST CONTENT" AND IS SUPPORTED
BY THE MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS, TOURISM
AND THE KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
You can come in.
You look so shy.
Right?
I feel a little shy for some reason.
Just be your usual self. This is awkward.
-Is this you?
-Yes.
Do you want some tea?
Today's my lucky day.
Was I always that mean to you?
Come on. This is nothing.
Thanks.
For what?
For reaching out to me
when you needed someone.
I crossed the line
because I had a tough day.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have called you.
Don't get the wrong idea. I'm nice to you
because you're his girlfriend.
That's all this is.
What's with you?
Why do you assume I like you?
Forget it, then. I was really worried.
Of course, why would you like me?
Aren't you hungry?
I always have meat in the fridge.
I am, but I shouldn't.
I have a shoot tomorrow.
Won Hae-hyo is a man
who thinks about tomorrow.
Impressive.
HYE-JUN
Hey.
Did you call me? I'm in Singapore now.
Sorry, I was on the plane.
I see.
Did something happen?
No, I just wanted to talk.
What are you up to now?
How about a long phone chat?
You should be well-rested
for your fan meet-up event.
I miss you.
Me too.
EPISODE 13
That was Hye-jun.
I know.
I didn't tell him about you.
He'd be upset to know
that we're together this late.
You're very considerate of him.
Because he's doing his best too.
I actually called him before I called you.
He didn't pick up.
So I'm his stand-in?
You know, it was like,
"I have someone else to call
even if you aren't around."
But as soon as I called you,
I regretted it.
I'm sorry.
I wouldn't have come had I not wanted to.
Feel free to keep using me
for your beautiful relationship.
Do Hye-jun and I need to use someone
to maintain our relationship?
Hey, don't take it so seriously.
Life is serious. It's no joking matter.
RECORD OF YOUTH
I knew it.
You can't live without me.
LEE JI-NA - JIN SEO-U
YOON JEONG-HU - SA HYE-JUN
Cut. Let's take a quick break.
FROM LOVERS TO FRIENDS
It sure is awkward to do scenes like this.
FRIENDS SINCE MODELING DAYS
SEO-U
GET YOUR ACT TOGETHER
THEY HAVE GREAT CHEMISTRY
BICKERING
SQUABBLING
THEY ARE ALL SMILES
SEO-U AND HYE-JUN ARE SHY
REHEARSING
LOVEY-DOVEY
ACTION
JEONG-HU AND JI-NA
FROM DRAMA TO ROMANTIC COMEDY
WE'LL BE LOOKING FORWARD
TO THE COUPLE'S ON-SCREEN CHEMISTRY
SA HYE-JUN AND JIN SEO-U ARE DATING
I can't believe this.
Now we have scandals round-the-clock.
This is nuts.
I must get a rebuttal article released
before Hye-jun arrives.
FEUD OVER CHARLIE JUNG'S INHERITANCE
Su-man.
You've lost so many exclusives.
I'm sorry.
You can't let this keep happening.
I get that you couldn't cover
Hye-jun and Seo-u.
But you had the exclusive
on him and Charlie Jung.
-Why let them steal it?
-I've been following up on it.
Keep digging into Hye-jun.
It seems anything about him goes viral.
I'm working on an exclusive about him
dating a makeup artist.
A makeup artist?
That's not exclusive enough.
These photos are nothing.
What's with you?
You can talk about this on TV shows
using initials.
Do we only care about facts?
A fact can be seen differently
depending on the angle.
SA HYE-JUN DENIES DATING RUMORS
WITH JIN SEO-U
Do we have about 30 minutes
until the shoot?
Do you want to make a stop?
Why are you so surprised?
Didn't you say you had a shoot?
I'm just stopping by.
Can you do my hair and makeup?
I can't. My client will be here shortly.
I'm sorry.
Why are you always sorry?
You say that way too often.
Do I?
What are you sorry about? Let's hear it.
Jin Seo-u and I are just friends,
nothing more than that.
I never asked.
Haven't you read the article?
About me dating…
The article about me and Seo-u.
Because the drama is such a hit,
there are articles about you every day.
I've stopped reading them altogether.
It's not good for my mental health.
That's great.
There are dating rumors?
It's Chi-yeong. He's telling me to hurry.
I'm coming.
I trust you.
I only believe what I see
with my own eyes and what you tell me,
so don't let it get to you.
Let's have dinner with my mom.
She wants to treat you.
Really? Why?
What do you think?
Because her son loves you.
No answer, again.
Why won't you give me any work, Jang-man?
-Going to work?
-Yes.
I have a shoot tomorrow.
Do you want to come with me?
-Why would I?
-I'll split the pay with you in half.
Just keep it for yourself.
You look so excited.
Isn't Hye-jun heading straight
to the shoot?
Is he coming home?
He will, even if it's late.
This is his home.
Don't you have work?
Me? Yes, I should head out.
Is the business slow
because of the economy?
No, I'm headed to Jang-man's place now.
We should never rely on
Hye-jun financially.
Let's make sure
we can always support ourselves.
Of course. Why state the obvious?
I'm afraid we might get swayed.
Don't people ask you?
Everyone's been telling me,
"Hard times are over.
Ask him to open a store for you.
What did Hye-jun buy you?
How much did he give you?
Why didn't you move
across the street
instead of buying this house?
The price will skyrocket
once redeveloped. Lucky you.
You can live comfortably now."
They're all jealous.
I don't want them to bad-mouth Hye-jun,
so I stay quiet.
Me too.
Parents should give to their children,
and take from them.
I was worried he couldn't support himself,
and I'm happy
I no longer have to worry about it.
Let's never change the way
we feel about this.
My heart hasn't changed,
but my reality has.
Jang-man!
It's been a while since
we last ate together like this.
Dad, this is called "brunch."
It's breakfast-lunch.
It's because none of us works nine to six.
Why didn't you go to work today?
I've learned enough.
I want to open my own studio.
-Did you quit?
-No, not yet.
If you want to do it,
get started when I can still help you.
-Really?
-Are you crazy?
It's a bad idea at a time like this.
Receiving salaries is the best.
I feel like I'm falling behind.
Hye-jun's a superstar now,
and Hae-hyo is steadily successful.
So you're the loser among your friends.
That's because I take after you.
Joining his fan club
doesn't make you his mom.
You're the loser Jin-u's mom.
Jin-u, you won.
Gosh! Yeong-nam is here.
Tell him I'm not here.
You can't keep avoiding him.
-Just tell him!
-How?
What's going on?
Who are you trying to avoid?
-It's…
-Are you going to keep this up?
Why won't you give me any work?
Yeong-nam, I understand
your feelings might be hurt.
But you will thank me down the road.
I can still check the floor plans
and do simple stuff.
Not working will stress me out even more.
Just change the way you think.
Why can't you get help from your son?
People will speak ill of Hye-jun
if you get hurt on the job.
All eyes are on him now.
Everyone wants to see
what he'll do for you.
I can't spend his money.
As you know, I never helped him
establish his career.
Who did he get his looks from?
Is he the only good actor in this country?
Don't you dare criticize him.
Clearly, he didn't get his good looks
from me.
It was you who married Ae-suk.
And he's tall because of your father.
Enough!
-Will you give me work or not?
-I won't!
You can't keep your old ways.
You're Sa Hye-jun's dad.
People are so nosy.
Why are people so interested
in others' lives?
Celebrity gossip is like
talking about your neighbors.
There's nothing wrong
with worrying about someone
and finding solace in it.
Look up Hye-jun,
and you'll find so many articles daily.
Even today, a dating rumor broke out.
But it's all fake.
How is finding solace in fake news nice?
Hae-hyo should have gotten that role.
They're airing reruns of Hye-jun's drama.
His drama made it big again.
The First Human.
Mom, I'm in that drama too.
I know. The drama is a huge hit,
but not you.
The writers are the problem.
Until when will they keep focusing
on the lead characters?
I'm getting many offers too,
even for lead roles.
I guess you don't check
the scripts I get these days.
I don't feel as determined anymore.
I've lost my motivation.
Try to believe in your son, Mom.
You're so handsome.
Why aren't things taking off for you?
Do you want to see this?
This is my absolute favorite
out of all the things you've done.
It's a commercial.
Who cares? You look amazing in it.
OUR YOUTH ISN'T OVER YET
-Where are you going?
-Do-ha wants to meet up.
I don't like him because
he reminds me of Lee Tae-su.
You don't have to see him anymore.
Lee Tae-su
won't leave us alone until he decides
that he doesn't need us.
What now?
Did you look into it?
Hae-hyo's follower count.
You're so persistent.
Give me something and I'll shut up.
Look. I'd say it's suspicious
if the number of comments
wasn't on par with his follower count.
Also if most of the likes are
from foreign accounts
and if he starts getting likes
as soon as he posts something.
And? Hae-hyo's follower count
is fake, right?
I don't know. There's no solid evidence.
Why don't you look into it?
I just gave you some pointers.
Where are you going?
A reporter wants to meet.
You…
I'm doing it for you.
Food is the best remedy for stress.
You've had a number of exclusives.
Why are you stressed?
My boss gave me an earful
for losing a couple.
I had another exclusive
on Sa Hye-jun's girlfriend,
but my boss rejected it
saying it's too weak.
-Who is she?
-A makeup artist.
I have photos.
I called his agent at JJamppong,
and she flat out denied it.
Any agent would have done the same.
You're such a wonderful person.
She betrayed you,
yet you're defending her.
Come on. It wasn't that bad.
Anyway, what kinds of photos?
I have them on my phone.
I'll show you later.
Don't you have to go
to the police station?
I'm still working on Charlie Jung.
He was dating an actor,
and they've been feuding over his assets.
What do you think people want to know?
It's who he used to date.
YOON JEONG-HU
I've received the data you sent.
But I can't make the investment decisions
with just that.
So, please provide more options.
Okay, Mr. Yoon.
I'll send you supplementary materials,
so please reconsider.
Okay.
Cut! Okay, next scene.
Good job. That was great.
Here's the next scene.
Who is Charlie's boyfriend?
Look at you getting straight to the point.
I can't tell you.
Just tell me, please!
I'm really stressed out.
Why dig into a closed case?
People are not ready to let it go yet.
It's Sa Hye-jun, right?
No.
Of course, you'd say no.
I know that it's Sa Hye-jun.
That's why you interviewed him first.
I told you it's not him. Sa Hye-jun…
We only interviewed him
because of the call history
and text messages.
Leave now, will you?
What did the texts say?
Was he the last one who called?
I said no!
A strong no means yes.
MODELING AGENCY CONTRACT
CONTRACT DURATION
Come in.
Can't you afford to move now?
What did Su-man say?
Gosh, you're so impatient.
Here's the bread you like.
I don't like them anymore.
But you got them for me, so I'll accept.
May I sit down?
Of course.
It's unlike you to ask such a question.
I've changed.
When you're well-off, you become relaxed.
And that helps you
become more understanding.
Sure, although it makes no sense.
You shouldn't treat me like this.
Do you know what I did for Hye-jun today?
I hope you didn't sabotage him.
So he's dating a makeup artist.
-Jeez!
-They even have photos.
Photos?
What kinds of photos?
Well, you know…
A kiss?
Will they publish it?
I talked them out of it.
-Why?
-I want to get along with Hye-jun.
-Okay, do that.
-Put in a good word for me.
And can you also arrange a meeting?
It'd be nice to work together.
Better the devil you know.
It's better to be duped
by the same person.
If you're duped by someone else,
you will never trust anyone.
He's a superstar now.
Even so, he's still the contractor
on his contract.
It was for a year, so the contract is up.
And we're about to renew it.
I see.
That's right. I see the wheels turning.
Looks like you're convinced
that he'll stay with you.
You never know.
But I know that he won't sign with you.
He has a brother, right? What does he do?
-Mr. Sa.
-Yes?
A VIP client is here.
What about it?
I thought he was your client.
Oh, hello.
-Hello.
-Yes.
I'm Lee Tae-su, Hye-jun's former manager
from his modeling days.
I'm currently with A June Entertainment.
I see. Take a seat.
Thank you.
I'll give you two some privacy then.
What?
You're charming too,
but in a different way.
I'm charming indeed.
It's just that my looks are
never judged fairly because of Hye-jun.
Right, I get it.
He bragged about you a lot.
He said you're very smart.
He'd never do that.
You don't have to flatter me.
I like this guy.
Hye-jun is very dear to me.
We went through a lot together
when I ran the modeling agency,
but I couldn't do much for him.
That's why I let him sign with Min-jae.
Then how did A June…
We were bought out.
They acquired my agency.
I got some shares in return.
The conditions were pretty good.
I heard you weren't doing well,
but you managed to sell the company.
After Hye-jun left,
I worked very hard to grow the company.
Now, I can give him
all the support he needs.
But why are you telling me all this?
You're his brother.
I know how much he loves his family.
Right, I know what you mean.
That being said… This is a gift card.
I couldn't help Hye-jun before,
so I'd like to give this to you instead.
A June is one of the top five
entertainment agencies.
We have an account at this bank,
so I'm sure you know.
Hye-jun is a superstar.
He should receive
the kind of care that he deserves.
You're smarter than he is.
Gosh, please.
I got better grades in school.
JJamppong relies on him,
but we're different.
We can pay him a lot for signing with us.
A JUNE ENTERTAINMENT
DIRECTOR LEE TAE-SU
You're not working out. Why are you here?
-What are you looking at?
-Hae-hyo.
I liked you.
I guess I had a fantasy about those
born with a silver spoon.
What do you mean?
Your parents aren't just rich.
They're both very well-educated.
That's why I wanted to befriend you.
I came this far on my own.
Right, so did I.
Did you know that you can pay
to increase the number of followers?
-Really?
-You didn't know?
But you see, I had a hard time
believing your follower count was real.
So I looked into it.
Looked into what?
I think it's fake.
I have circumstantial evidence.
If you didn't do it,
maybe it was your mom?
How dare you.
This only made me realize
that I should love myself more.
Thanks, friend.
We aren't friends yet.
You're just an acquaintance to me.
Thanks for your help.
-But that's it.
-I don't like you anymore either.
-Good job today.
-Good job.
Drop me off and go home.
Ms. Lee wants to see you.
I sued another group
of hate commenters today.
The police probably called the ones
we sued already.
We caught the one who posted
mean comments everywhere.
We'll see a lawyer tomorrow.
-What is this?
-Your contract.
What I hate the most
is using personal connections for work.
Same here.
Don't look tough. I'm nervous.
If you say you'll leave,
I'll beg you not to.
I'd choose jjajangmyeon over jjamppong.
No, jjamppong is better than jjajangmyeon.
End of story.
Your takeaway from this
should be the fact that I'm willing to do
the things I hate for your sake.
I was the one who stepped in
when the director and the producer
were wondering who to cast
for Normal Person.
And the numbers of followers
on social media you're so proud of?
Are you out? Can you talk now?
Yes, I'm just driving.
I'm meeting Lee Hae-ji,
the actress you introduced me to.
She was so nice
because you spoke highly of me.
That's great.
Are you upset about something?
-No.
-Cheer up.
The First Human is a hit.
You're in it, so you're a hotshot now.
-Is that supposed to make me feel better?
-Yes, it is.
Next time, do a better job.
And be sure to impress Hae-ji.
I will so that I don't embarrass you.
I don't care. Just be yourself.
So that's how I should have consoled you.
Thanks.
And I'm sorry
because you always help me out.
I'll repay you.
Turn to me when you really need help.
That won't happen.
Why are you so excited
about your follower count?
Why am I so excited?
I have one million followers
who are my fans.
Numbers like that are fake.
Do you want to know what's real?
Being applauded on stage like Hye-jun.
Darn it!
Mom.
-Are you going out?
-To see your aunt.
I want something casual.
-Where are you going?
-A date.
I'm trying to enjoy my dating life
like you suggested.
Then why tell me?
I always tell you where I'm going.
Don't test my patience.
I've conceded a lot.
I'll see you later.
Gosh, that brat.
Go on in.
-Did you eat?
-I did, of course.
Gosh, I'm home.
Home sweet home.
Don't you love your room?
I love it. I don't ever want to leave.
I'm sorry.
You say that to me
whenever you see me now.
I know, right?
I don't know why I feel sorry
whenever I see you these days.
-Mom.
-Yes?
When two women came into my life,
my life took a new turn.
That's Jeong-ha and me.
Min-jae and Jeong-ha.
-Not Jeong-ha and me?
-Why would you be one of them?
Right. You grew up on your own.
Mom, you're my mom.
You already have a place in my heart.
Right? I'm your mom.
What were you thinking?
I feel like I don't deserve you.
I saw how Hae-hyo's mom supported him.
And what I did for you
doesn't even come close.
By the way, why did you talk to Ms. Lee
about Jeong-ha?
We barely get to spend time.
I feel bad.
Should I spend time with her
in your place?
That won't be the same.
Right.
Did you tell her I'll treat her to a meal?
I did. She seemed happy.
Then, let's pick a date.
Hello, Hye-jun.
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT SA HYE-JUN
That jerk left another comment.
Why can't this jerk let him be?
He's everywhere.
I'll follow you to the end.
I BET YOU'RE CHARLIE'S LOVER
Hye-jun!
Yes. I'm in here.
I need to talk to you. Should I wait?
Let's talk.
Gosh, the material…
What is it about?
I met with Mr. Lee Tae-su
from A June Entertainment.
You were in his modeling agency.
-Why?
-His agency has accounts with our bank.
By the way,
he seemed to be really competent.
He was sorry
he couldn't help you more before.
He wants to work with you again.
He gave me a gift card, too.
Did you take it?
-What if I did?
-Why did you?
Do you know how he treated me?
How would I when you never told me?
Signing with a better agency--
Since when did you care about my career?
Hey!
You're not some superstar at home.
Why would you bring that up now?
Why did you take it?
You don't know what that implies.
Didn't you learn your lesson?
You brat.
I can't even punch you.
You're so annoying!
I knew it.
You can't live without me.
Hae-hyo! Won Hae-hyo!
I met with your aunt.
Her friends are totally in love
with you from The First Human.
Your aunt and her friends
liked you more than Hye-jun.
-What's wrong?
-What?
You're not going to respond?
Did you buy followers for my account?
I did.
You did?
How can you admit that so fast?
It's difficult to keep a lie going alone.
You're an adult. Let's share the burden.
Why would I
when I had nothing to do with it?
Because you benefited from it.
I didn't gain anything.
Even if I didn't gain anything,
had you been more grateful for what I did,
I would have shouldered it alone.
What did I gain from it?
"You're popular." "Young people like you."
It helps when casting a rookie like you.
You crushed my self-esteem
just for that?
I wanted to prove
that I could make it on my own.
That's the one thing I asked you
to let me have!
It's embarrassing. I'm embarrassed.
How can I do anything now?
How can I face people?
How can I live with dignity?
What? What are you doing?
It's all because of you.
It's all your fault!
Gosh. Goodness. Why are you hitting me?
What did I tell you?
I told you I wanted to send Hae-hyo
to a private school.
But you sent him to a public school,
and his whole life is ruined now.
Even Hae-na's life is ruined!
HAE-HYO
Why is he calling?
Hello?
I'm in front of your house.
I need to be comforted.
I'm just going to sit here.
Don't talk to me.
Then why did you ask me to come out?
I'll be quiet.
JEONG-HA
Are you sleeping?
Can't I go home? I'm sleepy.
Hey, it hasn't been that long.
It's been over an hour.
It's only been 30 minutes.
That means it was that much boring.
-Let's go.
-Good.
-You seem glad.
-Because I am.
I can breathe again.
Was it that suffocating?
Yes. You won't even tell me
what's going on.
You told me to be quiet.
I'm not in the mood to talk.
If you didn't want to talk,
why did you call me out here?
Wasn't I nice to you?
That's why I'm here.
All the nice things I did
only amount to 30 minutes?
Do you feel better?
I'm so angry at you,
so I forgot why I was upset.
Was that comforting?
Aren't I getting better now?
Hurry up.
Why are you walking so fast?
GRANDPA
Hey, Grandpa.
Since you moved down to the basement,
I barely get to see you.
I just wanted to hear your voice.
I'm glad you called.
It's been a while since I talked to you.
Right.
I'm filming a commercial today.
Congrats.
Isn't it hard to shoot a commercial
without an agent?
Should I talk to Min-jae?
I have someone in mind.
Sir, I won't be working
with Yeong-nam from now on.
I had to make this decision.
I know that he will never give up working.
But he never listens to me.
Do you want to see him destroy
his shoulders while working with me?
Hey, what are you doing today?
I have work.
Look at him. He wants to
keep his pride in front of me.
Can you give me a ride?
I'm shooting a commercial today.
-No.
-I know you'll give me a ride.
Why can't you just say yes?
I won't do that this time.
He's here. The model is here.
-Hello.
-Thank you for coming.
My son drove me here.
It wasn't any trouble.
I see. That's great. I was worried
that you didn't have an agent.
-Hello.
-Hi.
We don't have much time.
Let me go over the storyboard quickly.
-Listen carefully.
-It's your job. Why would I listen to him?
You're younger and smarter.
-It's your job. You have to listen to him.
-You little…
Is that your thing? You guys are so funny.
-Look over here.
-Okay.
We're going to the law firm after brunch.
Let's stop by A June Entertainment
on our way.
Why?
I have a meeting with Mr. Lee.
-Why are you meeting him?
-He went to see my brother.
-Your brother?
-Yes.
Gosh. He's unbelievable.
So did he win over your brother?
Talking to his brother was
pretty effective. He called right away.
I wonder if he's almost here.
My gosh. You and I seem to be
on the same wavelength.
Come on in.
Here.
Hye-jun, you have quite the aura.
You really have made it, haven't you?
Do you want a drink?
You didn't have to come here.
I could have gone to you. Take a seat.
Look at the flowers.
I bought them at a shop
in Yangjae-dong this morning.
Aren't they beautiful?
Did you forget what you did to me?
How can I forget that?
I'll do better next time.
You're indeed a professional.
I am.
I'll give you that.
Thank you.
I want to work harder now that
you've acknowledged my effort.
Please keep working harder,
and don't ever come near me again.
Stay away from my family.
-Did he say something?
-Why give him a gift card?
He didn't take it. Did he say he did? Why?
He said he got scammed before,
so he's very careful.
This is a gift card.
I couldn't help Hye-jun before,
so I'd like to give this to you instead.
You can give that to him, then.
You know, I got scammed once.
I would have accepted it if I wasn't
scammed. I'm careful nowadays.
I don't like him.
He was nothing like you.
I'm done talking to you.
But I'm not done.
Call me whenever you need me.
You know me. I'm the best
when it comes to cleaning up messes.
You just don't know
how this industry works.
Celebrities are prey for con artists.
I'm immune to them
thanks to you.
You don't have to sign with me.
I'm happy to see you from time to time.
Enjoy your lunch.
-Do you want to join me?
-No.
Fine. Yes. Play hard-to-get.
Don't make it easy for me.
Hye-jun, hold on. Wait.
I was your first agent.
You never forget your first.
I don't think I ever will.
I almost had him.
GYEONG-JUN
-Hello?
-Why did you tell him you were scammed?
What?
-I'm sorry.
-What?
I heard you didn't take the gift card.
Why did you say you did?
Do you think I'd take that?
Who do you think I am?
You need to repent more.
-Here you go, ma'am.
-Okay.
I'm finalizing the credit appraisal
for Iyu Corporation,
but they don't have a good credit score.
-Their finances?
-Worse than last year's.
We should adjust the loan.
We have a long history with them.
Let's think about it.
-You can answer it.
-No, I don't have to.
Pick it up. It might be your brother.
-An unknown number.
-I bet it's a sales rep.
I'm a curious person.
Hello?
This is Lieutenant Kim Ju-yeong,
a cybercrime investigator
at Secho Police Station.
-Is this Sa Gyeong-jun?
-Yes, speaking.
You've been sued
for contempt and defamation.
Didn't you reply to a comment
by an ID that starts with "top"
in a news article about the Best Actor
from OVN Drama Awards?
Do you remember that?
Yes, I do.
Do you know how much money
I spent on catching those haters online?
This is the best law firm in Korea.
No compliments?
Good job.
Let's go.
Have a seat.
Your lawyer will be here shortly.
Okay. Thank you.
What a superb view.
Hello, I'm Jung Ji-a,
and I'll be in charge of this case.
Wait. When I came here the other day,
you weren't on the case.
I just started working here.
I'm only an associate.
The team leader will be here.
Congrats.
Shouldn't you be sorry?
You knew that I was waiting
for the bar exam results.
-How could you not call?
-I never thought you would fail.
Who knows?
How's the case going?
I notified everyone,
so they'll be summoned soon.
But some wanted to apologize
and ask for your forgiveness.
-How should we handle it?
-Let's follow the trend.
That means no forgiveness
and no settlement.
APOLOGY LETTER
Read them.
These apology letters are for you.
Anything from the ID starting with "top"?
Yes. He wants to settle.
That kid? Never.
He's not a kid.
It's a man in his 40s.
Is your mother terribly sick?
I'm not sure
since her broken heart is the cause of it.
Can you deliver this to her?
It should be you.
Her condition will worsen if she sees me.
I heard you haven eaten yet.
Have some of this.
Just leave it there.
Hae-na made it. It's porridge.
She didn't know how to make it,
but she managed by following a recipe.
She doesn't even know
that I hate porridge.
Most children couldn't care less
about our preferences.
How can they do this to me
when I devoted my life to them?
You should eat something.
But I can't be bothered.
It's been a while since I ate your food.
You never cooked for me
after agreeing only to clean the house.
And that's how it should be,
so why does she sound upset?
It's also been a while
since I ate freshly cooked rice.
An electric rice cooker does the same job.
It's just the mood.
The mood can change your appetite.
The mood is that important.
Where are you off to?
Back to work.
Take a break and sit down with me.
I have to head home early
to maintain our house too.
It's not like I can make her stay
by paying her more.
Please come by the office.
I'll be waiting with the lawyer.
Hello.
You're here.
I bet you were shocked.
People can be so selfish, right?
After writing all those hate comments
about Hye-jun,
he sued you
for writing hate comments back.
-Hello, there.
-Right.
Hold on. You look familiar.
I'm the ex-girlfriend.
Oh, right.
Why are you here though?
We'll try and settle.
-Hand me a written apology--
-I'm not writing one.
-Why not?
-Because I did nothing wrong.
You should, even though you didn't.
This person wrote one to Hye-jun
and is waiting for leniency.
Whoever this is, he isn't sorry at all.
He's only faking it to get out of trouble.
And so should you.
What about my comment is insulting?
"You're the one who dated Charlie Jung.
He was your sugar daddy.
I bet you were dumped by Charlie Jung
because you stink."
Absolutely filthy.
How's that not a hate comment?
It's called "mirroring."
I only copied the words and phrases
that he used on Hye-jun.
When did you agree
to be questioned by the police?
I'll take care of it.
Why did I ever contact you?
I thought you'd have a better plan.
Did you think that Lee Tae-su would?
Why are you bringing him up?
I don't know. Why do you think that is?
It's because you won't listen to us.
You'll only tell me to write an apology.
That much I know.
Don't tell Hye-jun about this.
Haven't you memorized them yet?
-No, I'm done.
-You weren't at Pilates today.
I went to the gym hoping to run into you.
Did you meet Do-ha?
-He doesn't work out at that hour.
-He's a bastard.
It's not like you to swear.
Are you feeling okay?
Actually, I'd give anything
to not feel okay.
-What's up?
-I don't want to say.
JEONG-HA
I finally got to your text.
Sorry. I didn't know
you texted me yesterday.
That was quick.
It's from Jeong-ha.
I texted her last night,
but she read and ignored it.
-She must have got to it late.
-I guess.
She has an interview with Hae-ji
for a makeup job today.
-How do you know that?
-Because I set it up.
Okay, we'll start filming!
Let's go.
-Over here.
-Here, I found it.
-Really?
-Stop by the dry cleaner's for me.
Got it.
HABITS THAT MAKE YOU RICH
ACTOR LEE HAE-JI
Hello, I'm An Jeong-ha.
Oh, right. Please have a seat.
You look just like you do in your photos.
You've seen my photos?
Yes, I looked up
your photos and videos on social media.
I've also made sure
to make preparations for you.
The job's yours.
Sorry? But I didn't show you anything yet.
I haven't, but the job's still yours.
I only asked to see you
to tell you this in person.
-Why?
-Hae-hyo introduced you to me.
I trust his judgment of people.
That's not something I want though.
I want you to hire me for my talents.
Jeong-ha, I'm not a fool,
just so you know.
Let's see.
Remember the video about the pills?
There's a bottle of pills
I always carry with me.
I've studied the composition of cosmetics,
and there may be an ingredient that could
hurt my clients unbeknownst to them.
This is why I always
carry around this antihistamine.
What won me over was your talent.
Thanks for that.
I'll continue to work
with my regular staff
and I'll visit your studio
when I need a simple touch of makeup.
Thank you. Could you perhaps go over this?
Sure.
Yes!
HABITS THAT MAKE YOU RICH
ACTOR LEE HAE-JI
What do you have next?
I don't know. I bet you're busy though.
I'm shooting a commercial
probably until after midnight.
Oh, it's Jeong-ha.
Hey.
Thank you so much.
-What's going on?
-Lee Hae-ji gave me the job.
You're my savior, you know that?
Hye-jun's next to me…
and is shooting lasers from his eyes.
Tell him I'll call him.
Sure.
She said she'll call you.
Hye-jun, what are you up to?
She said she'd call, but hasn't.
HYE-JUN
-Hey.
-You said you'd call.
Sorry about that. I'm on the bus,
so I'll call you later.
She said it as if
I've never been on a bus before.
HYE-JUN
So where are you headed?
Home.
I'll get going then.
Why haven't you quit?
It's not like you need the money anymore.
Money isn't the only reason
I've kept working all my life.
What else can it be?
Why work when your family has money now?
What did Hye-jun say?
Is he okay with this?
According to him,
my life is mine, and his life is his.
He said so in middle school.
And you still believe that?
He was only a child back then.
It was his defense mechanism talking.
He probably only said so
because he made peace with it.
And I don't feel bad about this job.
If you told me you liked it,
I would've called you pretentious.
Everyone's different, you know.
Something that you can never do
may seem okay in my eyes.
Are you asking me this
because you don't like me coming over?
Of course not.
I just thought how I'd feel
if I were in your shoe.
Can I go now then?
Sure thing.
Here.
What is this?
My pay for today's shoot.
In cash?
I thought they wired you the money.
Some companies pay you in cash
on the very day. Take it.
Gosh, how much is this?
One, two, three, four, five, six…
It's too much. I'll only take 200,000 won.
Just take it all.
Hye-jun must give you a hefty allowance.
Still, spend it yourself
since you earned it.
Yeong-nam,
do you know why I wanted to earn money?
Why is that?
To give to you.
When you were growing up,
I barely provided for you.
What I regret the most
is that I couldn't
put you through college.
You were way smarter than Yeong-gyun,
but you burned yourself out
by tutoring him instead
and taking care of the family.
Thankfully, you met your wife
and was able to have kids
and start a family.
You're proof
that luck finds those that are selfless.
I couldn't be happier
to give you what I earn.
I want to earn as much as I can,
so I can make it up to you
for being a lousy father.
Why are you doing this?
What?
I don't have many years left to live.
Don't be ridiculous.
You will probably outlive me,
so don't worry.
Why are you in tears?
I'm not.
Why don't you come to work with me?
It's time you quit the job
you're doing with Jang-man.
I'll be good to you.
You can keep every penny I earn.
I don't need any of it.
Why are you being this way?
Why are you maturing all of a sudden?
It's scary when people change
all of a sudden.
Go back to your old self.
But I don't want to live
the way I've been living.
Even if finally growing up kills me,
that's what I will do.
Just don't!
Surprise.
What do we do?
She's going to expose your relationship.
This is bad for Hye-jun.
Aren't you happy?
I am.
I'm too tired to get up.
I thought you had a shoot.
I chose you and dinner instead.
-What?
-You should get yourself some dinner.
And don't come by any more.
There may be paparazzi tailing you.
-What if people find out we're dating?
-Then we'll date out in the open.
First was your ex-girlfriend
and then top celebrity Jin Seo-u.
Does that make me your third woman?
You're not like the other two.
We'll be able to date in public
once we announce our relationship.
Cameras will follow us around,
and we'll be broadcast live.
What will I do if we break up?
Are we breaking up?
You never know what'll happen.
Why did you call Hae-hyo first and not me
when something good happened?
Because you're busy.
But despite that,
I never once ignored your text
and even made time to come to see you.
Even with that hectic schedule of yours,
you've been doing your best.
But you see,
I'm trying my best too.
It will be brief,
so I should make you comfortable.
so I should make you happy.
It will be brief, so I should be happy.
I'm sorry.
Are you happy right now?
You have everything you wanted
and your career took off
in a far better way than you predicted.
But you also seem like our dads.
The dads that never had a life
because they had a family to provide for.
CHI-YEONG
Your job's calling you.
I bet you're exhausted.
No, I'm good.
You only have one more sequence left,
so hang in there.
-Would you like your phone?
-Sure.
LEE TAE-SU
Hello?
Hye-jun, I think it's finally time
for me to properly help you.
What are you talking about?
Do you have any idea
what tomorrow's headline will be?
WAS SA HYE-JUN THE LAST PERSON
TO TALK TO THE LATE CHARLIE JUNG?
SA HYE-JUN WAS THE LAST PERSON
TO TALK TO THE LATE CHARLIE JUNG
TODAY'S TOP NEWS
DID CHARLIE JUNG CALL SA HYE-JUN?
DID CHARLIE JUNG CALL SA HYE-JUN
BEFORE HIS SUICDE?
Subtitle translation by: Won-hyang Son
RECORD OF YOUTH
I'll sue them both,
the paper and the reporter.
What are they saying?
I did nothing wrong.
We may have to settle with him
because of you, although we shouldn't.
Let's reveal the text message.
Why should we,
when there's an easy way out?
Because he's a person.
He'd better brace himself
for what's coming.
I don't want to be your emotional outlet
anymore.
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs