RECORD OF YOUTH
THIS PROGRAM HAS BEEN SELECTED AS AN
"EXCELLENT BROADCAST CONTENT" AND IS SUPPORTED
BY THE MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS, TOURISM
AND THE KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
Why do you hate rainy days?
It makes me feel like I'm all alone.
-Mom!
-To kids, umbrellas on rainy days…
-Bye.
Goodbye.
…symbolize protection from adults.
After growing up,
I didn't expect anyone
to give me an umbrella.
That day, my dad told me
he had watched me
until he couldn't see me anymore.
He should have run to me
instead of just watching me go away.
For kids, things must be clear
for them to understand.
I wanted to watch him until I couldn't.
Did he turn around to see me again?
If he turned around,
was he disappointed that I wasn't there?
Small things like this sway my emotions.
I know this is a part of being in love.
Even until then,
I hadn't accepted such emotions.
When it came to love,
I was only a nine-year-old kid.
-It's cold.
-Let's go inside.
-But this is a new car.
-It's okay. Get in.
Put this over you for now.
Let's see.
Where's the button for the heater?
Gosh. Hold on. Where's the button?
Is this it?
Oh, no.
I think I got the right one this time.
I got it.
-What will happen to us?
-See? I got it.
We crave this uncertain
and unpredictable relationship.
That day,
we flipped a page of our youth.
#RAINING #NO UMBRELLA
#DON'T CATCH A COLD #THOUGHTS
#YOUTH #UNCERTAIN RELATIONSHIP
RECORD OF YOUTH
EPISODE 9
Hello.
Did you call the director
of The King Returns?
I don't like that drama.
"When you and I disagree,
we will follow my decision."
That was my condition.
Come on. You must follow up
with a romantic drama.
What's my schedule today?
Hair salon at 11 a.m.,
interview with Out News at 2 p.m.,
and commercial shoot at 5 p.m.
Min-jae.
Can I sign an exclusive contract
with Jeong-ha?
Or am I not famous enough for it?
If you do Love and Guilt,
you'll be famous enough.
You're so tenacious.
Should I pick you up?
I'll drive. Meet me at the salon.
-Grandpa.
-Hey, you're here.
I was wondering where you were.
I came to exercise.
I'll work hard and start
my career as a model, too.
Don't overdo it.
-I don't want you to faint again.
-It's all right. I have a few tips now.
I want you to get more famous
and prove your dad wrong.
He knows nothing about this industry.
Now that he's making some money,
he bought a car.
Gosh.
-Yeong-nam.
-What brings you here so early?
I see. This is the new car Hye-jun bought.
What a slick ride.
Gosh.
I was wondering
why you came here this morning.
Of course, I'm here for a reason.
I asked you multiple times for Hye-jun's
autographs, but I never got them.
-So I came here myself.
-Just for autographs?
Exactly. They are just autographs.
I'm serious about this.
My honor is at stake with dancers
from my belly dance studio.
Don't say that in front of him.
He'll think he's famous.
You're starting to worry me.
Be nice to him. You'll regret it later.
I won't regret anything.
Don't you worry about me.
Are we having guests?
Hye-jun!
-You startled me.
-She startled me, too.
Hello, sir.
Hye-jun, can we talk?
This isn't a good place
for a meet-and-greet.
What is this about?
You'd better stay sharp.
He's doing that just fine.
-You should stay sharp.
-Father.
Did you just scold me?
Yes, I did.
You don't get to scold me all the time.
Don't you know that Hye-jun is a star now?
That makes me a star's grandpa.
Gosh.
What is it? You're scaring me.
Can I ask you out?
Can I hit you?
Oh, my. I remember you
calling that drama lame.
But you're watching it every day.
It wasn't my choice.
Why were you watching it then?
It was just on. That's all.
-Is that a no?
-Yes, it is.
DEPOSIT: 275 MILLION WON
DEPOSIT: 273 MILLION WON
DAD
-Dad.
-Did I call too early?
But I didn't want to call you
when you were on the bus.
No, this is good.
I wake up early these days.
I have a lot to do.
What are you doing now?
I'm selling my house,
so I'm checking the market.
I'm looking for a lot, too.
Why would you do that?
You don't pay a lot for your mortgage.
And what lot?
Dad.
I find myself in a perplexing phase again.
I'm reevaluating my life to see
if I've been doing a good job.
Hey, you went through that recently.
So you quit your office job.
No.
That was a part
of my meticulous ten-year plan.
Gosh. We should discuss this in person.
Even so, thank you.
What do you mean?
For including me in your perplexing phase.
I love being a part of your life.
Dad, you should stop
feeling indebted to me.
That's not the right word. It's love.
I'll see you in Seoul.
WON HAE-HYO
I'm filming right now.
I'm wearing this
for tomorrow's press conference.
THANK YOU, STAFF AND CAST
THIS IS FROM WON HAE-HYO
Jeez. He's so high-maintenance.
Why does he want me
to be at the shoot? Why?
I'll let it slide
since he lost a commercial.
You haven't told him yet?
No. Another commercial is
under discussion.
If that works out, I'll say the agency
decided to drop the commercial.
The studio is planning a press conference,
and they asked us to set aside some time.
We must work around it because
Hye-jun has a tight schedule.
Why is he joining at all?
He has a small role.
He's in the limelight these days.
The investors are pushing for it.
-Don't change Do-ha's schedule.
-Okay.
That's some fancy catering.
Who is it from?
It's from Hae-hyo.
Do you seriously believe
it's from Hae-hyo, Jang-gun?
Didn't you hear Hae-hyo has
rich parents, backing him up?
No, I never heard about it,
but I saw his mom
when she came to see you. I saw her, then.
I thought about meeting somewhere else.
It's been finalized
that Do-ha will be in Catch.
Hae-hyo also got the script, right?
Did you want to show off
your successful transition?
I read the script.
I also heard
a famous writer will be joining.
And a novice writer got bumped down.
I'd like to pitch Hae-hyo
for the supporting character.
If you do, will that work?
Yes, but under one condition.
I want your apology.
Apologize for all of those insults
you threw at me.
I don't remember.
What did I exactly say?
I'll take that as a no.
This is a great opportunity for Hae-hyo.
He's the second man
in Superstar Do-ha's movie.
After this movie,
Hae-hyo will be offered lead roles.
I can't apologize in advance.
But I will apologize once it's finalized
that he gets the role.
Things are going well.
You look radiant more than usual today.
Hae-hyo's drama is going well. Is that it?
Only two episodes aired,
so it's too early to celebrate.
But I heard scoring 13 percent
for the first episode's ratings is high.
The second episode
bumped up by 1,3 percent, too.
Do-ha can't even hold a candle to Hae-hyo.
Being your client paid off.
I know you don't say empty compliments.
So you know I don't say empty compliments.
Isn't he the main character?
You could say that.
That's a big supporting role.
WON HAE-HYO WANTS YOU
I've never had coffee
from my colleague's mom.
My mom can be over-the-top.
She never listens to me.
Do you know
why I pitched you to the director?
Why? I was actually very curious.
-I want us to be friends.
-Me? Why?
You're a silver spooner.
You're easygoing and classy, too.
Silver spooners and dirt spooners.
Must you use such labels?
That's the trend these days. Why not?
Have you ever felt this?
Worrying about money as a kid.
Worrying your dad might not come home.
Worrying your mom might cry.
Don't look at me with pity.
Where I am now matters.
I'm a star.
But I don't have friends.
I don't like Hye-jun
because we were both born poor.
I can see he's tenacious
and full of greed.
You're a bit twisted.
Being motivated is hard
in tough environments.
He's commendable for staying motivated.
In that sense, you are, too.
-That's how you became a star.
-What a lecture.
Hye-jun is my friend. Don't badmouth him.
Min-jae, where are you?
I'm in front of the salon.
When you offer her the exclusive contract,
don't mention me.
Say that it was your idea.
No need to rush it.
I want its proper value.
I can only show the house on my days off.
Yes.
Okay.
You're selling the house?
Yes, I am.
Didn't your house represent your life?
I had a change of heart.
I need money
to set up my own beauty salon.
You'll quit the salon?
Isn't that too impulsive?
Why would you let Jin-ju's bullying
ruin your life?
I'm not ruining my life.
And it's not an impulsive decision.
I've been thinking about this and
I made up my mind only recently.
It's hard to come to a decision.
But once I do, I'll take it all the way.
Does Hye-jun know?
I want a good relationship for us.
Here's the first rule.
Don't ask your significant other
to share your burden.
Keep it a secret
until I talk to the director.
After taking care of one problem,
I'm going to tell her.
SA HYE-JUN AND WON HAE-HYO,
FORMER MODELS DOMINATE THE SHOW BUSINESS
Why include Hye-jun in this?
They aren't on the same level.
I must go and talk to them.
-Are you seeing a reporter?
-Yes.
Hello.
It's been a while.
Have you been avoiding me?
No. I come and go depending on
my schedule with my clients.
I already washed my hair.
-Hye-jun.
-Hello, Ms. Kim.
What a surprise to see you here.
I heard you outperformed
the main character
-and were in the limelight.
-That's not true.
I talked to Hae-hyo
after last night's episode.
He's filming at a studio set.
Yes. You guys haven't been able
to see each other as you're both busy.
I'll see him tomorrow
at the press conference.
Are they on the same level now?
No, not yet.
I didn't know you were joining.
But don't you have a small role?
How did you know?
I read all the scripts Hae-hyo receives.
-Gosh, that's amazing, Ms. Kim.
-I'm so proud of you.
You made it this far without any support
from your family.
It's just for the sake of appearances.
This event is for Hae-hyo and Do-ha.
I'll go for moral support.
You're humble, too. Being too humble
isn't a good thing, though.
Go ahead.
Come over to our house with Jin-u.
I'll order delicious food.
-Okay. See you later.
-Bye.
Why didn't you tell me he's a client here?
I don't have a big mouth.
I rarely talk about our clients.
-Who's his makeup artist?
-Ms. An Jeong-ha.
Hae-hyo and Hye-jun have
the same makeup artist.
You don't have to worry.
It looks like Hye-jun
has already fallen for Ms. An.
Sir, your skin is glowing.
It tickles.
This is what I always do, sir.
Get some sleep.
I'm very sensitive.
I can't fall asleep here.
I'm shooting a commercial later.
That's not on my schedule.
I guess Min-jae didn't book it yet.
I should cancel my appointment.
I was supposed to meet a manager from MCN.
I see.
Sorry.
Why are you sorry?
That's not part of your job.
Can I book Ms. An for tomorrow at 8 a.m.?
She already has an appointment at 8 a.m.
How about 9 a.m.?
That won't work for us.
Can you see if you can change it?
Well, how about Ms. Park Jin-ju?
Just for tomorrow.
I don't want to change it
because of scheduling problems.
She won't be available unless
Mr. Won Hae-hyo cancels his appointment.
-You look beautiful.
-Thank you.
Bye.
-Take care.
-Bye.
Who is she?
Parents always rule over their children.
My parents ruled over me.
And I will rule over my children, too.
I couldn't give birth at the right date
because of my mother-in-law.
What kind of path do you see?
Creativity rules the modern world.
He will shine more as a celebrity
than as a civil servant.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-Have you been well?
-Yes.
-All right. Sit down.
-Sure.
Among the mock trial topics you sent me,
my favorite was
the Deadly Freshmen Orientation.
That's my favorite, too.
There are precedents, too.
What's wrong?
This is your mock trial.
And I'm helping you.
What's with your attitude?
Ji-a, I did something crazy that day.
Aren't you going home?
What about you? Why aren't you going home?
I'm going to have another drink. Go home.
-Take me home.
-Can't you go alone?
-I want you to take me home.
-No.
Call your family. Or call Hae-hyo.
He probably gave Ji-a a ride.
Tell him to pick you up here.
No. Why are you so mean to me?
You…
insulted me.
-What did I do?
What did I do so terribly wrong?
I cherished you with all my heart,
so I always put you first
and was considerate.
Was that so wrong, too?
It's so obvious you're not drunk!
Hey, do you think
I liked everything about you?
You are drunk.
Don't say anything that you'll regret.
-Regret, my ass. Damn it.
-"Damn it"?
Yes, damn it.
I can say it if I want to.
What's wrong with saying that?
Get a grip.
Do you think I still like you?
What?
Do you think your tears
will make me feel bad?
Do you really not like me anymore?
No, I don't.
I really don't like you anymore.
It sure was a mistake.
Don't let it get too far
and end it though.
I hate stories with written endings.
I'm done with relationships
that follow written storylines.
You'll break up in the end
because you can't handle Jin-u.
Even if you can,
your parents won't approve.
Like me and Hye-jun.
Who knew you were a coward?
I can take on my mom even though
she currently has a hold on me.
Taking action is different.
But I believe that parents
end up giving in to their children.
That's true only for the unprivileged.
It doesn't apply
to kids with rich parents.
When push comes to shove,
you'll find out just how strong of a hook
your mom has in your life.
How can you be this handsome?
I'm taken aback every single time.
Your head and face…
-They're tiny.
-Stop it, will you?
Don't you have any complaints?
"Where's my van?"
"Until when must I drive?"
Above everything, you're patient too.
You're terribly stubborn.
So are you.
You'll be meeting the director
of The King Returns.
And Jeong-ha isn't needed for the ad.
The ad agency designates stylists for you.
Can I still eat with her?
The jjajangmyeon is awesome.
It's too bad you had to pass.
Jjamppong is way better.
No, jjajangmyeon trumps.
Have you no love for your agency?
It's jjamppong for us.
It's your company, not mine.
For me, it's jjajangmyeon.
Jeez.
Hey!
Must you rub it in my face like that?
What did we do?
Jeong-ha,
what do you think about being
Hye-jun's personal makeup artist?
It's my idea, not his.
It's not something I can decide on my own.
Besides, I'm exclusive to Hae-hyo.
I would need his permission too.
Your status at the salon will rise
if you agree to it.
The situation is complicated.
Well, I should get going.
You'll soon make it big as a YouTuber.
I haven't even decided on
changing my career.
Let me know how things go.
-Sure. Enjoy your meal.
-See you around.
Is she quitting the salon?
-I don't know.
-Shouldn't you?
My Jeong-ha will tell me
if it's something I should know.
She's not like someone I know
who goes off the grid when cornered.
Until when will you tease me for that?
Until you marry.
That means you'll tease me forever!
How dare you--
Are you saying you'll never marry?
You jerk.
-Hello.
Welcome.
The studio you'll work in…
I mean, the one you might work in.
Let me show you the studio. It's this way.
Thank you.
A one-man YouTuber is impossible.
No one works alone these days.
-Let's raise the key.
-Sure.
Let me take a bite. Hold it like this.
This is how you eat.
Here you go.
From gaining subscribers
to developing contents,
we'll help you in every way.
Gaining subscribers isn't easy, you know.
It requires a strategy.
Even now, countless people
knock on the YouTube business
because they think that yapping in a video
automatically fattens their bank accounts.
You're awfully quiet though.
Any questions?
It's not at all like how I have imagined.
Are you off to see a client?
You must've come in for one.
I decided not to hate you.
It's a waste of my emotions.
So instead, help me leave this salon.
How?
Apologize to me in front of everyone.
Let them know that they're wrong about me.
That's worse than
you splashing water on me.
I won't do it.
Since you want to leave,
I want you to stay.
I can take it, you know.
SU-BIN
I hope this can be of help.
CLICK TO DOWNLOAD
Take off the sunglasses
when you reach the spot,
hang them from the shirt pocket, and halt.
Please keep in mind that all the moves
must be done with fluidity as you walk.
-Let's try again.
-Right.
You'll lose your pace
if you look down as you
hang the sunglasses from your pocket.
That's what I warned you about
seconds ago.
My walk was fine the other day.
Keeping your balance
when walking is key, Mr. Sa.
I see.
Let's talk later.
What?
-It was fun today.
-I'm sure it's nothing.
It's not like she'll kick you out.
You have a smart way
rubbing it in, don't you?
I am clever, for that matter.
I graduated from a nice college.
-Anyway, I'll wait for you here.
-Don't.
-Just go.
-But…
Darn it.
Who took these photos?
My grandson's friend.
-Are they bad?
-Of course not.
I only asked because
I sense love in the photos.
So that's why you asked to see me today.
Then I'll get going.
No, wait.
Have you heard of Premium Silver Village?
Pre… What?
What's that?
A high-end nursing home.
Why the hell is she bringing this up?
Does she receive a cut
for connecting new residents?
I have no money for a room there.
Gosh, no. That's not it.
You've been hired to be in its print ad.
Me?
Even as a model,
I always wanted to be an actor.
It was my major
although I quit in my freshman year.
Being in Love and Guilt will
definitely make you a household name.
You're lucky to have
your next project be of a top writer's.
Are you turning it down?
My next project is my choice.
And whatever happens is my responsibility.
That's a smart answer.
So you'll be passing.
Were you even offered a part?
That'll conclude the interview, right?
-You move fast, Ms. Lee.
-Right.
Lastly, what kind of an actor
do you wish to be?
Someone of this era
who people can relate to
and find comfort in.
That's a heart-warming answer,
but nothing like who you are.
No, that's exactly how he's like.
-It's over now, right?
-Sure.
Thank you for today.
Thank you.
GRANDPA
-May I take this call?
-Sure.
-Thank you for today.
-Grandpa.
What is it?
Really? Congratulations.
-Ms. Lee.
-Yes?
Do you know Mr. Lee Tae-su?
Did he perhaps mention me to you?
No.
I'd rather keep my mouth shut.
Normally people say that
where they actually have a lot to say
or nothing to say at all.
Or when refraining oneself from swearing.
It doesn't mean that
I want to speak ill of him or anything.
I just added my opinion to your assessment
regrading the phrase "I'd rather keep
my mouth shut."
I see you're quite humorous.
I'm glad you think so.
I hope Hye-jun made a good impression.
Let me clean this up for you.
Have a good day then. Thank you.
-Mr. Sa.
-Yes?
Could I have Wooshin Company's
loan application and financial statements?
Just a moment.
-Please take your time.
-Right.
Which series will he join next?
-I don't know.
-How so?
Brothers rarely tell each other things.
Oh, I see.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
Won't he come by for dinner again?
-Should I invite him?
-Yes. It'll be on me.
Can I not come to the office
this weekend then?
It isn't even my shift.
Sure, stay home and rest.
All the more work for me, I guess.
Thank you.
Can you get me his autograph?
This makes me uncomfortable, you know.
This isn't professional of you.
I thought it was on mute.
Mr. Sa, are you kidding me?
-No calls during work--
-I'll get the autograph.
It seems urgent, so go ahead.
-Make sure to keep it on mute though.
-Yes, ma'am.
I apologize.
I hate asking him for favors.
MY FAMILY
Grandpa has an announcement,
so don't be late.
-What announcement?
-Will you be home early too?
-No, I have a commercial to film.
-A commercial?
What commercial?
I'll tell you later.
Why won't he tell us what's it about?
Is Hye-jun filming something?
A commercial.
Good for him.
You might be a billionaire soon, you know.
-Unbelievable.
-Top celebrities easily buy buildings
and turn their lives around.
Don't you be like this either.
That only happens to people
who saved their countries
ten times in their previous lives.
Anyway, what's up with my father?
Jeez, I'm so exhausted.
I saw Hye-jun and his girlfriend today.
Both of them? In a formal setting?
She's the makeup artist
at my regular salon.
Hye-jun goes there too.
I didn't know you go there too, Ms. Kim.
You never call me "ma'am," do you?
It's not like I want you too though.
He said he'd introduce me to her soon.
She's smart and is good at what she does.
I think she's sweet,
but I don't know how you'd think.
Only their feelings matter.
One's feelings are the easiest to change.
Being on good terms now
doesn't guarantee anything.
Hye-jun is
at a crucial moment in his life.
He could become even popular, so
news about him dating someone won't help.
I'm sure he has it handled.
Why bother being a parent
if you're not going
to interfere in their lives?
Lecturing me on parenting
has become a routine of hers.
She thinks it'll bring
Hye-jun up to Hae-hyo's level.
Parents exist to be a shade in the sun.
You never take my advice, do you?
It's why there's never any progress.
We come from completely different worlds
and have separate views
regarding our lives.
Understanding each other seems impossible.
You're figuring that out just now?
SIDE DISHES
Yes?
I don't know which olive oil to buy.
I'll get the most expensive one.
There's one that's most compatible
when making gambas al ajillo.
Then what?
Fine, I'll buy it instead.
Sure. That'll be better for us.
Unbelievable.
Jin-u's mom is a good cook,
but she gets on my nerves.
Are you talking behind her back?
We're close friends,
so don't expect me to chime in.
That's kind of upsetting.
Aren't we close too?
Well…
Well, what?
Jin-u's mom is like that at times.
It's because
she's generous and kind-hearted.
Having her as a friend is the best.
She'll always take your side.
I'm hungry!
You're home early.
Aren't any of your friends free
to join you for drinks tonight?
Hye-jun and Hae-hyo's careers
are on the rise.
When will the galbijjim be ready?
It's for Hae-hyo's family, not ours.
I make side dishes for them now.
Since when?
Did you meet with his mom then?
-Of course.
-Why would you work for her?
Well, she's bored.
You should've stopped her!
Well, I…
I'm against this.
-So?
-Let's have galbijjim, too.
Sounds good.
I'll make some for Hye-jun too.
Where are you going?
Will Hye-jun be late
because of this commercial?
He was vague in his text.
Did you know about his commercial?
I didn't.
I get why I didn't know,
but shouldn't you be more attentive?
That comment is slightly upsetting.
Are you holding me
by a different standard?
You're being overly sensitive again.
This is our son.
And it's natural to be sensitive.
I hear about Hye-jun from Hae-hyo's mom.
I've tried to raise my kids
to be responsible and independent,
so I hate coming across as inattentive.
Unlike you, I never got in their way.
Just forget it.
Bringing it up only makes me the bad guy.
You…
You're home late.
I came as fast as I could for Grandpa.
-Is Hye-jun home?
-Yes, Mom.
-Have you had dinner?
-Yes.
So this is how you look on set.
-You're so handsome.
-I'm your son, aren't I?
Hye-jun…
-Can we talk?
-Let me wash up first.
-He looks like a celebrity.
-He is.
I wonder what it is
that Father needs to tell us about.
Hye-jun, come over here.
I wanted to earn money
so that I could treat the family.
But you haven't yet.
I'll treat them to even something better
when I do.
This is 70,000 won.
I saved the money you gave me.
Fine. I'm glad that my mentoring paid off.
Good.
Father, did you order pizza?
It's here. Let's go.
It didn't take long.
Thank you!
It's on me today.
-Sure.
-Enjoy, Grandpa.
It's good.
Are you seriously eating
when I've yet to take a bite?
When did we ever bother?
How about we start today?
Fine. Go ahead then.
All right. Everyone, let's eat.
-Sure.
-Got it.
It's good.
Father, please tell us now.
I've been chosen for an advertisement.
-Are you sure it's not a scam?
-No. I thought so too,
so I asked the instructor
if I had to pay money.
As if she'd be honest.
That's how they hook you at the beginning.
It's a well-rated academy
which also serves as a modeling agency.
Not everything's a scam, you know.
After seeing the photos
that Jin-u took of me,
everyone's been gushing over
how good I look.
So…
It's not my own opinion.
The people at the ad agency said it.
Congratulations.
Right. Well, I owe it all…
to Hye-jun.
Let's just wait until you get paid, Dad.
Hye-jun's showed you how it can go south.
Nothing's a given
when it comes to this industry.
It doesn't hurt
to be happy about it though.
Even if it does go south,
what matters is that
I was considered for the job.
Who paid for the pizza?
You wouldn't know how,
so it must've been Hye-jun.
He paid for your lessons
and bought pizza to please you.
You're not his son, you know.
You should be the one encouraging him,
not the other way around.
Father…
Why are you crying?
Now I look like a jerk.
This is a reality check.
You're not a jerk at all.
With old age,
tears easily form.
He gave me money for the pizza.
70,000 won.
You, as my dad,
have never encouraged me once.
You've never supported the things I do.
It was only to guide you
down the right path.
Am I a joke to you
now that you're a hotshot?
Why on earth is that your response?
Just answer my question.
Have you ever supported
anything I've done?
There are a number of ways
for one to support another.
Some are strict like Dad
while some show encouragement
from within like me.
You have no right to undermine us.
You're one to talk.
None of it matters
unless the support is visible.
Nicely put, Hye-jun.
It's only encouragement when shown.
-Let's head inside.
-Yes, let's.
Come on. We aren't a bunch of kids,
so why must it always end this way?
I'll say it again.
The support that is never shown
means nothing.
Nothing at all!
Father.
Come on.
Why stay silent?
Say something cool!
When you said he thinks you're a joke
now that he's a hotshot,
you already lost.
What's the point of talking about
losing or winning? We're a family.
"Everything is a complete mess,
but I am happy."
I shall say that to brainwash myself.
Would he be asleep now?
JEONG-HA
Can you talk on the phone now?
Did everything go well at MCN?
I can't really talk now.
I like to make someone shine.
Here goes your "I Like" series.
You were born to be a makeup artist.
That's right.
And you were born to be a star.
You sparkle so radiantly
even when you're not doing anything.
You're such a sweet talker.
What are you up to now?
Just having some beer. What about you?
I'm texting with you.
You must be happy. I'm sure you're
totally focused on what you're doing now.
Yes, I am happy.
Is it me or the beer?
He's not out yet.
Ta-da.
Meet No. 1. It'll take you everywhere
from now on, Superstar Sa.
It has a name? What does it mean?
One, as in one, two, three.
Your first car.
Let's go, No. 1.
Wait!
That's my dad.
Hello, I'm Hye-jun's manager.
I'll introduce myself to you properly
another time.
Oh, sure.
Dad, Mom's saying breakfast is ready.
Who's that?
Hye-jun's manager is a woman.
And she's a good driver.
AN ABNORMAL MAN WHO WANTS TO BE NORMAL
Normal Person is a story about people who
never wanted to be normal
coming to desire normalcy.
Our superstar, Park Do-ha,
met his character,
who is an ordinary guy,
which made the story even more special.
Do-ha, you play the lead,
but you were beaten to a pulp.
Gosh, that was hard.
Hye-jun is a hard puncher.
Oh, I'm just realizing now
that the three of you are the same age.
That's why we had so much fun on set.
Hae-hyo and I are actually filming
the same drama at the moment.
My gosh!
That explains the amazing teamwork.
Hye-jun, why are you so quiet?
How did you play that ruthless character
with such a kind, sweet face?
Thank you.
Being able to take part in a movie
by Director Choi, whom I deeply admire,
was a huge honor to me in itself.
Since I didn't want to disgrace
his name or the movie,
I poured all my energy into it. So now,
I don't really have anything to say.
My gosh, this reminds me of
Gateway!
Oh, my. Hold on.
This isn't part of the script,
but I'm going to get up for a second.
I'm coming over.
Can I ask you to do something for me?
I really wanted to hear it in real life.
Can you say, "Can I ask you out?"
Just once, please.
Can I ask you out?
Yes, of course, you can.
Can I ask you out, too?
Thank you.
Oh, my heart. I need to calm down.
Calm down, my heart.
You're so well-spoken.
No, I'm not.
-Sa Hye-jun?
-Yes, over here.
Please leave it here.
-Have a good day.
-Thank you.
What is this?
The beauty brand sent this for you.
Wait, aren't I their model?
Congratulations on getting this.
I know, thanks.
And a cell phone ad too?
These aren't the only ads. He's been busy.
Here, look.
What is this?
Rom-coms always bring in more ads.
I want to be lucky like you.
I want to hang out, but I have a shoot.
Hey, he's busy too.
He has a meeting with a director.
-It's for my next drama.
-The King Returns.
-You already know?
-Of course, she knows.
You prick…
-Why didn't you tell me?
-Hey.
-Guys.
-Get off of him.
-Hey.
-Look at you.
Hello.
You did well.
What? You just got here.
No, I got here a while ago.
-I saw the whole thing.
-Do you not care about me at all?
Everything I do is for you.
Oh, is that so?
Look at that.
-This is so cool.
-Is it?
How could we lose the ad contract
to Hye-jun?
-Why didn't you tell me?
-If I did,
would anything change?
You're still so full of yourself.
-What?
-You soared to the top years ago.
Frankly, you're going downhill.
I'd say even just maintaining this
is a job well done.
Hey, you're talking to Park Do-ha here.
And you are my manager.
What is with you?
Are you lecturing me now?
Yes, I am!
We've worked together
for about a year now,
so we know a lot about each other.
Like our strengths, weaknesses,
and shortcomings!
Just trust me, okay?
No one cares about you more than I do.
I have to, for my own sake.
I benefit from your success.
You're such a brat,
so I want to just beat you up at times,
but I don't. I try very hard
to be patient around you.
So you should also learn to be patient.
What… What are my shortcomings?
All you have to do
is just keep living this way.
Okay. I'll trust you
and keep living this way.
However, I cannot let Hye-jun beat me.
You said you care about me.
Then what can you do for me?
Do not get in my way.
I will spare your life.
Those who have lived too long
tend to talk rubbish.
Let us handle this.
Go with your brother, Your Highness.
Spare his life if he begs for mercy.
Well done.
Thank you.
-Here.
-Was that okay?
It was awesome. Do you want to see?
Here, look.
The call time for tomorrow is 5 a.m.
-We'll send you the details. Thank you!
-Got it.
-Thank you!
Thank you for everything.
If the call time is 5 a.m.,
shall we sleep somewhere around here?
Yes, that'd be better.
All right.
-Hey, I was so surprised earlier.
-Why?
I wish you were here
to admire this sky with me.
I'll bring you here sometime.
Sure.
I'm off tomorrow,
but no one is coming to see my place.
I should go talk to the realtor.
If I offered help, would you accept it?
I'd say no, even to my dad.
Can I go to sleep now?
How could you get sleepy
while talking to me?
I'm really tired.
I've been looking at commercial spaces
whenever I have time.
But the ones that I like
are all expensive.
Sorry I can't enjoy
this romantic moment with you.
Sweet dreams.
-Hello.
I've listed my place for sale.
How come no one's coming to see it?
Your father took the listing
off the market.
What?
You should have checked with me first.
But do you think it will sell?
Yes, of course.
Can I come and see it tomorrow?
No, not tomorrow. I have to work.
Let's do it on the weekend.
REAL ESTATE
Dad, this isn't fair.
This space is perfect for a beauty salon.
A deposit of 5 million
with 500,000 won a month and no premium.
But it's old.
Come on, just 15 years.
That's nothing for a commercial space.
When can I sign the lease?
-Hi, Dad.
-I'm inside I Like You.
I LIKE YOU
CONVENIENCE STORE
Guess why I like hanging out with you.
You like everything about it.
I can do whatever I want.
Mom would've nagged me
about eating cup noodles.
I thought it was a compliment,
-but I was wrong.
-It is a compliment!
It's so good.
Here.
Home sweet home. Gosh, I'm so tired.
Don't lie down on the couch.
Go to your room and rest up.
No. I'm going to stay right here,
just like this.
Dad, when are you leaving?
If you sell the house,
where will you live?
What I need is money.
I'm sure I'll find a place.
Talking about money totally woke me up.
Don't sell this house.
I'll help you out.
No, it's my life.
I can take care of myself.
I don't want to burden you.
What?
I'm…
I'm sorry.
I completely ruined your childhood.
You must've been worried because
your mom and I fought all the time.
Yes, I was very worried.
If I took Mom's side,
I'd feel guilty because of you.
And if I took your side,
I'd feel bad for Mom.
I also wondered if you were fighting
because of me.
Come to think of it, you're right.
I was always worried about you and Mom
when I was young.
I always tell myself
that I must be strong.
If I start to rely on someone,
I'll be anxious thinking
that person might leave me.
Dad, what are you doing?
Don't be like this.
Don't cry.
You have the right to receive help
from your parents.
Why would I be burdened?
You're simply rejecting me.
You always do this to punish me.
You say that you like me,
but I know that
you haven't forgiven me, deep down.
I'll stay here like this
until you forgive me.
Dad, why are you being like this?
Do not stay too close.
You're smothering me.
This is only making people
stare at me more.
Shall I buy one for you?
What? That is a woman?
We are not buying this.
Meet me at the rear gate at three.
This is where my people live.
Let us move elsewhere.
You should get out of here.
Yu-ri, escort His Highness!
-Please, Your Highness.
-No.
This country's future
depends on Your Highness!
-Please leave!
-If we cannot leave together,
-I will not go.
-Your Highness!
You are my people too!
I will not neglect
any single one of you.
-Gosh!
-Oh, my!
-Sa Hye-jun!
-Wait!
I have a better idea.
Let's create a fan club for him.
Who can make our heart flutter like this?
-Our husbands?
-No!
-Park Do-ha?
Then what should the fan club's name be?
It's for Sa Hye-jun, so…
-Hye-jun, Hye-jun…
-Hye-jun…
-What can we do for him?
-Everything.
Yes, anything for him.
-Yes!
-Hye-jun All the Way!
A SUPERSTAR IS BORN!
SA HYE-JUN, A TOP CELEBRITY
THE KING RETURNS MAKES A STAR
SA HYE-JUN HOSTING THE OVN DRAMA AWARDS
WHO WILL WIN BEST ACTOR?
PARK OR SA?
THE KING RETURNS MAKES
SA HYE-JUN A STAR
HE IS AWESOME
I'M FANGIRLING OVER HIM
HE MAKES MY HEART FLUTTER
I LOVE HIS ROMANTIC EYES
Hey, is this for real?
-Do you want me to pinch you?
-Gosh, no.
-Hye-jun.
-Yes?
You're no longer just my star.
You're on your way to global stardom.
Superstar Sa Hye-jun.
Oh, please.
Even you are being like this?
You must stay focused
even if everyone is excited.
I would if you were overly excited,
but you're always so focused.
-Hye-jun.
-Yes?
If you're named Best Actor,
mention my name during your speech.
-My goodness.
-I won't win that award.
They asked me to host the ceremony
because I'm not getting any awards.
You should ask the scriptwriter
at the ceremony.
No need. I also think
Park Do-ha will win that award.
That's why Hye-jun was
asked to be the host.
Min-jae, you're my manager.
You have to say I'll win the award
no matter what.
You told me to calm down.
Why are you doing this to me?
Because it's fun. Teasing you is fun.
You brat!
SA HYE-JUN NAMED HOST
FOR OVN DRAMA AWARDS
I have to say,
I have such a keen eye for talent.
I have a keen eye for talent,
but I just wasn't patient enough.
Can't you see that I'm here?
Come sit over here.
Yes, coming.
I am coming, okay?
Did you see the article?
Hye-jun and I are both nominated
for Best Actor.
Can you believe that?
Of course, not. It is crazy.
I mean, how dare he?
Sa Hye-jun is no match for you.
That sounded totally insincere.
Jeez, this prick is too quick-witted.
You'll get it, without a doubt.
He's hosting the ceremony.
Why would they ask him to host
if he was the awardee?
They clearly wanted to be considerate of--
He's that big of a deal now?
Yes.
He's a hotshot now.
SA HYE-JUN NAMED HOST
FOR OVN DRAMA AWARDS
I KNEW HE'D MAKE IT BIG
I LOVE SA HYE-JUN SO MUCH
SA HYE-JUN RISES TO STARDOM
PARK DO-HA VS SA HYE-JUN
WHO WILL BE NAMED BEST ACTOR
AT OVN DRAMA AWARDS?
I'm so upset.
They're only talking about
Hye-jun and Do-ha.
Ma'am.
"Ma'am"? Please, Gyeong-mi.
I prefer calling you like that.
I don't like it. I don't want my kids
to think I'm a pompous stuck-up.
What's she saying?
You must be stressed out these days.
Why would I be?
Things are going so well for Hye-jun.
He's hosting the ceremony
and has been nominated.
You've been looking after everything for
Hae-hyo, but his career isn't taking off.
Is she deliberately trying
to get on my nerves?
That's not true.
He'll be named Rookie of the Year.
Also, Hye-jun is just a nominee.
He will win the award.
I'm going to the ceremony too.
Ae-suk asked me to come.
My gosh.
Ma'am. I mean, I-yeong.
Will you be there too?
Now that she's calling me
by my first name, I'm really annoyed.
No, I won't be there.
-Aren't you leaving?
-I am.
I put all the side dishes in the fridge.
FOLLOWERS, 1M
What are you doing?
Mom, I've reached one million followers.
-So you're happy?
-I am, of course.
What is this?
I got it for the award ceremony.
How do you feel
when you see Hye-jun these days?
Well, I'm really happy for him.
He's been through a lot.
That's all?
Why? What else?
I hope he wins the award for Best Actor.
Is it my fault
that you turned out like this?
Probably. You raised me.
-And you raised me well.
-My blood is boiling right now.
How can you smile?
I did all I could
to give you the support you needed.
How could you disappoint me like this?
I can't sleep because of you.
You are the problem. You're too laid-back.
Why are you so excited
about your follower count?
Why am I so excited?
I have one million followers
who are my fans.
Numbers like that are fake.
Do you want to know what's real?
Being applauded on stage like Hye-jun.
You are watching
the 2019 OVN Drama Awards live.
Now, we will announce
the winner for Best Actor
for the miniseries category.
-Hye-jun.
-Yes.
-You must be nervous.
-Me?
-Why do you ask?
-Why, I wonder.
I love what you're wearing today.
It's the most perfect outfit
for this award.
Thank you.
-And you look stunning today.
-Thank you.
-Shall we announce the winner?
-Shall we?
Last year's winner, Song Min-su,
will present the award.
Personally, I'm a big fan of Min-su.
He also started out as a model, didn't he?
Are you two close?
Hello, I'm Song Min-su.
Hi, Hye-jun.
I haven't been able to reach you.
Are you ignoring my calls
now that you're popular?
Min-su, I changed my number.
-For real?
-No, I was just kidding.
I was just kidding too.
When I was standing on this stage
last year,
I was so nervous
that I couldn't really enjoy the ceremony.
Today, I'd like to enjoy it
to the fullest.
First, let's meet the nominees
for Best Actor
for the miniseries category.
BEST ACTOR
Sa Hye-jun, from The King Returns.
If we cannot leave together,
I will not go.
Park Do-ha, from Catch.
Jeez, call the cops!
Those are the nominees.
Let me cut to the chase
and announce the winner.
The 2019 OVN Drama Awards.
Best Actor for the miniseries category
goes to…
I see. This actor is the winner.
Sa Hye-jun, The King Returns.
Congratulations.
BEST ACTOR
Thank you.
SA HYE-JUN
Who knew this day would come?
Up until just a year ago,
I was an unknown aspiring actor
who had multiple part-time jobs.
My grandfather encouraged
and supported me all through those years.
Thank you, Grandpa.
And Mom, I love you.
Last but not least,
all the members of Hye-jun All the Way.
Thank you.
Subtitle translation by Won-hyang Son
RECORD OF YOUTH
This doesn't feel real.
Yes, I was upset so many times.
Min-jae, have you seen Jeong-ha?
You left out Dad though.
Must you be so childish?
What is it that you want to be?
A star or an actor?
I hate being compared to Hye-jun.
I'm Hye-jun's friend.
-Don't do this again.
-I really miss this.
Just don't get a photo taken
hugging each other or something like that.
Do you know someone named Charlie Jung?
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs