Watch on kisskh.me
[Moonlight]
[Episode 10]
Watch on kisskh.me
Being a commercial writer isn't that bad.
Without a slight desire
to write,
you can't write anything popular at all.
Besides, I've read it.
You really poured your heart
into this book.
Listen.
Don't be fooled by Mr Zhou Chuan
and think he is above you.
That fellow
is only good at twisting words.
You'd better not
talk to him about life
or ambition whatsoever.
He's toxic.
I really want to record all these
and send it to Zhou Chuan.
Oh, don't.
Let's just continue eating, Mr Jiang.
Why isn't she back yet?
[Corner Bookstore]
[Hi, we have received your submission
under science fiction genre.]
[But it's far from what we imagined.
Hope we can collaborate in the next one.]
Here's your coffee.
Thanks.
[The Long Goodbye]
[You like this book too?]
[Yes, I do.]
[Why?]
[It's supposed to be a detective fiction]
[but my mind is not only on the mystery.]
[I'm more intrigued]
[by the characters]
[and how they cross paths.]
[It's exactly Raymond's charm.]
[I like this book too.]
[Every character]
[has his or her own story.]
[Moreover his writing]
[is known for one unique feature.]
[He uses simple]
[but very precise words]
[to illustrate]
[the deepest thoughts of his characters.]
[Very intense.]
[How I wish]
[my novels are as good as his.]
[You're a writer?]
[Yes.]
[I write mostly]
[detective mysteries.]
[I'm an editor.]
[Really?]
[Yes.]
[If you don't mind,]
[I can look at your novel.]
[Sure.]
[I'm Jiang Yu Cheng.]
[I'm Gu Bai Zhi.]
Can I help you?
No, it's fine.
[I bought these couple watches
when I got married.]
[I'm thinking of saving them]
[as a wedding gift to you and Xiao Jiang.]
[No, Ms Liu.]
[Mr Lin left them for you.]
[I'll be seeing him soon.]
[Why do I need these?]
[My only hope is that
you and Xiao Jiang are together.]
[I can then leave in peace.]
[What are you talking about?]
[Gu Bai Zhi]
Hello?
Just two hours later
and you got yourself this drunk?
Sis.
What is it?
Jiang Yu Cheng.
Why didn't you pick up?
[Are you done?]
[It's just a contract.]
[Can you get it over with?]
I'm starving here.
I haven't eaten anything
after I finished writing.
Can you return my editor to me?
Without Chu Li you'd starve?
If Chu Li doesn't read the manuscript,
I can't eat.
Are you crazy?
You kept her this late.
You're the crazy one here.
Not even a single reply.
What happened?
She left long ago.
If she didn't reply your message,
why don't you call her?
Right.
Er Gou, let's go.
Let's go for a walk.
Go for a walk.
Mr Zhou Chuan.
It's already so late.
You want to walk the dog now?
Who's walking the dog?
Why didn't you reply my messages?
What took you so long?
You've been talking to him
so many times before.
Aren't you done talking already?
You've gotten attached to him?
Mr Zhou Chuan.
What's brewing in that head now?
My phone died.
I was just seeking advice from Mr Jiang
on book publicity
and ways to engage with
physical booksellers.
Why don't you ask me?
You know about these too?
Are you kidding?
Of course I don't.
Forget it.
Let me make you some chrysanthemum tea
to calm you down.
Make tea? I'm starving.
Make me something to eat.
Have you sealed the deal
on Jiang Yu Cheng's new book?
Not yet.
I want to wait
for the birth of your masterpiece.
The printing house is going to
run out of paper very soon.
I didn't know you have a grudge
on the printing house.
Why are you so confident?
What got into you?
[I've walked the dog.]
[Not Drama King, it's Saviour]
[What do I need you for?]
[Why aren't you back yet?]
[Is there so much to talk about?]
[I'm dying of hunger here.]
[From now onwards,]
[every minute you take to reach home]
[is causing you a hundred in rent.]
Mr Zhou Chuan.
Book of Luo He God is going to print.
You must be nervous.
You should be the one feeling nervous.
You went for a jog and
walked the dog at seven,
showered and set your hair at eight.
Now you are here in time
for breakfast with me.
Isn't this a little too much for you?
I remember Mr Jiang say that
once you are nervous,
you'll try to become a normal person.
You should be the one feeling nervous.
If this book failed to sell,
it won't be the end
for Yuan Yue Publishing House and me.
But without a doubt,
you won't be my managing editor anymore.
[This person who gave me
my first contract]
[will turn into]
[a stranger?]
Don't you think
I'm particularly virtuous and classy?
I'm done talking.
I'm going to office now.
Why are you working on a Sunday?
That's all thanks to you.
You are simply
too important to us.
For the coming Sundays,
our entire department is working overtime
just for you.
Goodbye.
Out on weekends?
You think this is a hotel?
Sis, you're up.
Here.
Why are you in my house?
I called you yesterday.
The bartender answered
and told me you were drunk.
I immediately went to get you.
I'm sorry. Thanks.
Do you still have a headache?
Take this pill.
[Jiang Yu Cheng]
Did I say anything last night
that I'm not supposed to?
[Reading Club]
[Reading. The City Never Sleeps]
You're early.
Don't tell me you're here to buy books.
I called you last night.
But when I answered,
you didn't say anything.
I guess you must have called by accident.
Is there anything else?
I visited Ms Liu.
Her condition isn't too good.
Soon
she might even forget me.
Some things
are better forgotten.
Can I ask you for a favour?
Go ahead.
Can you accompany me to visit Ms Liu?
[Yuan Yue Publishing House]
[Count down 15 days]
Mr Xia has gone out for a meeting today.
I'll chair this meeting.
Book of Luo He God
is at the final phase.
Chu Li,
circulation department informed that
they lack of manpower.
You'll have to write
the subscription letters.
I think you should prepare
all the letters today
along with the information sheet
so that the circulation department
can send them out
to the various dealers
first thing next week.
No problem.
I think once we obtain the first
subscription quantity from the dealers,
we'll know
where this book stands
in terms of sales potential.
Chu Li.
350 thousand
is the figure you set.
Hence,
you have to work hard.
[This figure]
[is now mine to bear.]
Mr Liang has been very supportive.
He visited major bookstores nationwide
to obtain a two-week placement
at 32 Guanghua Bookstores,
increasing the exposure
for Book of Luo He God.
Guanghua Bookstore?
Two-week placement?
That's great.
Chu Li.
Don't get too excited just yet.
Yuan Yue Publishing House may seem to be
scrambling high and low
to achieve the 350 thousand mark
that you set
for your book.
However,
you're still a rookie
who's too young
and lack experience.
350 thousand is an astronomical figure.
I think
it's not possible at all.
Well...
Chu Li is a newcomer.
Not only her,
Deputy Editor Miao,
even you can't achieve this figure too.
But having said that,
with the support we get from
marketing and circulation departments,
who knows
we can really achieve it.
If a newcomer like Chu Li
really achieve it,
won't it be a slap in your face,
Deputy Editor Miao?
Fine.
I'm not afraid then.
If this book can really
hit that figure,
I'll give her my title.
Really?
Alright then.
We'll work hard towards this.
Alright.
You're right on time, Mr Zhou Chuan.
I'm preparing the subscription letter
for your Book of Luo He God.
The publicity wordings used in the letter
may be used for the blurb
on the belly band later.
Come over.
Let's do this together.
If I do your job,
then why do I need you?
Just come over and do this together.
I'm looking at other belly bands
for some inspiration.
This is easy.
You just need to brag.
The key is to make it your own
and thought-provoking.
Let me summarize it for you.
The most common is
recommendations by famous figures.
The more figures the better.
The more famous the better.
Look at this one.
Just a few words in large font.
"No wonder Murakami read it twelve times."
This is a world class author.
It's not surprising Murakami likes him.
Yours is writer's mentality.
You have to think of
the hidden marketing logic.
Think about it.
A book that Murakami read twelve times.
How can people not buy it?
The vast reader base of Murakami
must buy it.
And once is not enough.
You need to read it twelve times.
Those who had this book
will have to buy it again.
Isn't this brilliant?
After looking at so many samples,
I now realize that copywriting is a craft.
Just like romance.
You must know how to tease.
Do you know that 80 percent of readers
find belly bands redundant?
They will just throw it away.
They will have to buy it first.
Money-minded editor.
Don't come near me.
Mr Zhou Chuan.
How would you tease?
Tease who?
Readers of course.
Should we say you are
the Chinese Tolkien?
My book has nothing to do
with magical rings.
How about Chinese Martin?
That Game of Thrones writer.
♫ I want to hide like a kid
who made mistakes ♫
You're more like him.
It has dragons and what not.
♫ My heart skipped a beat ♫
You can have a thick face
but not a dispensable one.
♫ When you look at me
everything seems so cute ♫
Don't let me down.
♫ I am the only one feeling strange ♫
This is so hard.
♫ I have got a million whys ♫
♫ But I can't tell ♫
Mr Zhou Chuan?
♫ I still have my sanity ♫
Mr Zhou Chuan.
I've finished writing.
Please take a look.
I need to submit this tomorrow.
♫ I fled for a week ♫
♫ You don't seem to be surprised ♫
What do you mean
closing in on the grandmaster
author Jiang Yu Cheng
♫ Because when you look into my eyes ♫
vows to shed his boy-next-door image?
Is this the wisdom you learn
♫ I have told you a thousand times ♫
from the seniors all night?
Miao said
subscription letters must be
fiercely exaggerated.
♫ The world is on
the verge of elimination ♫
At critical moments,
you have to use other writers
as scapegoats.
♫ Only you are still favoured by me ♫
After thinking very hard,
writers who were once famous
but won't hold a grudge on you
♫ Because when you hold me in your arms ♫
if you use them as scapegoats
only come down to two persons.
The first is Mr Jiang Yu Cheng.
♫ I have never felt so right ♫
The second is Mr Zhou Gu Xuan.
♫ If this is not love ♫
♫ What can I tell myself ♫
So you know this is worthy
of a good beating?
I'm just voicing out the dream we share.
I want the book to be a hit.
♫ I have got a million whys ♫
You want to
step out of your boy-next-door shadow.
Everyone wins.
You really think Jiang Yu Cheng
is so good?
He is close to losing his own shadow.
You want me to emerge from his shadow?
♫ Because when you look into my eyes ♫
Come here.
You think I won't hit you?
♫ I have told you a thousand times ♫
Don't be mad.
I can just remove that sentence.
I don't want my dear landlord
♫ You don't have to guess ♫
to die young.
Please rest early. I'll leave now.
♫ How much I depend on you ♫
Stop there.
♫ Because when you hold me in your arms ♫
♫ I have never felt so right ♫
♫ If this is not love ♫
♫ What can I tell myself ♫
The season is changing.
Why are you running around bare-footed?
[I visited Ms Liu.]
[Her condition isn't too good.]
[Soon she might even forget me.]
[You know,]
[Ms Liu and Mr Lin]
[are like my mother and father.]
[You'd better be at your best.]
[I will.]
[Ms Liu.]
[You're here.]
[Give me your bag.]
[Come over here.]
[Why did you bring so much?]
[You're welcome, mother.]
[Who are you calling mother?]
[It's fine.]
[I'm sorry.]
[Put them down.]
[Come.]
[The kids are here?]
[Come to the table. Time to eat.]
[Come, come.]
Mr Liang.
The first batch consists of
87 booksellers.
These are the subscription forms.
Mr Liang.
What is the subscription quantity?
The total is 45,200 copies.
For the final conservative estimate,
hitting 200 thousand isn't a problem.
It's only been the first day.
The subscription has already exceeded
our breakeven point for printing.
Is it really 45,200 copies?
You must have saved the world
in your past life.
You met such a great writer.
Mr Zhou Chuan.
45 thousand.
45 thousand on the first day.
We have over 400 more booksellers
in queue.
I got it.
Looks like
we can achieve a solid
six digit sales volume.
See? I told you, you can do it.
That pathetic little contract
can never
stand in your way.
My books are popular.
Those booksellers
are like bears coming after honey.
It's also months of publicity stunts
that I did.
I worked hard
on the subscription letter too.
I know.
Good job.
Do you know
I'd revised over 20 versions
of that subscription letter?
I still have all the records.
I can show you if you don't believe me.
Are you done?
Should I research on
how to praise an elementary school kid?
I'm just happy.
Let me take you to a place.
This place is so pretty.
♫ Dream flies above the horizon ♫
♫ Night asks for dawn to come ♫
What a pretty sight.
♫ Yet I'm still here ♫
♫ Waiting for a mapless journey ♫
Let's go.
♫ The stillness you stirred ♫
[Xinghe Road]
♫ Fear is forgotten and
so is that time on the rooftop ♫
Keep walking.
Why are you stopping?
♫ Every footprint turns into
a stubborn silhouette ♫
♫ Nobody wants to be the first
to let their heart sway ♫
♫ The wind quietly brought in a letter ♫
♫ It tells that meetings and partings ♫
This is
♫ Are to carry on the eternal light ♫
Xinghe Road.
♫ Glaring thoughts should not be heard ♫
I know.
You know the legend of Xinghe Road?
Legend? What legend?
♫ Hide in a corner away from the light ♫
According to legend,
♫ Waiting for you to come ♫
couples who walked on this road together
will always be together.
You don't know
but you brought me here?
How old are you?
Do you still believe in legends like this?
You're probably right.
♫ Love is a variation ♫
♫ Occassionally melancholy,
occassionally full of bliss ♫
♫ I once looked up and
the rain stopped filling the sky ♫
♫ Because you sheltered my tears ♫
You should look where you go.
He's far enough. He can't hit me.
♫ From falling ♫
You should still avoid it.
It's common sense.
Mr Zhou Chuan.
I need to go to the editorial department.
Isn't today a Sunday?
Why are you going to work?
Circulation department wants to
see the online publicity banner
for Book of Luo He God tomorrow.
Ah Xiang and I will probably
work overnight on it.
Why are you working so hard?
You are not paid for overtime.
Who am I doing this for, mister?
Aren't you doing it for yourself?
I'm doing this for an ungrateful wolf
who spits sarcasm
without a clue
of people working overtime for him.
Ungrateful wolf?
I didn't say anything. I'm going now.
[Gone just like that.]
[The subway is closed.]
[Zhou Chuan]
You must be hungry.
Quick, eat something to fill that tummy.
Chu Li, put them aside first.
Tell me the cover feature
of Book of Luo He God.
Let me take a bite first.
Alright.
This is so good.
Book of Luo He God.
Special paper for book jacket
and belly band.
Imposition printing.
Single-side art paper for inside covers.
70gsm munken papers for inside pages.
Please speak human language.
What do you think? Am I impressive?
I worked hard to memorize them.
I just want to brag.
Impressive.
The cover uses
double-layer hollow design.
The rough sketch is inserted
to show the perfect integration
[Book of Luo He God]
of tradition and modern times.
[Mr Zhou Chuan is hungry.]
[I've ordered take-out.
Do you want some?]
[Zhou Chuan]
Have you decided on the giveaways
that will get the readers
excited about going to the site?
I did some research.
Some wanted autographs, manuscripts
and also extra volumes.
Chu Li.
Come take a look.
What do you think
about this publicity banner?
[An oriental fantasy masterpiece
from best selling author Zhou Chuan]
[Book of Luo He God]
It's good.
Good.
Hello?
Chief Editor Yu.
It's me, Zhou Chuan.
Hi, Mr Zhou Chuan.
Can I help you?
I just want to know.
I've been trying to call my editor
about the online pre-sales of my book
but I didn't get any response.
Is she alive?
Mr Zhou Chuan,
your managing editor
is still alive.
[Online pre-sales is going well.
Please don't worry.]
[Chu Li]
[must have been exhausted.]
I'll remind her
to check her phone.
I'm glad the online pre-sales
is going well.
All good now. Bye.
Chu Li.
Chief Editor.
Do you need anything?
You must be tired.
The online pre-sales is going well.
You've worked hard.
Thanks, Chief Editor.
You and Ah Xiang can go home now.
Take a good rest.
Oh, right.
You'd better check your phone.
[The subway is closed.]
[Not Drama King, it's Saviour]
[Mr Zhou Chuan is hungry.]
[You probably need
to take a cab home tonight.]
[An additional fee is incurred
if you take a cab at this hour.]
[You're still in the office?]
[Are you still working
on the online pre-sales?]
[Your risk of sudden death is increasing.]
[You have a nice bed at home]
[but you rather sleep in the office?]
[Are you out of your mind?]
Miss.
Do you go to gym?
Miss, I can give you a discount.
You don't look fat
but you can still strengthen your body.
Our trainers are all award winners.
No, thanks.
Our equipment are very good.
Look at our facilities.
Look.
Stop pulling me.
Your fee is equivalent to
my monthly meal expenses.
Let me go.
I'm sorry.
Why are you so rude?
Just tell me if you're not interested.
Why did you push me?
You used violence on me.
You have to compensate me.
Compensate?
These papers
probably cost 20 yuan.
Do you want me to print a few hundred more
to build you a shelter?
These are colour prints.
It costs me one and a half
for one piece of paper.
So many pieces here.
You have to pay me 300 yuan.
If not, I'll call the cops.
300 yuan?
Call the cops then.
I can sue you for extortion or something.
You...
Don't run.
You can't go if you don't pay.
Stop pulling me.
Compensate me first.
What's going on?
Get up.
I'm scared
just because you have company.
You still have to compensate me.
Compensate...
He hit him.
Don't act on impulse in future.
Although the other party started it,
using violence in public
is still wrong.
We got it.
Thank you, Mr Policeman.
Get on.
I'll carry you on my back.
What?
Did you hurt your head too?
I said I'll carry you on my back.
Did I not make myself clear?
But...
What is it now?
Can you hurry up?
Don't let me squat here
in front of the police station.
About that...
The online pre-sales is almost ready.
We are just waiting for web support now.
The circulation department
is working on it already.
For the exclusive giveaways,
what do you think we should give?
Autograph?
Autograph might not be that attractive.
Not attractive?
How about lucky draw for forwarded post?
This is very important.
Do you have any private item?
Private item?
My editor's head.
Oh, right. Mr Zhou Chuan.
Why were you on the street today?
You weren't even walking the dog.
I was on my way
to the convenience store.
Nothing odd about that.
Why don't we take a cab...
[Chu Li, don't forget our appointment]
[Flying Elephant]
[with the printing house
tomorrow evening.]
[Flying Elephant]
[I won't go the office tomorrow morning.]
[Mr Zhou Chuan wants to
have a meeting with me]
[about the exclusive giveaways.]
[Chu Li]
Get up.
Disinfect your wound before you sleep.
You'll get an infection if you don't.
If you don't get up now,
I'll pull out your pants.
Don't think that you can get away
with your good looks and writing skills.
I'll call the cops
if you do something to me when I'm asleep.
I just want you to get up
and take off your pants.
What?
You have to disinfect that knee.
You have been out all day.
Are you going to fall asleep
with all that?
Alright, I got it.
I can't take off my pants with you here.
Go downstairs now.
I'll take them off once you're gone.
You can't fool me with that.
It's a trick to get me out
so that you can continue sleeping,
isn't it?
No, no.
You go out first. I'll take them off.
Alright?
I'll come up to check in a while.
You sound like
a teacher
checking on a student's homework.
Go now.
Hello?
Buddy.
What got into you?
I'm not used to this.
What's the matter?
I think I'm undergoing puberty.
What happened?
I suddenly realize
the deep physical meaning
in gender distinction of mankind.
Man
and woman.
I don't understand.
It's tiring to explain to you.
Go downstairs to apply medicine
and come back up to bed.
You can sleep in tomorrow.
I've applied leave for you.
Just go to the printing house
in the evening.
Why are you fixing my schedule?
Flying Elephant texted you.
You looked at my phone?
The message popped up
according to your setting.
I can't unseen it.
Since I've seen it,
I decided to apply leave for you.
What's the problem?
This did sound like me.
I guessed it right.
You
always talk behind my back
with your colleagues.
"Mr Zhou Chuan is running late again."
"Who does he think he is?"
"The centre of the universe?"
You added that last one.
Your leg.
Stop jumping.
The stairs will collapse.
Don't you know you are heavy?
I must thank you for your trouble
to carry me home then.
I'm glad you know.
Get on.
Since I've started a good deed,
let me carry you down.
Thank you, Mr Zhou Chuan.
Go slow.
You pulled an all nighter
just for that 350 thousand.
If you don't hit that target,
you have to carry me
around the neighbourhood.
I don't want to.
Be gentle.
Are you making some embroidery?
At this rate,
it will take you forever.
Let me do it.
You know how to treat wounds?
I attended first aid training.
Thank you, Mr Zhou Chuan.
You really don't want to slit the wound
to check for residues?
What if the wound heals
with the residue still inside?
Let me do it myself.
Eight Treasure Congee?
Why is it so salty?
Mr Zhou Chuan.
I'm really sorry
I got up late this morning
and did not make you breakfast.
Oh, right.
Give me the phone number
of this take-out restaurant.
I want to file a complaint.
Food has dignity too.
This Eight Treasure Congee
is supposed to be sweet.
This is salty and inedible.
I made this.
You made this?
Actually, it won't be salty
after adding hot water.
Then you should have more.
Eight Treasure Congee can boost your qi
and nourish your blood.
It's perfect for hard workers like you.
You made this congee just for me?
Yes.
I'm afraid if you work yourself to death,
no one can help me
hit the 350 thousand target.
I knew it.
Hello? Chief Editor Yu.
Really?
I'll tell him now.
Good news.
Pre-sales of your book starts next week.
I'll hashtag you
on all official platforms.
You must forward them out.
The more the better.
I'll have to pass this congee.
I need to go to the printing house now.
It's really too salty.
I've booked a cab for you.
I'll pay for it.
Goodbye.