watch on kisskh.me
[Moonlight]
[Episode 09]
Shut the gate if the pipe broke.
Why are you covering it with hands?
What if the metal pipe broke?
You would've broken your hands.
Mr Zhou Chuan?
Put the clothes on first.
What's the matter with you?
Why did you return all of a sudden?
This is my house.
Can't I come back?
I haven't asked you.
What did you do to my pipe?
Perhaps it's broken due to
your sudden return.
Really?
And maybe it's because
I patted it lightly.
Patted it lightly?
Which rainforest
are you from, King Kong?
Pretending to be a monkey
and destroy my house.
Didn't you say
you'll be back in several days?
Is this the reason
you ran around with your pyjamas
and turned my bathroom into
Waterfall Cave?
You... You saw it?
I'm not blind.
Stop covering!
You'll smother yourself!
Where's your manners?
Look people in the eye
when they're talking to you.
I've seen it all anyway.
Just smother yourself.
Why are you being reasonable
now that you've seen it?
Why can't I look
if you dare to wear it?
I'm going back to the room and sleep.
Just say I'm not around
if someone looks for me.
Tell them you don't know where I went.
Especially if it's my father
and Jiang Yu Cheng.
Hold on!
You haven't told me
why you came back all of a sudden.
Is it because you had a fight
with your family
or with Mr Jiang?
The 30th rule of the tenancy rules.
All right, I'll stop asking.
From my experience,
your father must be in a bad mood.
Hello.
Hello, Mr Jiang.
Why do you call me at this hour?
Mr Jiang, I'd like to ask you.
What happened to Mr Zhou Chuan?
He looked upset
when he came back just now.
[He seemed to have quarrelled with
his family this afternoon.]
We planned to have dinner tonight
but he didn't come too.
As I expected.
But how did you know he went back?
Isn't there a location feature
in the chat software?
[Perhaps when we were having
conversation just now,]
the distance between us
was shortened by dozen kilometres.
Is there such a function?
Yes.
It's getting late.
Get some rest.
I'll stop bothering you.
Goodbye.
[Breakfast is on the table.]
[Microwave it for
two minutes before eating.]
[Chu Li]
Chu Li!
Big trouble!
Cocoon urges the entire illustrator world
to boycott Yuan Yue Publishing House.
Saying that our editors
are hard to communicate
and always rush her
to submit the drafts.
She said we even find fault with
her drafts after handing them in
and threaten the illustrator
with rejection.
Come in.
Mr Liang,
there's something I need your help.
You
can mess things up even by just
making appointment with an illustrator.
Ask Yu Yao
to clean this mess up for you.
I can't help you.
Mr Liang.
[Book of Luo He God]
Look at this calligraphy.
Doesn't it have an overbearing impact
in comparison to those books
in the same genre?
[Book of Luo He God]
An overbearing impact.
I'm sorry.
It's hard for me to admire
your poor aesthete's taste.
Just explain it to me.
We can follow the trend.
This is a type of mindset.
Everyone is wondering
if Yuan Yue Publishing House
could create something unique.
No one has ever
used this traditional ink and
calligraphy as the cover.
It's outdated.
That's why no one use it.
It's not outdated. Why is it outdated?
If we only use it
as couplets on the cover,
that will be boring
and outdated for sure.
But if we use a kind of
special display technique,
then this calligraphy
can be cool as well.
Then have you thought about
the reason why you want to
use illustrations as the book cover?
I've thought about it.
It's because many readers think
that would fulfil their fantasy
if their imaginary characters
appear vividly on the illustrations.
Right.
Then why do you want to
break their illusion?
Don't you think it's cruel?
I'm not trying to break their illusion.
I just want to try
a different display technique.
For example, we can
use this calligraphy on the cover
and use hollow technique
to vaguely reveal the illustration inside.
It will be more
attractive with this way.
And it can fulfil
the readers' fantasy as well.
Are you here to apologise?
But it's too late.
I just went to the legal department.
This is the termination agreement
they drafted.
If you're furious with
Yuan Yue Publishing House,
we'll agree to terminate the agreement.
But we will not return the drafts
and we own the use-right.
You still have to pay us twice the fine.
You guys were the one to spite me
and you still have
the audacity to fine me?
Who's the one that
refused to communicate
and violated the contract?
You knew it well.
Do you want me to
remind you with the chat histories?
I didn't hold you to account
because Yuan Yue Publishing House
is a big company.
We don't want to waste time
to deal with an ordinary illustrator
because of some trivial matters.
That will dishonour
Yuan Yue Publishing House
and Mr Zhou Chuan.
Who are you scolding?
But it's different now.
You're complaining around.
You assaulted me
in every illustrator group
with your illustration.
Have you forgotten
the privacy terms in the contract?
For this reason alone,
I can legitimately terminate
the agreement.
If you did that,
no illustrator will be willing
to cooperate with you.
You don't have to care about that.
Mr Xia
has invited a famous calligrapher
to write an epigraph for
Mr Zhou Chuan's book.
I can't believe you'll use
calligraphy as the cover.
This is our official account.
It has been forwarded over
ten thousand times in a short time.
The readers are cheering
in the comments.
They said the cooperation between
Zhou Chuan and Yuan Yue Publishing House
is a transboundary between
emerging art and traditional art.
Terminating the agreement
won't affect us in such situation.
But it's different for you.
Soon, everyone will say that
we terminate your agreement
is due to your terrible work.
Tell me.
What do you want?
The second plan is
your drafts won't be rejected.
Let bygones be bygones
but you have to sign
a complementary agreement
to agree that your illustrations
can only be used
in the poster or inside cover.
Only inside cover?
Think about it.
I'll leave first as I'm busy.
There's a truth that
I always wanted to tell you.
Your ability is outstanding.
But I was young and ignorant
to like you.
Director Gu, it's me.
Director Gu,
what should I do?
You have to help me.
This is quite a major controversy.
Director Gu, I
didn't meet the deadline
because of you.
I just asked you for
the cover of Yun Fei.
You can't complete the job you took
and now you're blaming it on me.
It won't do me any good
if you screw up.
I have ways to give us an out.
I'll do anything you want.
Chu Li,
look, Cocoon just issued a statement.
She said people got the wrong idea.
"It has nothing to do with
the editor of Yuan Yue Publishing House."
"I worked well with
Yuan Yue Publishing House."
"We even had coffee
together this afternoon
and discuss about
Mr Zhou Chuan's new book."
She even posted the photo of the cafe.
It's really hard for her.
I guess her heart was bleeding
when she wrote these words.
[Sorry,]
[the user you're calling is unavailable.]
[Mr Zhou Chuan,]
[I've taken care of
the matter of the cover.]
[You'll be satisfied.]
[Chu Li]
Chu Li.
Mr Xia.
This cover
is interesting. Look.
Monochrome calligraphy
is eye-catching
[Book of Luo He God, Zhou Chuan]
and Cocoon's colourful drawing
can be seen vaguely.
It's the combination
of modern and traditional.
I'm very satisfied.
This is my idea
but it's designed by Ah Xiang.
You've done a great job
in such a short time.
Ah Xiang,
I think
you're as good as Cocoon.
Youngster like you
should express yourself more.
Don't always hide in the back.
Okay, the design of this cover
will be settled once it's completed.
The next step is to collaborate with
the circulation department
in publicizing it.
Right, Chu Li.
I heard that you assured Miao and Liang
that you can reach the sales volume
of 350,000 for the book?
All right.
That's brave.
But you have to walk the talk.
I'll try my best, Mr Xia.
Oh my god!
Is Mr Zhou Chuan
experiencing depression?
Brother, are you still alive?
Mr Zhou?
Mr Zhou, what do you want
to have for dinner?
I don't want to eat.
Dinner is on the dining table.
Remember to eat it when you come out.
Mr Zhou, I've taken care
of Cocoon's cover.
You don't have to worry.
[Do not disturb]
This can't go on.
What are you doing?
Open your door.
I can't hear you with the door closed.
I said what...
Why don't you get up?
It's improper for man and
woman to be too intimate.
What does that mean?
Where is the last pretty boy
in 21st century like we said?
What's going on
as you look like a caveman?
Get out.
Mr Zhou,
how long do you plan
to lock yourself?
You don't even update
your article on the internet.
The readers thought you went missing.
Do you know that cause for concern?
What's going on?
Why do you take it on all by yourself?
Why is your face
so big?
Right, right.
I know I'm a freeloader.
And I bother you
with the matter of publication.
It's true that I am bold.
But we live under the same roof after all.
We are not friends
but we are more than
just a nodding acquaintance.
I'll ask you even if you think
that I'm nosy.
What happened when you were
in your hometown?
What's with all those emotions?
I just asked you
why your face is this big.
I mean your facial shape
is big.
Then,
how about this?
Why are you playing dumb?
Can you get out?
I'm fine, I just want
to rest for two days.
Every job provides annual leaves.
Is that too much for a writer
to rest for several weeks?
This is not a break.
You're attaining mortality.
As your editor,
I can't sit there
and watch you ascend.
I don't need an editor
to worry about me.
How about this?
Let's eat out later.
It's my treat.
I know there's a restaurant nearby
which sells delicious beef pot.
Let's go.
Eat out?
The 7th rule of the tenancy rules.
"No outside food as cover-up."
And you violated the 8th rule just now.
"Taking advantage of
living under the same roof
to do something beyond the
relationship between the landlord
and the tenant is forbidden..."
Stop!
The 4th rule. "Respect your landlord."
The 5th rule. "Respect..."
I'll get out first.
If you don't come out in half an hour,
I'll let Er Gou destroy this house.
♫ I want to hide like a kid
who made mistakes ♫
♫ My heart skipped a beat ♫
♫ When you look at me
everything seems so cute ♫
♫ I am the only one feeling strange ♫
♫ I have got a million whys ♫
[Author Zhou Chuan]
"I'm seduced by the light."
♫ But I can't tell ♫
♫ I still have my sanity ♫
The poet of Mountain Cave Faction
in there!
What light do you mean?
Are you having illusion as
you've locked yourself for so long?
♫ I fled for a week ♫
It has been half an hour.
I'll let Er Gou out
♫ You don't seem to be surprised ♫
if you don't come out.
♫ Because when you look into my eyes ♫
Shut up.
♫ I have told you a thousand times ♫
Good morning.
Have you finished writing the book?
Why do you mention book
once you see me?
Go back and write it
if you haven't finished.
I refuse to.
Exercising makes me
feel better when writing.
Then just exercise near your house.
Don't come here.
The air and view here are good.
That makes me more energetically.
Yun Fei,
I'm not a young lady.
I know what you're thinking.
I'll make it clear with you.
This won't work for us.
Why won't it work?
You are
a young lady to me.
What's wrong with me?
I won't date the author.
Do you refuse to date an author
or me?
I heard that
you had
dated Mr Jiang Yu Cheng before.
Right?
Just ask the one
you heard it from.
Then just leave this aside.
What if I
like you?
I want to court you,
and I want to date you?
I have a headache.
Did you have a fight with your family?
Did Jiang Yu Cheng tell you?
He really has a blabbermouth.
No, no. He didn't say anything.
I just guessed it.
You asked me
if I have no childhood
or I'm heartless.
Why I don't miss my time as a student?
I really don't miss it.
How is it possible?
People like you...
You have good looks
and you're talented.
You're great in writing
and you're graduated
from top university.
Your school days
should be your finest moment.
Let me tell you a story about a friend.
[Father,]
[have you read my manuscript?]
[Is it all written by you?]
[It should have more
than 200,000 words.]
[I didn't count the words.]
[When do you start to write it?]
[I think I started from senior one. ]
[I wrote it once I had the time.]
[How is it?]
[I finally realize]
[the reason why your result]
[didn't improve]
[in your senior years.]
[You wasted your time and energy]
[on writing this meaningless stuff.]
[This stuff?]
[Then what kind of
stuff did you write?]
[What kind of attitude is that?]
[A man should know his place.]
[You've been rejected
by several publishing houses.]
[It wasn't for no reason.]
[I can hardly read]
[half of your manuscripts.]
[I don't know what you're writing!]
[Tell me]
[what you're trying to say.]
[Does your novel
mention any real life?]
[Does it have any social sense?]
[Does it have your own thought?]
[Nothing at all!]
[Some of them is just self-righteous]
[wit and pubertal venting.]
[A shallow novel like this
which is only for entertainment]
[will never be
considered as literature.]
[I can teach you the correct]
[literary writing]
[after your college
entrance exam ends.]
[I don't want to write anymore.]
[What does that mean?]
[Does the stuff you
write have any point?]
[You are just imposing]
[your value on others.]
[Saying that your
writing is meaningless,]
[this is me being gentle.]
[If I were to be harsh,]
[I would say what you write is trash!]
[It's a waste of papers!]
[Are you satisfied?]
No way!
That was cruel!
How could he tear his son apart
after working so hard to raise him?
Are you talking about my father or me?
You guys are in the same strain.
So,
Oriental Beauty is not
your first novel.
It's not. My first novel
was called trash by my father.
So, now you know why I refused to
sign the contract with Miao.
Apart from being a glib,
he always talks about
father-son enterprise.
"Mr Zhou senior must
be very proud of you."
"Father and son make a literary family."
He would say the words that I
hate the most in my life
within ten seconds.
So,
I could only tell him to stay out.
Mr Zhou Chuan, I didn't expect
there's such bitterness
behind your smile.
I didn't expect you can still create
Oriental Beauty, such masterpiece
after your maiden work was torn.
I really admire
your indomitable spirit.
Did you learn this
exaggerate expression from Miao?
Do I look alike?
Your flattering gaze isn't alike.
But Mr Zhou Chuan, to be honest.
I believe that you can get back up
in front of your detractors
after Book of Luo He God is published
and say aloud,
"Look, I did it!"
You can invite me if you think
you have insufficient aura.
Why are you staring at me?
I... I'm just thinking that
you look cute today.
But your face is big.
Here, here!
Eat a sweet ice cream when you're upset.
I don't want to eat it.
Try this ice-cream.
It's very delicious.
I don't want to.
It's too sweet.
Right, it's quite sweet.
Let's go home early.
Er Gou is waiting for us to feed him.
I warn you.
Don't engage in such
boring activity anymore.
Okay.
Sister.
We have a special rapport.
Why are you here again?
I'm here to court you.
Are you free tonight?
I'll eat with you.
I'm not free. I'm going somewhere.
I'll come with you.
It's a private matter.
I... No.
I'll never disturb you.
I'm already here, sister.
Get in the car.
So, this dictionary is published!
I'm not dreaming, right?
You're not dreaming.
I thought
once the data dictionary has launched,
this thing I made
would be completely worthless.
Why would it be worthless?
The gold will shine one day.
I put seven years of my life into it!
It's not wasted.
I can
retire comfortably now.
Why didn't you take Jiang with you?
Has he finished writing his new book?
His new book is already on sale.
He is too busy recently.
I'll take him to visit you
after some time.
Okay, okay.
Time to eat.
Let me treat you
with a cup of juice tea.
Then,
I want to tell you a good news.
Thanks for your juice tea.
What is the good news?
After a few days of the publication of
The Disappearing Amusement Park,
there're many letters from the readers.
I think it's obvious
that Mr Jiang Yu Cheng
will become famous again.
I'll be happy as long as Mr Jiang
could keep writing
new articles.
Then I pray for your teacher
to keep on writing and succeeding.
How is it?
Everyone come take
two movie tickets from me.
Movie ticket?
This is the perk comes with Yuan Yue.
There's a replay of a movie
about an author and an editor this week.
By then, you can
watch it with an author
who is close with you.
It's a chance to build
rapport with them.
Okay, thank you, Chief Editor.
Okay.
Thank you, Chief Editor.
Chu Li.
The respond of
Jiang Yu Cheng's serial is good.
This is the publishing contract of
The Disappearing Amusement Park.
But
the minimum guaranteed print run
the Marketing Department provides
is the same with Book of Luo He God.
He said since you could score this number
and handled Zhou Chuan, then
you can also handle Jiang Yu Cheng.
But the styles of these two authors
are totally different.
I know. I know.
It's hard.
But... That's why you should find a way
to take Mr Jiang and make him
sign the agreement promptly.
I understand.
I'll try my best.
All right.
Then do you want to
watch it with Mr Zhou Chuan
or Mr Jiang Yu Cheng?
Make your own decision.
Do you mean the movie?
If I invite Mr Zhou Chuan,
he'll tell me not to bother him
with such boring activity.
And he'll stick these two movie tickets
on my forehead as if they are
Demon Sedative Amulets.
Sister,
is Ms Liu your relative?
Don't ask something you shouldn't.
When is that dictionary
published?
Why haven't I seen it before?
That dictionary was planned to publish
but it got cancelled.
Ms Liu had made painstaking efforts in it.
She couldn't accept that
and had sudden cerebral haemorrhage.
That's why she lives here.
I see.
So, Ms Liu is your senior.
Then why was the publication cancelled?
Why do you have so many questions?
That's because I want to know you more.
Okay, I'll ask other people
if you don't want to tell me.
I was Ms Liu's apprentice.
As for the cancellation
of the publication,
who would buy
a paper dictionary nowadays?
The era has changed.
Mr Zhou Chuan.
The new books are on the shelf over there.
Okay, thank you.
Mr Zhou Chuan.
Chief Editor Yu.
What a coincidence!
Right, that's a coincidence!
I was talking to one of my authors.
Right, has Chu Li invited you?
Our company
has given out two movie tickets
to each person.
If Chu Li invites you,
please accept her.
This...
About the movie, I...
I don't really like to watch movie.
Why don't you ask her
to invite other person?
I think Chu Li must be really sincere
if she invites you.
Just consider it as a senior
taking the junior to edify sentiment.
And let her learn from you.
All right.
I'll reluctantly agree to it
if you say so.
Mr Zhou Chuan, you're a gentleman,
very generous.
I'm sorry, I've got a call.
I'll go to work first.
Go ahead.
-Goodbye.
Hello.
Just call that number will do.
Mr Zhou Chuan,
are you going to
walk the red carpet?
The Ideal Empire?
The original version of
The Ideal Empire is written in Greek.
You're reading the
English version which is
translated from the Chinese version.
There are two languages in between.
It will create biases
from the original text.
I suggest you
to read the Chinese version.
Those translation experts
are professional after all.
I'm going to cook now.
Teacher, I've drafted the agreement.
I'll send it to you
if you're free tomorrow.
What are you doing?
Who are you talking with?
Mr Jiang, who else would it be?
Tomorrow is your day off.
Why don't you sleep in?
Why do you want to send agreement?
Just send it to him by delivery.
Why do I have to send delivery
while we're living in the same city?
Yuan Yue Publishing House
has given me two movie tickets.
Let's go and watch it together
if you're free.
It's about author and editor...
You're going to watch
the movie with Jiang Yu Cheng?
Are two of you close enough
to watch movie together?
And Yuan Yue Publishing House
doesn't stipulate that
Jiang Yu Cheng must watch it.
It gave two movie tickets
for you to watch it
with anyone you like.
Right, Yuan Yue Publishing House
didn't stipulate
the person I want to watch it with.
But aren't we going out
together tomorrow?
We can watch it together then.
Give it back to me.
Then
what movie are you planning to watch?
City of Words.
This movie is replaying recently.
Of course I know it.
You know it?
Why?
Am I not allowed to take interest in
theatrical and biography movie?
I'm planning to watch it too.
You're planning to watch it?
So,
don't watch it with Jiang Yu Cheng.
First come, first served.
I said I want to watch it first.
It's me who stand in front of you first.
Isn't one of these
two movie tickets supposed to be mine?
That's not reasonable.
Why is it not reasonable?
We have the same editor.
Ain't I your author?
Yuan Yue Publishing House didn't mention
that you must give
this ticket to Jiang Yu Cheng.
Why can't you give it to me?
You make me feel dizzy.
[Okay, then see you tomorrow at noon.]
[I'll buy you lunch.]
[What do you want to eat?]
Let's go and watch it tonight.
Let's eat out and watch the movie.
Don't do that.
It's just a movie ticket.
It's only 38 yuan.
Aren't they money?
38 yuan is money as well.
How about this?
Both of you go and watch it.
I'm not going.
Two authors watch this kind of movie?
What are we going to do?
Complaining about
how unreliable the current editor is
or teasing each other?
"This drained author looks like you."
"The arrogant and annoying look
of this male lead looks familiar."
Okay, I surrender.
How about this?
You and Mr Jiang, each of you will get
one of these two free movie tickets.
I'll buy this movie ticket which
costs 38 yuan with my own money
and sit between you guys.
I won't give him a chance
to tease you for being arrogant.
And I won't give you a chance
to tease him for being drained.
That's okay, right?
Can you leave here
if there's nothing else?
Can you cut the potatoes
and beef for me
if you have nothing to do?
We're having beef
stewed with potatoes tonight.
I want to eat pizza
tomorrow at noon.
Ask Jiang Yu Cheng to treat us.
Chu Li,
why is he here?
He? He...
Unfortunately,
while you're maintaining
the relationships
of author and managing editor with her,
so am I.
One order of red wine
bovine tendon pizza with thin crust.
Extra cheese, thank you.
Why do you wear like this today?
You can only wear it out
if you were ten years younger.
I've never seen your suit too.
Why? Did you buy it last night
and ask for urgent delivery?
Aren't we here to watch movie?
Why do you wear
like a playboy?
This is to respect the lady.
Who would be like you?
As if you were going to
walk the red carpet of the Oscars.
I look formal with whatever I wear.
I can't help it too.
I'm frustrated too.
I want to eat chicken pizza.
I'm sorry, Chu Li.
It's easy to be childish
when being with someone.
Follow her orders.
And extra cheese.
[City of Words]
Chu Li.
You eat snack after having meal?
Is your stomach an abyss?
I'm full that
I'm almost puke as the pizza is huge.
That's because
you've eaten too much, okay?
I...
Here.
Thank you, Mr Jiang.
It's all sweet.
Are you treating her like a child?
Have you heard a saying?
Gift blind the eyes.
I'm helping you to
accommodate the awkwardness
in case your food is wasted.
Didn't you just have meal?
Why are you eating again?
I just ate a small piece.
You're heavy enough.
You...
Why do you say something this harsh?
I tell you what.
If Er Gou was a female,
he would have left the house.
Thanks for speaking up, Mr Jiang.
Someone is really poor
as he's mooching meals.
You even want to
treat us dinner after lunch.
Are you thinking that you're rich?
I suggest you to transfer it
to my bank card.
I want to treat Chu Li to dinner
not you.
I'm just planning to
go to the same restaurant.
I didn't say I'm going to mooch meals.
I'm not telling you
which restaurant we booked.
Then I insist to follow you
and see which restaurant you go.
Why don't we go back home
and have our own meal?
I agree.
I have someone to prepare
three meals for me anyway.
You've hire a new maid?
And you have the audacity
to follow us?
You must be rich then.
I didn't hire a cooking maid.
She even walks the dog, writes
and watches television with me.
Who is that unfortunate
to become your girlfriend?
It's said that the cover illustrator of
Book of Luo He God
has a crush on you.
The time matches too.
Is it really Cocoon?
Am I blind?
Then who is she?
[Watch your mouth and your language.]
[Little Monkey]
[Beware of ruining my innocence.
Is your girlfriend looking for you?
Go home and accompany her.
Do you think I like to
follow you around?
[Not Drama King, it's Saviour]
[Go home with me.]
Mr Zhou Chuan, goodbye.
Be careful on the way home.
He really left.
[Not Drama King, it's Saviour]
Mr Jiang,
can we talk about
the publication contract?
Mr Jiang, take a look.
The number in the agreement
is the same with Zhou Chuan's
Book of Luo He God.
But...
I'm sorry, Chu Li.
I think you know
what I'm going to say.
I, too, know
what you're going to say.
It doesn't matter that the minimum
guaranteed print run is less.
What matters is Yuan Yue
Publishing House can sell it.
As long as the sales
of this book is high,
then you'll pay me a reasonable royalty,
right?
Did you convince
Zhou Chuan with the same way?
Seems like Mr Zhou Chuan
has complaint to you.
Of course,
there're many other reasons.
Zhou Chuan
is arrogant
and has Eighth Grader Syndrome.
Perhaps he's full of ego too.
He's willing to sign
Book of Luo He God over to you.
It's more of
having self-confidence
than having faith in you.
You're right.
I know that.
But I'm different.
About The Disappearing Zoo,
I've created a miracle
in the sales volume
of rookies in the publishing industry.
For the second and third series,
each of them was
the famous book for everyone.
They were placed on
the best-seller spot in every bookstore.
But the fact is
every book I wrote has been
in downward trend since then.
Those two books that
I recently published
have poor sales too.
I can't afford to lose.
Mr Jiang.
But I've said that
I'll give you a chance.
What chance?
Please give me a satisfying figure
after Zhou Chuan's
Book of Luo He God is published.
Like you said before,
prove it to me.
Let me see
your value as an editor.
If you can't even handle
a famous author
like Zhou Chuan,
then don't even think about
helping someone like me.
It's embarrassing to talk about
the sales volume and
the terms of royalty
in front of my fan.
Do you feel disillusioned?
No, I don't feel that way.
I'm different from Zhou Chuan.
Right, you guys are quite different.
He only wants to write happily.
For me, I want more.
Mr Zhou Chuan publishes
his book with rage.
He wants to show that his father
was wrong with his achievement.
You've shifted with the market
from the beginning.
You're the chosen one,
a best-selling author.
Everyone gets what they need.
There's neither lowliness nor nobleness.
Being a commercial author
is nothing to be ashamed of.
If you have no desire
to write,
then things you write
will never be a big seller.
Moreover, I've seen it.
You are genuine when writing this book.