[Please]
[Express]
[Please Feel at Ease Mr.Ling]
[Episode 1]
Watch on kisskh.me
Fell into the sea
of love~ Do you also have expectations~
Want to feel your breathing rate up close~
To experience all your emotions~
Fell into the sea of love~
To sing love songs for you~
Willing to use the best metaphors for you~
Are you crazy? Driving so fast! Hey!
[Harvard Business Review]
President Ling, President Chen's wife sent these handmade cookies over this morning.
First, there's no a list of ingredients for the food.
Second, there is no certificate allowing the creation of this food.
Third, there is no government safety certification. Take it away.
I understand.
[Greentown]
[New Way]
President Ling, President Ling Fang's actions are too big recently.
Don't worry about it. Just observe for now.
Yes, sir. The meeting with the Vice President of Jiang Group is scheduled at 3 tomorrow at Michelle Hotel.
Vice President Jiang often uses work as an excuse to extort and harrass.
Cancel the meeting. We don't need a collaboration like this.
Greetings, President Ling.
Let's begin.
Unlike the past where we only considered the increase in speed of our designs,
this time through our customer experience, we are full scale improving this-
Do you have a question, President Ling?
It's equal and greater. Not greater.
I apologize. What are you referring to?
Your HTML code is missing a greater and equal to.
I apologize! I will change it right now.
Once a code is implemented, a targeted attack to steal data from beginning to end
only takes a few hours.
Yet it takes several months for us to find loopholes.
Then what are you going to do about the customer information leaks that have happened in this time?
You don't need to come to work tomorrow.
Enemies meet on narrow roads.*(One can't avoid meeting someone they don't want to)
Quick service!
-Ok, thank you.
-Please choose Quick Arrival again.
Thank you!
President Ling. President Ling.
-President Ling.
-This is President Ling's flowers.
President Ling, flowers in memory of your mother.
-Go ahead with your work.
-Ok.
International news now.
Last afternoon, a store in America's Nebraska state
Shelby prefecture had an elevator malfunction.
The 3 women and 1 man within the elevator all died.
In particular, the man died tragically
caught between the elevator and shop floors.
When the rescuers arrived, said man had already lost consciousness.
Anxin, you're back!
I'm back.
Anxin, you just got back?
Yep, it's time to get off work too.
That's right. Hey,
did you switch shifts with Xiao Li again? You're too nice.
What's wrong with that? I receive money for working overtime anyways.
Ok, then. I have to go home early today.
The weather report says there's lightning and rain today. I haven't taken in my laundry yet.
Then hurry and go home.
I'm leaving! Bye!
Bye!
[Quick Arrival Delivery Service]
Urgent report from the weather channel.
Between 1 pm this afternoon and 10 pm tonight, there will be thunderstorms.
Please be careful when outdoors.
There is heavy traffic in the Kang Jia Ling neighborhood.
Streets are slippery on rainy days. Please drive carefully and avoid tailgating.
[Kang Jia Ling Road 184 meters ahead]
Rerouting for you.
Final destination, Glass Cemetary.
Please turn left at the crossroads ahead.
Follow closer. Follow closer.
What- Why'd he switch roads? Did he notice us?
Don't worry. I'll catch up in the next intersection.
Alright.
Call President Ling Fang first.
President Ling.
President Ling, we've lost him.
You can lose him that easily?
He suddenly turned at the intersection. We couldn't do anything.
Then hurry and chase! Search all the routes to the cemetary.
Brother! What are you up to hiding over here?
You scare me? Scare me? Scare me?
You've gotten courageous, huh. When'd you get here?
Why do you always hit my head?
Let me tell you, if you keep doing this, I'll go tell Second Brother.
Oh, right. Where did Second Brother go?
Don't always think about your Second Brother...Second Brother. I'm your actual brother.
It's all the same.
Of course not.
Let's go. I'll take you to eat some good food.
-Your treat?
-Of course!
Let's go.
Don't panic, don't panic.
[Express Delivery]
Hey!
Wake up!
Hospital, hospital!
- Make room.
- Please, make room.
Excuse us, please make room.
Make room! Make room!
Make room, make room.
Wait here, we'll go find a doctor.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, they're going to find a doctor.
How are you?
Are you okay?
Have you seen this person?
- I haven't.
- Look carefully. He's this tall. He's injured.
What's wrong?
I wasn't—
S-sorry, I-I...
I didn't do it on purpose.
Please step away for a moment.
- Push him in.
- Okay.
We have already arrived at the scene.
This is where the accident happened. Right now, everyone can see
the medical personnel have already arrived. The police and firefighters have started a search and rescue effort.
Up to this point, they have not found any injured persons.
For further developments, please stay tuned to our channel.
Dad! Mom! Dad!
- Dad!
- Dad, Mom!
- What's the matter?
- Ling Yue, h-his car fell into the ocean.
The p-police are searching now.
Then how is he? How is he?!
Second Brother, he... he may have also fallen into the ocean.
What did you say?
That's impossible.
How could this happen?
- Dad!
- Lao Ling!
- Go call an ambulance!
- Today at around 1pm,
the President of both Ling Group and Niu Wei, Ling Yue,
drove a Blank Benz with license number Ak805
into the ocean.
Now the police have already pulled the car out of the water, but Ling Yue is not inside the car.
The search and rescue team is widening its perimeter.
We will continue to follow up with further information.
It's so late and we still don't have news.
I'm afraid it bodes ill and not well.
It's best if he doesn't come back.
Ling Tian is getting old and useless.
His eldest son is responsible for managing real estate.
His youngest son is always messing about in the entertainment circle.
What's most important is e-commerce.
That was always the responsibility of his second son.
Now he is missing. Our opportunity has come.
Xin'er, notify the marketing department.
We must immediately expand our business while Niuwei is without a leader.
It's time we retake the top spot in e-commerce.
[Beilun Changzheng Orthopedic Hospital]
Hey, don't move. Be careful not to strain your injury.
Who are you?
- I...
- Let me borrow your phone.
What do you need to use my phone for?
To call the police.
- Why are you calling the police?
- You crashed into me.
No, no, I can explain, that's not what happened.
Then just handle it by reporting to the police.
Please, if there's a problem, we can talk it through.
Can you not call the police?
Please.
Then who am I?
You...
You don't know who you are?
I only remember that you crashed into me.
How do you feel?
A little dizzy.
Doctor, didn't he injure his leg?
How come I feel like his brain isn't working right either?
Judging from the examination, there shouldn't be a problem.
But getting hit from an outside force can cause a light concussion.
That can bring about temporary memory loss.
Outside force?
I didn't—
Then, how long will his condition last?
That's hard to say. Two to three days,
or several months are all within the realm of possibility.
First pay the fee, then take the bill to get medicine.
Rest well.
Pay the fee.
Thank you.
[¥35,981 (~$5,600)]
Excuse me, may I ask,
can you give a discount?
There are no discounts.
This... why is it so expensive?
Was the head of the hospital the operating surgeon?
The surgery fee isn't expensive, but doesn't he also have to be hospitalized?
Then if he doesn't stay in the hospital, how much does it cost?
¥13,000 (~$2,000).
Then let's not stay in the hospital.
What a handsome face. It would be such a shame if it left a scar.
You should buy insurance for this face.
My face didn't get injured too badly, did it?
Even a small injury is an injury.
You have to look after even a small injury.
I'll leave now.
Thank you.
The doctor said you don't have to stay in the hospital.
You just have to come back for a follow-up visit at the set date.
I'll go down to complete the paperwork to be discharged from the hospital.
You can get your things ready, and then we can leave.
Did you hear me?
What is this?
The compensation you will have to pay.
A professional carer,
nutritionalist, Hilton presidential suite.
Total expenses equal 300,000 yuan.
(~$47,000)
Are you blackmailing me?
Then call the police. Have the police take care of it.
A collision that results in an injury is not a minor charge. Not to mention whether or not my leg will have long term consequences,
the compensation and damages from absent at work alone are more than 300,000 yuan.
And you'll also have to go to the police station, be detained for three to five days, and cooperate with the police investigation.
Do you still think I'm blackmailing you?
Didn't you lose your memory?
You've lost your memory yet you're going to this extent—
I did lose my memory, but I didn't become stupid. Past experiences are still in my head.
Let's talk about the compensation instead.
I really don't have money.
After I paid the bills,
I now only have 1,888 yuan left.
(~$300)
Wait a moment.
Sister Li.
Anxin, shouldn't you pay your rent for this month now?
No, Sister Li. I just sent it to you a couple days ago.
I told you long ago. The rent increases this month. Did you forget?
By fifty—
No, Sister Li. Isn't fifty percent a little too high?
Little sister, many people are fighting for your house.
I saw that life isn't easy for you so I never rented it to someone else.
If you're tight on money, then how about you make some room for others?
I can't, Sister Li. I'll send it to you. I'll send it right now.
Bye, Sister Li.
[Devil Landlord]
[Sent 1,000 yuan
Rent]
[Remaining balance 888 yuan.]
Eight, eight, eight. This number is quite auspicious.
Look, I really don't have money.
I just paid my rent.
- So?
- So...
So...
So, how about...you live at my house?
My house is pretty luxurious.
It won't be much worse than that...Hilton Hotel.
And if you need any carers,
I can be your carer. Does that work?
It's not that it won't work.
But you'll have to write me an IOU.
I, Gu An Xin, on the evening of May 5,
accidentally crashed into and injured the victim.
To compensate for the victim's variety of losses,
I am willing to listen to the victim's requests.
During his recovery period, I will provide a place to live and take care of his daily life
until the amount owed 280,000 yuan is paid in full.
(~$43,000)
Can you be discharged now, Mr. Victim?
[IOU]
What do I call you from now on?
Anything.
But I can't keep calling you "victim."
As long as you can pay attention to the road, you can call me anything.
I only have 888 yuan left in my card today.
How about I call you...Xiao Ba. Okay?
(eight is pronounced "ba")
Anything is fine.
Just say "anything." Why  be mean?
Here.
People can really live here?
What do you mean by if people can really live here?
I've lived here for years now.
Then which floor do you live on?
The second floor. Right there.
Slowly.
Let's go.
You don't have an elevator?
Only stairs.
Moreover, it's only the second floor. I will help you up.
What?
No need. Just lead the way.
I can walk myself.
What do I wear?
I only have one pair of slippers.
How about...I give you one. I'll go buy new ones for you tomorrow.
Totally luxurious.
Drink some water.
What is that?
This is something that all cups have when used for a long time.
Probably water marks.
It's fine. You won't die. Drink it.
It's clean now.
Where do I sleep?
I can't sleep on the couch, right? I'm still a patient.
I'll give you a tour of the bedroom.
You draw comics?
I doodle when I'm bored.
I'm just a delivery man.
Sit anywhere. I will tidy up this place for you.
Don't touch.
Is that your mom?
Does it have anything to do with you?
Just asking.
I'm telling you, you can sleep in my bedroom.
but you can't touch anything in my bedroom.
These are all my treasures. I bought them with my savings.
Heard me?
No need. I will sleep on the couch.
Theres no air conditioning. Only a fan.
If you think it's too hot, then you can only bear it.
What is it?
The couch can't be placed under the fan.
Why? Are there any Feng Shui specifications for that?
It's too dangerous.
How is it dangerous?
Either you move the couch,
- Cou—
- Otherwise,
if you don't mind, I can sleep in the same room with you.
You...you look pretty normal. You aren't going to do anything to me, right?
Not necessarily.
- I'm warning you—
- I'm also warning you.
You still owe me 280,000 yuan.
(~43,000)
Not 280,000 yuan.
It's 272,000 yuan.
(~42,000)
The water bill, room and board,
the tricycle, and the costs of my care.
Adding all of this up, it's about 8,000 yuan.
(~$1,000)
So now, I still owe you 272,000 yuan.
So was your service more expensive or this shabby house of yours?
How is my house shabby? I even have a luxurious big bathtub.
Furthermore, my service is 24 hours,
personal service. This is cheap enough already.
How personal?
Within 3 meters,
1 meter away.
Okay.
Then listen carefully.
I only drink mineral water. I only use 100% cotton towels.
The lights must be out in the living room by 11:00 PM. You're not allowed to bother me after that.
I've only thought of these. I will add on when I think of the rest.
Why does your brain work so well even though you've lost your memory?
I will emphasize this once more. I have a temporary memory gap.
Not dementia. Those who can't do anything when they lose their memory only belong in tv dramas.
Go, move the couch.
The Big Bad Wolf and Little Sheep
Why is there still so little clicks?
You can eat cup noodles at noon, a very good deal.
Breakfast is on the table.
Your mineral water is in the fridge.
Second-hand clothes are under the couch.
Yellow one is mine. Blue one is yours.
How come there's a fire at house 208?
I heard the microwave caught on fire.
- 208?
- Yeah.
What happened to my house?
In the future, when using appliances, you must be careful.
Don't put metal in the microwave.
Microwave...
You've never used a microwave at your house, right?
If you have nothing to do, go take a stroll outside. Don't mess up the house.
This is all money.
Damage of appliance, 600 yuan.
(~$100)
My phone number.
If you run into trouble then call me but I hope that you have no reason to call.
Okay?
Hello?
Anxin, your brother broke the beer bottles in my store. You should come over quickly.
Brother?
Look at what my beer bottles have become.
- Sorry, sir.
- The delivery just arrived.
This beer is very expensive.
Your brother broke the whole crate.
I'm going to lose a lot of money.
That's all I have in cash right now.
When I get my paycheck I will send the rest to you immediately. Okay?
- Seriously.
- I told you to go take a stroll outside.
I didn't tell you to go out and take money for a walk.
- Hello?
- My son is crying and scared because of your husband.
Sorry, little kid.
You're Gu Anxin?
Why is a grown-up taking toys from a kid?
Can you watch your husband? Seriously.
I'm really sorry.
Little kid, sorry.
You can't sit still, right?
You can't let me do my work, right?
Anxin, there's a problem with your attendance lately.
You shouldn't disappear in the middle of work anymore, I'm reminding you out of goodwill.
Got it. It won't happen next time.
Hello?
Is this Gu Anxin? Your brother is lost. Come pick him up.
I'm warning you. You better have thought it carefully.
If you injure me you will have to compensate.
The ride fare for coming home today,
50 yuan. Damages from loss of work...
Damages are 600 yuan. And on the way back,
you got hungry and bought some food.
Fatigue fee.
Put it down.
I'm telling you, the most valuable thing at home
is this television. It's the most treasured by the landlord.
If it breaks, neither of us will be able to pay for it.
Look,
this red button.
If you press it, it will turn on.
Press it again, it will turn off.
You actually don't have to worry about the other buttons.
Just remember this one and it will be enough.
Give it a try.
He's crippled but has quite a big temper.
Toi...toilet. My toilet. Toilet.
What happened?
There's something in the bathroom.
Where?
It came out.
Just this?
- Is it really funny?
- Of course it's really funny.
Your size is a waste. You're afraid of cockroaches.
- Do you know how many types of bacteria are on a cockroach?
- How many?
- There are 48 types.
- Wow.
It can carry around at the most, 48 pathogens.
Parasite eggs, fungus, bacteria, and all that.
They will spread a lot of viruses.
Isn't the problem solved if you just step on them?
You think it ends with stepping on it?
Do you know how many larva it can create?
How many?
A single cockroach can produce 84 larva.
So, you're saying that there are 84 cockroaches in my house?
That's right.
I'm telling you, you haven't realized the severity of this issue.
Enough. Stop nagging.
I'll go buy pesticide for you tomorrow.
This cost will be your responsibility.
Because prior to your arrival, there were no cockroaches in my house.
What do you mean?
You mean that I brought this bacteria in?
I didn't say that. You said it yourself.
Oh right. I also need to remind you.
When it's the dead hours of the night,
and you're lying on the couch,
there are 84 cockroaches in the house now,
in case they crawl, crawl, and crawl in the night,
and crawl onto the couch,
take care.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com